message_id,text,entities,annotation
<11792830.1075859955495.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Good catch.  NY law should apply throughout the Americas and in Japan.  We 
used UK law in Europe and Singapore on the theory the counterparties there 
would be more comfortable with Uk law.  I'm not sure which the Australians 
would prefer.  What do you think of the following:

16.  If you are accessing this website from North America, South America or 
Japan, the terms of this legal and Privacy statement shall be governed by the 
laws of the State of New York; if you are accessing this website from any 
other location, its terms shall be governed by English law.



	Leonardo Pacheco@ENRON","[{'word': 'Leonardo Pacheco', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'NY', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Americas', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Japan', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Europe', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Singapore', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Australia', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'North America', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'South America', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Leonardo Pacheco', 'PERSON'), ('NY', 'LOCATION'), ('Americas', 'LOCATION'), ('Japan', 'LOCATION'), ('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Singapore', 'LOCATION'), ('Australia', 'LOCATION'), ('North America', 'LOCATION'), ('South America', 'LOCATION')]"
<16461482.1075846947944.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Tana,
Wow, you are really on the ball.  Looks like we will have a great party. I 
will email
Matthias and Karin about the potatoe recipe and Stephen Long about the garlic 
bread
recipe.  Judy Weller's phone number is 713-524-7567. And Mark and I are 
willing to
bring whatever; Ulf might want help with the pork chops and chicken.  How are 
plans
with the grill going?  We can always bring ours if you know of someone with a 
truck we
could borrow.
Peace,
Beth

Tana Jones wrote:

 I got several responses last night and this morning by email, so I am 
attaching
 a revised list.

 (See attached file: church gourmet.doc)

   
                                 Name: church gourmet.doc
                                 Type: Microsoft Word Document 
(application/msword)
    church gourmet.doc       Encoding: base64
                          Description: Mac Word 3.0
                      Download Status: Not downloaded with message

 - lcm.vcf","[{'word': 'Tana', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Matthias', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Karin', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Stephen Long', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Judy Weller', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mark', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Ulf', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Beth', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Tana Jones', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Tana', 'PERSON'), ('Matthias', 'PERSON'), ('Karin', 'PERSON'), ('Stephen Long', 'PERSON'), ('Judy Weller', 'PERSON'), ('Mark', 'PERSON'), ('Ulf', 'PERSON'), ('Beth', 'PERSON'), ('Tana Jones', 'PERSON')]"
<27347038.1075842439828.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I am very pleased to announce that L.D. Stephens has accepted the position of 
Account Director in the Business and Power Development group of the Northern 
Natural Gas Marketing Division.   L.D. has been with Enron for 18 years and 
has held many positions from Field Technician to Field O&M Supervisor to 
Regional Team Advisor.  Most recently L.D. was a Sr. Facility Planner and had 
primary accountability to provide planning support to the commercial 
activities of the Business and Power Development team.   L.D. has a B.S. in 
Industrial Technology from Southwest Oklahoma State.  He will be located in 
Omaha and will manage a number of projects primarily in the area of on system 
power development and ethanol market development.  

Please join me in welcoming L.D. to our group.

Thank You. 
John Dushinske","[{'word': 'L.D. Stephens', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'John Dushinske', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Northern Natural Gas Marketing Division', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Omaha', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Southwest Oklahoma State', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('L.D. Stephens', 'PERSON'), ('Enron', 'PERSON'), ('John Dushinske', 'PERSON'), ('Northern Natural Gas Marketing Division', 'LOCATION'), ('Omaha', 'LOCATION'), ('Southwest Oklahoma State', 'LOCATION')]"
<22015863.1075844739388.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Chris:

We should chat.  Per the ISDA, ENA is the calc agent and we have already 
agreed to usual Market Disruption Events and fallbacks in the ISDA.  If you 
want to change the ISDA agreement, then we can consider the items which 
Merchant has included in the draft.

As calc agent, we should create a draft and send the form to you for review.  
However, I do need you to explain/verify Floating Price B.  And verify 
rounding convention which differs from our standard.

Please call to discuss. 


Sara Shackleton
1400 Smith Street, EB 3801a
Houston, Texas  77002
713-853-5620 (phone)
713-646-3490 (fax)
sara.shackleton@enron.com



	Chris H Foster","[{'word': 'Chris H Foster', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sara Shackleton', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '1400 Smith Street, EB 3801a', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Houston, Texas  77002', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'ENA', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ISDA', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Merchant', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Enron North America Corp.', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Chris H Foster', 'PERSON'), ('Sara Shackleton', 'PERSON'), ('1400 Smith Street, EB 3801a', 'LOCATION'), ('Houston, Texas  77002', 'LOCATION'), ('ENA', 'ORG'), ('ISDA', 'ORG'), ('Merchant', 'ORG'), ('Enron North America Corp.', 'ORG')]"
<27358009.1075862249772.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I have made additional changes on pages 11-12 on the Northwest adaptations to make LMP work.  I have indicated the kinds of adjustments from the PJM platform necessary to make it work.  I don't think is necessary to take a swing at Mark Mayer of BPA to make our point that LMP will work.  Mark was caught flat footed and unprepared for Dick O'Niell's cheap shot.  Second, the proportion of hydro and the mix of other units is quite different in PJM and NYISO, so the fact that they fit hydro in around the edges is not necessarily proof that it will work in the PNW.  For that reason, I have noted the mix of units (hydro and base load) to show that the unit committment process will be different but you can still produce hourly prices.
 
Steve","[{'word': 'Mark Mayer', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'BPA', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': ""Dick O'Niell"", 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Steve', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'PJM', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'NYISO', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'PNW', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Mark Mayer', 'PERSON'), ('BPA', 'PERSON'), (""Dick O'Niell"", 'PERSON'), ('Steve', 'PERSON'), ('PJM', 'ORG'), ('NYISO', 'ORG'), ('PNW', 'ORG')]"
<16106780.1075840819692.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Louise:

You requested that I give you a list of things to avoid discussion with ABB.  We've maintained a reasonably open relationship with ABB up to this point, but here are some (fairly obvious) things that we should probably steer clear of:

1.  No discussion about Fronterra;
2.  No specifics about the DeAcero contract, e.g. extension date, CP's, etc; and
3.  No discussion about project credit issues or financing alternatives for the project.

When this ABB contingent was here last (Feb 2001), Dave and Janet essentially indicated that this was an important project to Enron, that we were entirely committed to seeing it through and that if it weren't for the damn CFE, we'd already be done, etc. etc.  I think if we stick to that line, we'll be fine.

If I think of anything else, I'll let you know ASAP.

DTT","[{'word': 'Louise', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'ABB', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dave', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Janet', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'DTT', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Feb 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Fronterra', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'DeAcero', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'CP', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'CFE', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Louise', 'PERSON'), ('ABB', 'PERSON'), ('Dave', 'PERSON'), ('Janet', 'PERSON'), ('DTT', 'PERSON'), ('Feb 2001', 'DATE'), ('Enron', 'ORG'), ('Fronterra', 'ORG'), ('DeAcero', 'ORG'), ('CP', 'ORG'), ('CFE', 'ORG')]"

Thank you for your order.

You sold 120 shares of BRCD (Brocade Communications Sys I Com) at 169.000000.


Time and Date: 14:37:18 on 11/30/00
by e-mailing support@datek.com. Please reference the order tracking number.","[{'word': 'LARRY CAMPBELL', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '11/30/00', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'BRCD', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Brocade Communications Sys I Com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Datek Online', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('LARRY CAMPBELL', 'PERSON'), ('11/30/00', 'DATE'), ('BRCD', 'ORG'), ('Brocade Communications Sys I Com', 'ORG'), ('Datek Online', 'ORG')]"
<31603176.1075855142203.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"DON BAUGHMAN JR,
 
 
Our records indicate that you have not selected reviewers.  Please suggest a list of reviewers as quickly as possible - the feedback process cannot begin until your list of reviewers has been reviewed and approved by your supervisor. 
 
To suggest your reviewers, access PEP at http://pep.enron.com and select 'Suggest Reviewers' from the Main Menu.   
 
If you have any questions regarding the PRC process or the PEP system, please contact the PEP Help Desk at:
Houston:  1.713.853.4777, Option 4 or email: perfmgmt@enron.com
London:  44.207.783.4040, Option 4 or email: pep.enquiries@enron.com","[{'word': 'DON BAUGHMAN JR', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Friday, May 25, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('DON BAUGHMAN JR', 'PERSON'), ('Friday, May 25, 2001', 'DATE'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<23472789.1075840217587.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Ken - I thought I would give you a quick update on our conversations 
regarding Atlantic Copper.  Our team met with the senior management from 
Atlantic Copper last week in concert with the London Metal Exchange Week.

There are several hurdles to overcome in structuring a deal to acquire 
Atlantic Copper and a long term copper concentrates supply from FM's 
Indonesian mine complex.   Current contract prices for copper smelting and 
refining capacity are low and they might be a bit unrealistic on price.    We 
suggested a conceptual structure that may work but is 
probably a long shot at this time.   They were interested and requested a 
more definitive proposal, which we will develop this week.

We will keep you posted.

John","[{'word': 'Ken', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Atlantic Copper', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'FM', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'John', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'last week', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'this week', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'London', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'London Metal Exchange', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Ken', 'PERSON'), ('Atlantic Copper', 'PERSON'), ('FM', 'PERSON'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('this week', 'DATE'), ('London', 'LOCATION'), ('London Metal Exchange', 'ORG')]"
<25203218.1075842194688.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Phyllis:
Here is where I understand we are with the LOC provisions and the LC for.  


1. No changes will be made to the LOC provisions.

2. In the form of LOC, i will delete the language in drawing condition 1 ""the 
entire undrawn amount of the LOC"" and put in ""$.""  I will alos 
delete the automatic renewal language in the third paragraph such that it 
will read ""This LOC shall expire  days from the date of issuance.""

Are we ready to finalize?  If so, I will e-mail to you final forms of the 
docs.


EB 3889
713-646-3393 (Fax)
carol.st.clair@enron.com","[{'word': 'Phyllis', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Carol St. Clair', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Phyllis', 'PERSON'), ('Carol St. Clair', 'PERSON')]"
<26536281.1075861859423.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"James, please find the file attached with the SoCal amounts in dispute as we discussed.  Let me know if you need any further assistance.

Richard,
We are meeting tomorrow afternoon (internally) to discuss a possible SoCal settlement position.  Could you verify the amounts from March, 2001 through September, 2001 by lunch time tomorrow?  (I was using a combination of a spreadsheet Linda Ward had provided to me a couple months ago and inquiring in the CBS invoice system.  I want to make sure I have the most current information.)  If not, let me know your timing.  Also, have we been billing interest on the disputed amounts?  I don't see anything in the invoice system.  Please let me know.

Thanks,
Lindy","[{'word': 'James', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Richard', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Linda Ward', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Lindy', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'March, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'September, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'tomorrow afternoon', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'a couple months ago', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'SoCal', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'CBS', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('James', 'PERSON'), ('Richard', 'PERSON'), ('Linda Ward', 'PERSON'), ('Lindy', 'PERSON'), ('March, 2001', 'DATE'), ('September, 2001', 'DATE'), ('tomorrow afternoon', 'DATE'), ('a couple months ago', 'DATE'), ('SoCal', 'ORG'), ('CBS', 'ORG')]"
<8382380.1075842443798.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Dear General Counsels:

The attachments are Westlaw October allocations and Lexis-Nexis September 
Usage (Actuals) reports.  Please feel free to call me if you have any 
questions.

   

We had an amendment to Westlaw contract to include Public Records and Dow 
Jones/Company News with current $14,000 monthly rate in August.   As of 
today, I am still working with Westlaw to get Aug. and Sept. charges to 
reflect the changes (total about $5,000 credit).  I apologize for not having 
the corrected Westlaw invoices to do Aug. and Sept. allocation reports to 
you.   

October Lexis Nexis Usage report has not coming yet.  August one, according 
to Julie Pechersky was sent to me but got lost in the mail.  I am in the 
process having Lexis to send us another copy.   Again I apologize for the 
long wait even it's not under my control.

Thanks,
Sylvia Hu
Corporate and Law Information Services
x36775","[{'word': 'Sylvia Hu', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Julie Pechersky', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'August', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'today', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Westlaw', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Lexis-Nexis', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Dow Jones/Company News', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sylvia Hu', 'PERSON'), ('Julie Pechersky', 'PERSON'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Westlaw', 'ORG'), ('Lexis-Nexis', 'ORG'), ('Dow Jones/Company News', 'ORG')]"
<19328210.1075840198707.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Mike,

We will be setting up both physical and financial books for everyone.  I know not everyone will have physical but to keep it consistent everyone will have both just in case.  I have the 10 names you sent Jeff earlier, please let me know if that changes.  Do you know what the structure going to look like? ie.  will each trader be assigned specific curves/locations, cash vs. term, how many different people will be setting curves.

We will be starting over with our curve files also.  We want to only start with the true published curves.  We have many derived/internal curves that aren't necessary and if we need to create more curves we will look into it later.  Since the number of curves will be greatly reduced, we will probably start with one file.    

Thanks
Kam","[{'word': 'Mike', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jeff', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Kam', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Mike', 'PERSON'), ('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('Kam', 'PERSON')]"
<32604882.1075840962903.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Pat

For your information, I have attached the current proformas (UBS and the standard).  I know John and Mike have had a lot of conversations on this - essentially where we stand is that the work has been done to complete the commercial reductions (by name) but the non-commercial groups have just been reduced across the board and we intend to start the process today on how to cut the numbers on the non-commercial side.  The theory was that communicating the Netcolite concept was something we would not do until we had a bit more clarity.  Webb knows but that's about it on the non-commercial side.

Hope this helps.

Louise

  

Louise Kitchen
Chief Operating Officer
Enron Americas
Tel:  713 853 3488
Fax: 713 646 2308","[{'word': 'Pat', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'John', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mike', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Louise', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Webb', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'UBS', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Enron Americas', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Pat', 'PERSON'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('Mike', 'PERSON'), ('Louise', 'PERSON'), ('Webb', 'PERSON'), ('UBS', 'ORG'), ('Enron Americas', 'ORG')]"
<19381265.1075855062853.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"This is a friendly reminder for your support for the American Heart Walk on Nov 3.  I thank you all.

Several of you have pledged your support.  Please submit to me your tax deductible contribution by 22 October, Monday so I can turn our team's collection in before the deadline of 30 October, Tuesday.  In order to obtain Enron's matching gift in behalf of your donation, I also would like your GIS number (900...) since the matching gift program now has gone paperless.  My inter-office address is Mail stop ECS 03-455.


Tushar Dhruv
ECS 03524
713-853-5336 (Office)
713-503-6798 (Cell)
713-646-3653 (Fax)","[{'word': 'Tushar Dhruv', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Nov 3', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': '22 October', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': '30 October', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Tushar Dhruv', 'PERSON'), ('Nov 3', 'DATE'), ('22 October', 'DATE'), ('30 October', 'DATE'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<14623691.1075849821003.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Geynille and team,

I'll be at Harvard on the 3rd and the morning of the 4thI'm happy to take 
the short drive to participate in the reception on the evening of the 4th. If 
needed I can participate in interviews on the 5th. 

 Also, Carol/Cindy, I'd like to see if we can follow up on the Jean Baker 
Miller Training Institute research relationship possibilities sometime on the 
5th.

Geynille, I'll take care of my own arrangements and expenses, but would you 
please reserve a room for me (for the evening of the 4th) at the same 
location as the rest of the group will be staying?

Thanks!

Christie.","[{'word': 'Geynille', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Carol', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Cindy', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jean Baker Miller', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Christie', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'on the 3rd', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'the morning of the 4th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'on the evening of the 4th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'on the 5th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Harvard', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Jean Baker Miller Training Institute', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Geynille', 'PERSON'), ('Carol', 'PERSON'), ('Cindy', 'PERSON'), ('Jean Baker Miller', 'PERSON'), ('Christie', 'PERSON'), ('on the 3rd', 'DATE'), ('the morning of the 4th', 'DATE'), ('on the evening of the 4th', 'DATE'), ('on the 5th', 'DATE'), ('Harvard', 'LOCATION'), ('Jean Baker Miller Training Institute', 'ORG')]"
<17603763.1075862292350.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Dear ROD ,

You have received this email because you are a valued customer of Platts - the energy information division of The McGraw Hill Companies.

It's easy to subscribe to GLOBAL ENERGY BUSINESS. Click here to answer a few short questions and be on your way to your FREE subscription to GLOBAL ENERGY BUSINESS!



GLOBAL ENERGY BUSINESS is the magazine of choice for energy executives and senior managers worldwide. In each issue, you will receive comprehensive analysis and perspective on a host of subjects essential to your firm's operation, including:  

Energy Trading 
Information Technologies 
Power Generation 
Energy Delivery * Finance 
Retail Energy Business 
Legal/Regulatory 
Management Strategies 
Corporate/Executive Profiles 

Click on the link below to subscribe to GLOBAL ENERGY BUSINESS. 



If you feel you have received this message in error or would like to be removed from this list, please click on the link below.","[{'word': 'Platts', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'The McGraw Hill Companies', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Platts', 'ORG'), ('The McGraw Hill Companies', 'ORG')]"
<2150224.1075842964264.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Pinnacle 2001 is quickly approaching!  Remember, all EES employees are 
eligible to be nominated, but only those who stand out as
top performers in their field will be selected for participation.  Pinnacle 
2001 will be held at a five-star resort on the island of Nevis in the
West Indies. This years event will be an exciting and great experience for 
those selected. Click on the attachment below to get a feel of
what's to come at Pinnacle 2001.  After launching the file, the Pinnacle 2001 
website can be accessed by clicking on the link at the bottom
of the page.","[{'word': 'Pinnacle 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Nevis', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'West Indies', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'EES', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Pinnacle 2001', 'DATE'), ('Nevis', 'LOCATION'), ('West Indies', 'LOCATION'), ('EES', 'ORG')]"
<15140020.1075844138471.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"It's time to update the McAfee virus files....

Please Note: This update is for Windows95 customers only, if you have 
questions, call the Helpdesk.

But before you run the winstall, please verify that you have version 4.0 or 
greater :

To check the VShield version:

Right click on the Virus shield in the lower right corner 
Select About  
 
The McAfee VShield version should be 4.0 or greater, if not, please contact 
the Helpdesk


To Update the McAfee files:

Click Start 
Select Winstall Auto Update, should take about 20 seconds to run - If you 
don't have the Winstall Auto Update, please contact the Helpdesk 
When the Winstall is completed, you may be prompt to reboot your PC

If you have any questions, or concerns before running the update, call the 
Helpdesk
Thanks - Omaha ETS Helpdesk x7454, 87,7454","[{'word': 'McAfee', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Omaha ETS Helpdesk', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('McAfee', 'ORG'), ('Omaha ETS Helpdesk', 'ORG')]"
<15291859.1075860872470.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I am writing to you as Co-chair of the 2001 Enron Kids program.

A lot of ex-Enron folks who use your website were involved in this year's Gordon Elementary School adoption program.  Many of these people sacrificed some of their own Christmas so that kids at Gordon Elementary would not be let down.  I would like them to know that their efforts were truly appreciated by the students, faculty, and especially those of us on the Committee.  Would you please consider posting on your site the attached thank-you letter from the school? 

thank you
Kevin Hyatt
Co-Chair
Enron Kids Committee 2001","[{'word': 'Kevin Hyatt', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron Kids Committee', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Kevin Hyatt', 'PERSON'), ('2001', 'DATE'), ('Enron Kids Committee', 'ORG')]"
<11387656.1075852221819.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"It is unbelievable how the management (both past and present) think they can run a business with no regard for the customer.  They have to be one of the worst marketing organizations in the world.  They have a great product, but don't have a clue on how to promote it.

Another big news item : PPI used to be the headline sponser.  They left a few years ago and FedEx came on board.  Rumors are rampant that FedEx will be leaving soon.  You have to wonder what it takes to make the light go on for some people.

It is extremely frustrating to try and continue to be a fan.","[{'word': 'PPI', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'FedEx', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('PPI', 'ORG'), ('FedEx', 'ORG')]"
<29225788.1075843329751.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"?
On  Friday, Socalgas?filed a protest to the emergency application we filed 
on  Thursday which asked the CPUC to exercise its authority under Public 
Utility  Code section 2774 and order Socalgas to provide use with emergency 
assistance to  avert core gas supply shortages.? Socalgas asserts (1) section 
2774 does  not apply to gas shortages arising from financial difficulties; 
(2) the  emergency assistance we requested would jeopardize its financial 
viability and  ability to provide gas service to its own core customers; (3) 
the requested  relief would be an unconstitutional taking of its property; 
and (4) PG&E has  not exhausted its own remedies  in particular, the 
protest complains that  PG&E wants Socalgas to act before PG&E diverts 
noncore gas  supplies.? Socalgas states it plans to ask a federal court for 
injunctive  relief to prevent CPUC issuance of the requested order.?  
?

?


 - Protest to PG&E-cover.doc
 - Opposition-PG&E.doc
 - CERTIFICATE OF SERVICE.doc","[{'word': 'Socalgas', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'CPUC', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'PG&E', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'On Friday', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'on Thursday', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Socalgas', 'PERSON'), ('CPUC', 'PERSON'), ('PG&E', 'PERSON'), ('On Friday', 'DATE'), ('on Thursday', 'DATE')]"
<31609129.1075842014780.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"BROADCAST MESSAGE TO ALL PILOTS:

PLEASE REMEMBER TO CONTACT YOUR PATIENT AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THE PAPERWORK, AND AT LEAST 24 HOURS BEFORE THE FLIGHT TO CONFIRM TIME AND PLACE. WE HAVE HAD PATIENTS CALLING IN BECAUSE THEY HAVEN'T HEARD FROM THEIR PILOT YET. ALSO, SOME ARE WORRIED WHEN THEY DON'T HEAR FROM THEIR PILOT AS THE MISSION DATE GETS CLOSE AND THEY ARE FINDING OTHER WAYS TO GET THERE AND ARE CANCELING.

I currently have 13 pending missions. If you can fly please call or email the office as soon as possible. 


1 for SAT		1.  New Orleans to Huntsville, AL (leg 1 of 3 leg mission)

1 for THURS		1.  Houston to Jackson, MS  (LEG 2 of 3 leg mission)


PLEASE CHECK THE WEBSITE FOR OTHERS


thank you
Beth
972 458 0700
afsc@angelflightsc.org
http://www.angelflightsc.org/afpage2a.htm","[{'word': 'Beth', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'New Orleans', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Huntsville, AL', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Houston', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Jackson, MS', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Beth', 'PERSON'), ('New Orleans', 'LOCATION'), ('Huntsville, AL', 'LOCATION'), ('Houston', 'LOCATION'), ('Jackson, MS', 'LOCATION')]"
<6594630.1075862095737.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I am writing to make a correction to yesterday's table.  Joel and I 
were looking over Connecticut's SIP rule because he noticed that 
1990 seemed too early.  Connecticut defines baseline EGUs as 
those that were operating prior to 1990 and those units are 
allocated from the main trading budget.  The change I would like to 
note is that the state also distinguishes between ""new units"" and 
""new EGUs.""  New EGUs are anything operating prior to the 2001 
season and they are allocated separately, but also from the main 
trading budget.  The point is that anything prior to 2001 will receive 
allowances from the main pool, they will just be allocated 
differently.  This won't affect our current tasks as Connecticut does 
not allocate until three months prior to the start of the season.  I 
am attaching a corrected table.  

Thanks, 
Sara","[{'word': 'Joel', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sara', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'yesterday', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'prior to 1990', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'prior to the 2001 season', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'three months prior to the start of the season', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Connecticut', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Joel', 'PERSON'), ('Sara', 'PERSON'), ('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('prior to 1990', 'DATE'), ('prior to the 2001 season', 'DATE'), ('three months prior to the start of the season', 'DATE'), ('Connecticut', 'LOCATION')]"
<5946054.1075846663755.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Here is the final draft of my rebuttal testimony.? I will  be spending the 
rest of the morning cleaning up the few remaining holes for  numbers, etc.? 
Please note I have added extensive rebuttal to the SCGC /  TURN study 
showning that demand charges could increase EG fixed costs by up to  20%.? 
The study, which Edison received in a data response late Wednesday,  is very 
weak.? Please call with any final comments by 1 p.m.  today.
?
Also  this draft has revised language indicating that this  testimony is 
not meant to express the CCC's or Dynegy's opposition to any  element of the 
Interim Settlement.? I would appreciate any feedback on  whether this 
language is consistent with how other signatories to the Interim  Settlement 
are dealing with this issue.
?
Tom Beach","[{'word': 'Tom Beach', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'late Wednesday', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': '1 p.m. today', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'SCGC', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'TURN', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Edison', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'CCC', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Dynegy', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Interim Settlement', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Tom Beach', 'PERSON'), ('late Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('1 p.m. today', 'DATE'), ('SCGC', 'ORG'), ('TURN', 'ORG'), ('Edison', 'ORG'), ('CCC', 'ORG'), ('Dynegy', 'ORG'), ('Interim Settlement', 'ORG')]"
<13711519.1075852431226.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"You are invited to a MEETING OF THE MINDS!  

On Thursday August 30 @ 4:30 please, plan on attending the monthly 24 hour group meeting.

Agenda:
You will have the opportunity to meet 
Introductions of new staff.
Discuss current events.
You will be able to make suggestions for the group.
Be advised of desk happenings.
Open forum for discussion.

There will a happy hour immediately following the meeting, held in or near Downtown.  Sling me some suggestions of where you might want to go.

If you have any questions, give me a call.

See y'all there.

Don
Cell No. 281-787-0029","[{'word': 'Don', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Thursday August 30', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Downtown', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Don', 'PERSON'), ('Thursday August 30', 'DATE'), ('Downtown', 'LOCATION')]"
<11209227.1075844019261.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"What does this all mean for you after July 1, 2000?

New SAP Coding for everyone
 This includes all new General Ledger Accounts, Workorder numbers and Cost 
Centers.  Company numbers have now been expanded to four positions.
 
All departments have been assigned a new SAP Cost Center number 
 A new SAP Company/Cost Center must be used to request Houston Office 
internal services such as:
   Forms & Stationary   
  Overnight Deliveries (Fed Ex, UPS, etc.)
  Audio/Visual Services
  TAP - Travel Agency in the Park
  A/C Lighting after hours
  Catering
  Contract Staff

New forms have been developed
 Invoice and Expense Reports will accommodate the new SAP codes.

Where do you find this new information?

Documentation, forms and cost center codes are on the intranet ""Quick 
Reference"" site at: 
 http://sap.enron.com/quickref

Call your Project Manager for Project codes.","[{'word': 'July 1, 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Houston Office', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('July 1, 2000', 'DATE'), ('Houston Office', 'LOCATION'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<12527926.1075847647235.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Here are two documents per your request, Maureen - I was not sure which one
you wanted:

(See attached file: 5 Part Leadership ModelFall 2000.doc)(See attached
file: Evaluations1.ppt)

++
| This message may contain confidential and/or privileged     |
| information.  If you are not the addressee or authorized to |
| receive this for the addressee, you must not use, copy,     |
| disclose or take any action based on this message or any    |
| information herein.  If you have received this message in   |
| error, please advise the sender immediately by reply e-mail |
| and delete this message.  Thank you for your cooperation.   |
++
 - 5 Part Leadership ModelFall 2000.doc
 - Evaluations1.ppt","[{'word': 'Maureen', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Maureen', 'PERSON')]"
<14488552.1075852808718.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Mr. Lay,

We have not met, but I want to thank you for the letter you sent to all
employees re: Sept. 11.

I am a still-new employee (1+ years) of Portland General Electric (a
wholly owned electric utility subsidiary :-), but I want to tell you
how proud I am of being a member of a team so dedicated to doing its
best at all times  even in the absolute worst of times, as we've
experienced in the last month.

I only hope that if PGE must leave the Enron family, we will be able to
maintain the same high level of respect and integrity we've achieved to
date. I am proud to be an Enron/PGE employee.

Regards,

Jeana McClure
e42625
Web Specialist III
503.464.2843
Portland General Electric
http://www.portlandgeneral.com/



Do You Yahoo!?
Make a great connection at Yahoo! Personals.
http://personals.yahoo.com","[{'word': 'Mr. Lay', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jeana McClure', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sept. 11', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'last month', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Portland General Electric', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Mr. Lay', 'PERSON'), ('Jeana McClure', 'PERSON'), ('Sept. 11', 'DATE'), ('last month', 'DATE'), ('Portland General Electric', 'ORG'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<15745030.1075858571862.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Ernie and Gerald, well dudes, we're doing just what we said we were not
going to do.  Fall out of touch again.  Here is the latest.  I am out on my
ship for six months now.  We left June 4th and we get back in November.
It's a bitch to be gone from the family for that long but it very busy so it
goes fast for me.  We had our fourth (and probably last) kid on May 13th.
Her name is Chloe Elizabeth.  She is perfect.  My two year old (Kate) was
very surprised when we brought her home.  Carson said he wanted a brother
and Kelly wants to hold her all the time.  You can check some pictures out
at www.geocities.com/pbieraugel.  Take it easy you guys and stay in touch.
Paul.","[{'word': 'Ernie', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Gerald', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Chloe Elizabeth', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Kate', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Carson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Kelly', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Paul', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'June 4th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'November', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'May 13th', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Ernie', 'PERSON'), ('Gerald', 'PERSON'), ('Chloe Elizabeth', 'PERSON'), ('Kate', 'PERSON'), ('Carson', 'PERSON'), ('Kelly', 'PERSON'), ('Paul', 'PERSON'), ('June 4th', 'DATE'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('May 13th', 'DATE')]"
<6413207.1075840783702.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Dear Vince,

I was wondering whether in addition to your talk on market and credit risk
at EPRM you would be interested in participating in the panel debate at the
beginning of day two? The panel will be a senior-level debate on the future
of the US power markets and I thought this might be something you would be
interested in speaking on.

I have reattached an up-to-date version of the agenda. Please let me know
what you think.

Best wishes,

Victoria

P.S. The other people invited so far to take part in the panel are Eddie
Meche, Reliant and Bill Schivley, Select Energy.



Victoria Kerridge
Manager, Risk & EPRM Conferences
Risk Waters Group
T: +44 (0)20 7484 9875
F: +44 (0)20 7484 9800
E: vkerridge@riskwaters.com
http://www.riskwaters.com

Risk Waters Group
Haymarket House
28-29 Haymarket
London
SW1Y 4RX

 - EPRM 2002 draft.doc","[{'word': 'Vince', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Eddie Meche', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Bill Schivley', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Victoria Kerridge', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'EPRM', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'US', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Reliant', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Select Energy', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Risk Waters Group', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Vince', 'PERSON'), ('Eddie Meche', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Schivley', 'PERSON'), ('Victoria Kerridge', 'PERSON'), ('EPRM', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('Reliant', 'ORG'), ('Select Energy', 'ORG'), ('Risk Waters Group', 'ORG')]"
<17555119.1075852287516.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Oh no.  In the meanwhile,

Ella learned to tie her shoes. Unbelievalbe , but she just did it, just like that.  I talked to her about having Ms Jane help her learn and she put me to shame.

Sam misses you.

I want to book the Broadmoor - it looks great, 3 days tennis, 1/2 day Friday, Sat and Sun, August 10, 11, 12.  Dede is booked, and I have a call in for you and me.  You'll come, right?

I miss you.

I signed up for a little mixed doubles on Friday night, 630 -830.  Do you want me to sign you up?

Everybody is fine.","[{'word': 'Ella', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Ms Jane', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sam', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dede', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Friday, Sat and Sun, August 10, 11, 12', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Friday night', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Broadmoor', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Ella', 'PERSON'), ('Ms Jane', 'PERSON'), ('Sam', 'PERSON'), ('Dede', 'PERSON'), ('Friday, Sat and Sun, August 10, 11, 12', 'DATE'), ('Friday night', 'DATE'), ('Broadmoor', 'LOCATION')]"
<26490427.1075840182114.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"This is how the logic is now within UBSWenergy.com:

All counterparties with Master Agreements with ECC that hit a US product must be booked as two legs:  leg one booked between ECC and the counterparty with risk assignment of FT-US/CAND-ERMS; leg two flipping the position out of FT-US/CAND-ERMS to the appropriate risk book (the book on the online product).  This applies only to finanical swaps and not physical deals.

Please let me know if there is going to be a change and if so what the deals should look like in Tagg.  The programmers need time to modify logic and I need time to test!

Thanks for your help.
Dawn
3-9353","[{'word': 'ECC', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dawn', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'UBSWenergy.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('ECC', 'PERSON'), ('Dawn', 'PERSON'), ('UBSWenergy.com', 'ORG')]"
<14211927.1075842770407.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I have been working with Gerald Nemec on precedent agreements to gas 
transportation agreements with Transcontinental Gas Pipeline.  The 
transportation agreements provide pipeline capacity in support of two 
electric generation plant projects that Enron is developing in Georgia.  The 
project companies are the Hartwell Land Development Company, L.L.C. and the 
Athens Development Company, L.L.C.  Transco has requested a corporate 
guaranty from Enron to cover the obligations of Hartwell and Athens.  At 
first, Transco provided their form of guaranty, but we rejected it.  Later, 
we provided our preferred form of guaranty.  Transco reviewed this guaranty 
and provided their proposed revisions.  I believe that Gerald Nemec forwarded 
these comments to you.  Could you please give Gerald or myself an update on 
your review of Transco's comments.","[{'word': 'Gerald Nemec', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Georgia', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Transcontinental Gas Pipeline', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Hartwell Land Development Company', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Athens Development Company', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Gerald Nemec', 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', 'LOCATION'), ('Transcontinental Gas Pipeline', 'ORG'), ('Enron', 'ORG'), ('Hartwell Land Development Company', 'ORG'), ('Athens Development Company', 'ORG')]"
<24240242.1075860883210.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"John
I am surprised that you interpret this is a new request.
From day 1, ETS has been responsible for preparing a Level B estimate for the Sun Devil project.
What I would like your group to do is come up with a cost estimate for all work related to the environmentsl aspect of the project from today through to completion of the project. i.e a Jan, 2004 in service date
Timewise, I would lime a first pass estimate by Sept 21, a second pass estimate by Sept 26, and the final complete estimate by Sept 28
Please call me if unclear and so that we can discuss.
Thanks","[{'word': 'John', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jan, 2004', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Sept 21', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Sept 26', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Sept 28', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'ETS', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('John', 'PERSON'), ('Jan, 2004', 'DATE'), ('Sept 21', 'DATE'), ('Sept 26', 'DATE'), ('Sept 28', 'DATE'), ('ETS', 'ORG')]"
<26558773.1075859934451.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Dave:

Below please find the language that Mark & I propose for the EnronOnline 
Markets page as well as each commodity ""home"" page for the web site.  Please 
let us know if it looks like each such page is going to be limited in length 
so that it is not necessary to scroll down to see the entire page.

Your company should not enter into any transaction unless it fully 
understands the potential risks and rewards of that transaction and has 
independently determined that the transaction is appropriate in light of your 
company's objectives, experience, financial and operational resources, and 
other relevant circumstances.  Please bear in mind that in providing this web 
site, Enron is acting as a potential arm's length counterparty and not as 
your company's adviser.  For further information, please see Legal and 
Privacy Information [link]

Let us know if this disclaimer language will work.

Leslie","[{'word': 'Dave', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mark', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Leslie', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Dave', 'PERSON'), ('Mark', 'PERSON'), ('Leslie', 'PERSON'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<12895763.1075844726129.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hi Sara, 

I need to reschedule on of the three brokerage account meetings that are on 
my calendar for tomorrow.  

My calendar indicates that I have a 9 a.m. one hour meeting with you, a 10 
a.m. one hour swaps meeting, a 1:30 brokerage account meeting a 2:30 one hour 
credit support meeting and a 4 p.m. meeting with someone from yet another 
Enron entity seeking to open a brokerage account on an urgent basis.

Keegan and I have now developed a strategy to ensure that we do not have so 
many meetings on one day.  Most of the other meetings are group meetings and 
therefore are not possible to reschedule.  

Cheryl Nelson
Senior Counsel
EB3816
(713) 345-4693","[{'word': 'Sara', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Keegan', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Cheryl Nelson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sara', 'PERSON'), ('Keegan', 'PERSON'), ('Cheryl Nelson', 'PERSON'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<23047167.1075847038198.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Type of Contract:  ISDA Master Agreement (Multicurrency-Cross Border)

Effective Date:   September 1, 2000

Enron Entity:   Enron North America Corp.

Counterparty:   H.Q. Energy Services (U.S.) Inc.

Transactions Covered:  Approved for all products with the exception of: 
Foreign Exchange
          
Confirming Entity:  Enron North America Corp.

Governing Law:   New York

Special Provisions:  The Confirmation section prescribes using the form of 
confirmation contained in the 2000 ISDA Definitions or the 1993 ISDA      
Commodity Definitions.  The timing for dispute of confirmations has been 
amended from the standard 2 days to 3 days.

    Confirmation Desk:  note p.28 of the Schedule to the Master Agreement 
prescribes the rounding conventions.","[{'word': 'September 1, 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron North America Corp.', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'H.Q. Energy Services (U.S.) Inc.', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('September 1, 2000', 'DATE'), ('Enron North America Corp.', 'ORG'), ('H.Q. Energy Services (U.S.) Inc.', 'ORG')]"
<16385657.1075859893916.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"On Friday we will be receiving the remaining customer list from credit, due 
to the timescales I am asking for turnaround on the customer matrix and 
master agreement review by the end of play Tuesday 12th October.

Any problems with this please notify me immediately as we are now running up 
against very tight deadlines in terms of getting all of the information in 
the system for the launch schedule.

Thanks

Louise

Mark,
On another note we are requesting a review of the blanket decision which has 
been made to prevent any regulated utility from completing any financial 
transactions, if we are not prepared to do the due diligence on which ones 
can transact and which ones can not - is this our responsibility or theirs?  
ie their decision whether to trade or not.
Louise","[{'word': 'Louise', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mark', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Friday', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Tuesday 12th October', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Louise', 'PERSON'), ('Mark', 'PERSON'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Tuesday 12th October', 'DATE')]"
<28500259.1075842941960.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"SB 1741; Telecommunications:  technology specific area codes, Author: Bowen 
Introduced 2/23/00
Sponsor: Author Sponsor
Summary:
Currently, in California,  area codes cannot be approved based on specific 
technology.
This bill would require the Public Utilities Commission to request authority 
to establish technology specific area codes based on wireless and data 
communications.  This bill would also prohibit the Public Utilities 
Commission from approving new area code splits or overlays unless a 
technology specific area code had been established in the affected area and 
further area code relief is warranted.

Position: 
What is our position on this issue? Should we watch this bill?
Attached is the bill.","[{'word': 'Bowen', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '2/23/00', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'California', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Public Utilities Commission', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Federal Communications Commission', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('2/23/00', 'DATE'), ('California', 'LOCATION'), ('Public Utilities Commission', 'ORG'), ('Federal Communications Commission', 'ORG')]"
<9104007.1075844348812.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"""Each party consents to the recording, at any time and from time to time, by 
the other party of any and all communications between officers or employees 
of the parties, and waives any further notice of such recording.  
Additionally, in the absence of a Confirmation executed by both parties, any 
such recording may be submitted in evidence to any court or in any 
proceedings for the purpose of establishing any matters pertinent to the 
terms of a Transaction.""


Marty:  This would appear in Part 5(f) of the Schedule.  Let me know if this 
is acceptable.  I'll follow up with Tanya on Monday.","[{'word': 'Marty', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Tanya', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Marty', 'PERSON'), ('Tanya', 'PERSON')]"
<31441372.1075861471989.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Per the attached document, Angela Lewis, a representative from The Japan
Partnership,
an international executive search firm, will be in the area at 5pm on
Sunday, October 7th and
is interested in meeting with native Japanese graduating Haas students to
discuss career opportunities in Japan.

If you are interested in attending this presentation, please respond back to
me
right away.  The volume of responses will determine whether the event will
take
place or not. It is scheduled to take place in the Faculty Club.

Regards,
Rich

Rich Wong
Account Manager, Technology & Entertainment
MBA Recruiting
Haas School of Business Career Center
545 Student Services Building #1900
Berkeley, CA 94720-1900
ph:  510-643-4211
fax:  510-643-5257
email:rwong@haas.berkeley.edu","[{'word': 'Angela Lewis', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Rich Wong', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sunday, October 7th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Berkeley, CA', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'The Japan Partnership', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Haas School of Business Career Center', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Angela Lewis', 'PERSON'), ('Rich Wong', 'PERSON'), ('Sunday, October 7th', 'DATE'), ('Berkeley, CA', 'LOCATION'), ('The Japan Partnership', 'ORG'), ('Haas School of Business Career Center', 'ORG')]"
<2719733.1075856644362.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Message sent from the pjm-customer-info mailing list at 
pjm-customer-info@majordomo.pjm.com:

In response to customer feedback and in order to make our website more user
friendly, PJM will add buttons for the more widely used eTools to the PJM home
page. The button will be located just under the weather maps and will 
eliminate
the user's need to scroll or make multiple clicks to reach the  suite of PJM
eTools.  The entire suite will continue to be accessible via the ""Business
eTools"" link on the navigational bar. The new buttons should be available on
Thursday 12/14/00 at approximately 3:00PM.





Please DO NOT REPLY to this message. If you have a question for PJM Customer
Relations and Training, please complete and submit this form:
http://www.pjm.com/contact/questions.html

To unsubscribe from this list, send an e-mail to majordomo@majordomo.pjm.com
containing only the following line in the body of the e-mail:

unsubscribe pjm-customer-info","[{'word': 'Thursday 12/14/00 at approximately 3:00PM', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'PJM', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Thursday 12/14/00 at approximately 3:00PM', 'DATE'), ('PJM', 'ORG')]"

Thank you for your order.

You bought 70 shares of CIEN (Ciena Corp Com) at 113.430000.


Time and Date: 10:33:01 on 11/03/00
by e-mailing support@datek.com. Please reference the order tracking number.","[{'word': 'LARRY CAMPBELL', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '11/03/00', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'CIEN', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Ciena Corp Com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Datek Online', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('LARRY CAMPBELL', 'PERSON'), ('11/03/00', 'DATE'), ('CIEN', 'ORG'), ('Ciena Corp Com', 'ORG'), ('Datek Online', 'ORG')]"
<29791654.1075839935086.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Jerald Surface will be in Portland (from Houston) to interview for a position in Real Time. I will provide a copy of his resume to his interviews for review. See below for interview schedule and location:

Jerald Surface, Cascade Conference Room, Thursday, July 5th, 2001

11:30am - Chris Mallory
12:15pm - Greg Wolfe
1:00pm - Stewart Rosman
1:45pm - Amy FitzPatrick

Jerald Surface, Mt. Rainier Conference Room, Friday, July 6th, 2001

9:15am - Bill Williams III
10:00am - Ryan Slinger


Thanks,
Grace
x8321","[{'word': 'Jerald Surface', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Chris Mallory', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Greg Wolfe', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Stewart Rosman', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Amy FitzPatrick', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Bill Williams III', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Ryan Slinger', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Grace', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Thursday, July 5th, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Friday, July 6th, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Portland', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Houston', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Cascade Conference Room', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Mt. Rainier Conference Room', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Jerald Surface', 'PERSON'), ('Chris Mallory', 'PERSON'), ('Greg Wolfe', 'PERSON'), ('Stewart Rosman', 'PERSON'), ('Amy FitzPatrick', 'PERSON'), ('Bill Williams III', 'PERSON'), ('Ryan Slinger', 'PERSON'), ('Grace', 'PERSON'), ('Thursday, July 5th, 2001', 'DATE'), ('Friday, July 6th, 2001', 'DATE'), ('Portland', 'LOCATION'), ('Houston', 'LOCATION'), ('Cascade Conference Room', 'LOCATION'), ('Mt. Rainier Conference Room', 'LOCATION')]"
<3810539.1075861037948.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Sara- I am sorry to hear Frank has left.. have you spoken to him, is he OK? How are you doing?

Can you please tell me how you are dealing with counterparties who still have exposure to Enron?

I know all contracts are null and void.. what is the process for them to take off deals.

The only counterparties I have with any exposure are:
tudor
wexford

I am asking for them specifically.

Also, on monies we owe counterparties.. like tudor and catequil, what is the process they must go through?

Thanks very much,
Caroline

cell- 917 324 1999
home- 212 737 2082","[{'word': 'Sara', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Frank', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Caroline', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'tudor', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'wexford', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'catequil', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sara', 'PERSON'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('Caroline', 'PERSON'), ('Enron', 'ORG'), ('tudor', 'ORG'), ('wexford', 'ORG'), ('catequil', 'ORG')]"
<10183854.1075852516627.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Per our discussions yesterday, the following should hopefully be completed before the 2:30 (CST) conference call on Recoupment and the 4:00 (CST) conference call on PX Credit & 1c/kwh Surcharge.

1.	Bob Williams - Synopsis of 1c/kwh Surcharge
2.	Sue Mara - Background on CPUC Activity on 1c/kwh Surcharge (to be included in Bob Williams' write-up)
3.	Dian Huddleson - Plan for Requesting Net Bill Reinstatement
4.	URM - Analysis of PX Credit Methodology
5.	Mary Lynne Ruffer - Analysis of Net Bill Amounts
6.	Jim Steffes - CPUC Legal Analysis

The goal for today is to have all necessary data to develop our recommendations for how to proceed in these matters so that we can meet with the business heads tomorrow.

Call In Information -

2:30 Recoupment
1-800-998-2462 # 5462908

4:00 PX Credit & 1c/kwh Surcharge
To Be Provided By Linda Noske","[{'word': 'Bob Williams', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sue Mara', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dian Huddleson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'URM', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mary Lynne Ruffer', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jim Steffes', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Linda Noske', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'CPUC', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Bob Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Sue Mara', 'PERSON'), ('Dian Huddleson', 'PERSON'), ('URM', 'PERSON'), ('Mary Lynne Ruffer', 'PERSON'), ('Jim Steffes', 'PERSON'), ('Linda Noske', 'PERSON'), ('CPUC', 'ORG')]"
<16291641.1075854491287.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Kay please forward to Max Yzaguirre.

Max, congrats on the Decero PPA - we need to wrestle up another 100 to 200 
MW.  This should be a priority given the profit potential of this deal as per 
Oz and Doug (+50M in 2000).  Is there an ability to let Sabine or Irvin run 
with Vitro and get your attention on this item asap.  I know that the 
Monterrey project is eating into your time.  Do we need to augment your 
resources?

On a different note, the current Monterrey control budget is showing a $5.3M 
negative variance from the original control budget.  Is this accurate?  Does 
this reduce the profitability or is it absorbed by the PPA's?

Regards
Delainey","[{'word': 'Kay', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Max Yzaguirre', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Oz', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Doug', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sabine', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Irvin', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Delainey', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'in 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Monterrey', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Decero', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Vitro', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Kay', 'PERSON'), ('Max Yzaguirre', 'PERSON'), ('Oz', 'PERSON'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ('Sabine', 'PERSON'), ('Irvin', 'PERSON'), ('Delainey', 'PERSON'), ('in 2000', 'DATE'), ('Monterrey', 'LOCATION'), ('Decero', 'ORG'), ('Vitro', 'ORG')]"
<20551004.1075843021810.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"FYI.?? SoCalGas' response to protests to  AL2966.
Received: from dymwsm06.mailwatch.com by ArterHadden.com; Tue, 07 Nov 2000 
10:54:19 -0500
Received: from dymw0125.mailwatch.com (dymw0125.allegro.net [204.253.83.81]) 
by dymwsm06.mailwatch.com (8.11.0/8.11.0) with SMTP id eA7FsbW02410 for 
; Tue, 7 Nov 2000 10:54:37 -0500
Received: from 204.253.83.72 by dymw0125.mailwatch.com with SMTP ( 
WorldSecure Server SMTP Relay(WSS) v4.3); Tue, 07 Nov 00 10:51:53 -0500
X-Server-Uuid: 8014d96c-8cb5-11d4-814d-00508bd934cf
Received: from mail1.sempra.com (mail1.sempra.com [4.21.3.129]) by 
dymwsm10.mailwatch.com (8.11.0/8.11.0) with ESMTP id eA7Fpph12200 for 
; Tue, 7 Nov 2000 10:51:51 -0500
Received: from mail1.sempra.com (localhost [127.0.0.1]) by mail1.sempra.com 
with SMTP (Microsoft Exchange Internet Mail Service Version 5.5.2650.21) id 
WGWCN70F; Tue, 7 Nov 2000 07:50:43 -0800
Received: from 4.21.3.3 by mail1.sempra.com (InterScan E-Mail VirusWall NT); 
Tue, 07 Nov 2000 07:50:34 -0800 (Pacific Standard Time)
Received: by ex-socal-c01.pacent.com with Internet Mail Service ( 
5.5.2650.21) id ; Tue, 7 Nov 2000 07:50:47 -0800
Message-ID:","[{'word': 'Tue, 07 Nov 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'SoCalGas', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'AL2966', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ArterHadden.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'dymw0125.mailwatch.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'dymwsm06.mailwatch.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'dymwsm10.mailwatch.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'mail1.sempra.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'InterScan E-Mail VirusWall NT', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ex-socal-c01.pacent.com', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Tue, 07 Nov 2000', 'DATE'), ('SoCalGas', 'ORG'), ('AL2966', 'ORG'), ('ArterHadden.com', 'ORG'), ('dymw0125.mailwatch.com', 'ORG'), ('dymwsm06.mailwatch.com', 'ORG'), ('dymwsm10.mailwatch.com', 'ORG'), ('mail1.sempra.com', 'ORG'), ('InterScan E-Mail VirusWall NT', 'ORG'), ('ex-socal-c01.pacent.com', 'ORG')]"
<16526501.1075841492599.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"To member:   dvdexpress
From member: shig4413




There's a dutch auction going on for these items. Find by using Enron Cube. Auction is at $23 right now.


This email was sent by an eBay member via eBay's email forwarding system.
If you reply to the email, your response will go directly to the member and
not through eBay.

eBay does not tolerate spam (i.e., unsolicited commercial email) and is
taking steps to protect members from this abuse. In addition, solicitations
to buy or sell items outside of eBay violate eBay rules and are not covered
by services that protect members such as feedback, insurance, escrow, and
dispute resolution. If this is an offer to buy/sell items outside of eBay,
please do not participate. Enter the following link into your browser to learn more.  Link: http://pages.digitalcity.ebay.com/help/emailinfo.html","[{'word': 'dvdexpress', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'shig4413', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'eBay', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('dvdexpress', 'PERSON'), ('shig4413', 'PERSON'), ('eBay', 'ORG')]"
<19505705.1075851888987.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Bill-
Two files are attached. The first file is the text and figures of a plan for 
characterizing impacted soil in the former surface impoundment areas. The 
second file contains the attachments to the characterization plan. The 
attachments include copies of soil boring logs and a summary of some previous 
soil sample results. I will also send two hard copies of the plan to you via 
FedEx. Transwestern is ready to proceed upon approval from the NMOCD and the 
Thanks,
George





George C. Robinson, PE
Contract Environmental Engineer
Cypress Engineering
ENRON Office: (713) 646-7327
ENRON email: george.robinson@enron.com","[{'word': 'Bill', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'George C. Robinson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Cypress Engineering', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ENRON', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Bill', 'PERSON'), ('George C. Robinson', 'PERSON'), ('Cypress Engineering', 'ORG'), ('ENRON', 'ORG')]"
<9821416.1075861920380.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hi, Dana:

We have received the original copy of the ISDA Master Agreement.  In looking through the supporting documents, we noted two outstanding items:

1.	We did not receive an original signed IRS Tax Form W-9 as required pursuant to Part 3(a); and

2.	The Certificate of Incumbency we received was not an original and was dated November 14, 2000.  We would like to receive an original certificate dated a current date.


Marie

Marie Heard
Senior Legal Specialist
Enron North America Corp.
Phone:  (713) 853-3907
Fax:  (713) 646-3490
marie.heard@enron.com","[{'word': 'Dana', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Frank', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Marie Heard', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'November 14, 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron North America Corp.', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Dana', 'PERSON'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('Marie Heard', 'PERSON'), ('November 14, 2000', 'DATE'), ('Enron North America Corp.', 'ORG')]"
<503355.1075841997625.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Richter reserved that last year.  He made the money.  It's his.  It goes against refund risk in California.  If we take a hit in CA due to refunds, Richter should eat a good chunk of that hit  if there is extra money then he should keep it.

John has asked me to do a thorough review of our Schedule C reserves in light of the northwest refund decision, BPA's new contracts that started in October, and the overall lower price environment.  Richter's reserves will be a part of this bigger effort that I will get done this week.

Let me know if you have any questions.","[{'word': 'Richter', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'John', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'BPA', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Richter', 'PERSON'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('BPA', 'ORG')]"
<3124288.1075842758547.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"My dear compadres,

We are a month away from our trip to the beautiful Lake Tahoe.  Here is the
link to the house we have reserved.
As a repeat offender, we get a price break and it is going to be $198.00
for the house from March 8th to the 13th for ten people.

http://www.tahoevacationguide.com/LTRB/Homes/2240E.html

So, I currently have

Michael W.
Mark M.
Virginia H. and Friend.
Patricia
David?
Gerald?

Let me know!!!

Have a great weekend

Thanks,
Patricia Cuero
Bus Ops, Program Manager
(512) 723-6977
(800)  289-3355 ext. 36977
(512) 728-3653 fax


""The only limits on what you can accomplish are the limits you place on your
own imagination.""","[{'word': 'Michael W.', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Mark M.', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Virginia H.', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Patricia', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'David', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Gerald', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Patricia Cuero', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'from March 8th to the 13th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Lake Tahoe', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Michael W.', 'PERSON'), ('Mark M.', 'PERSON'), ('Virginia H.', 'PERSON'), ('Patricia', 'PERSON'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Gerald', 'PERSON'), ('Patricia Cuero', 'PERSON'), ('from March 8th to the 13th', 'DATE'), ('Lake Tahoe', 'LOCATION')]"
<20065557.1075844212840.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hello All-

I wanted to let you know that, as of July 1, Jan Haizmann's responsibilities 
will expand to include competition issues in European energy markets.  As you 
know, in addition to his work for EBS in Europe, Jan has been spending 
considerable time directing EBS' government affairs work in Asia.   Due in 
large part to the progress he has made, we are now able to shift that effort 
to an individual in the region until a new hire is on board in Singapore.  

Jan will continue to spend approximately half of his time on EBS government 
affairs issues in Europe.  The remainder of his time, which previously was 
spent on Asia, now will be spent on European energy markets.  

Please feel free to call me if you have any questions.

Regards,

Sue





Sue Nord, Sr. Director
Government Affairs
713 345-4196","[{'word': 'Jan Haizmann', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jan', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sue Nord', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'July 1', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Europe', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Asia', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Singapore', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'EBS', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Jan Haizmann', 'PERSON'), ('Jan', 'PERSON'), ('Sue Nord', 'PERSON'), ('July 1', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Asia', 'LOCATION'), ('Singapore', 'LOCATION'), ('EBS', 'ORG')]"
<28928061.1075844690659.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Melissa:

Before I can respond, I need to know the following answers:

(1)  What is the Exercise Period (Commencement/Expiration Dates) for the 
swaption and during what hours can we exercise?  Is it from Jan. 2 - Feb 28, 
2001 from 9 am to 11 am New York time?

(2)  Is the Commencement Date also the Premium Payment Date?

(3)  For early termination purposes, is there just a single Optional Early 
Termination Date or is it a period of time and during what hours?

(4)  Did we want to specify any Cash Settlement Reference Banks?

I can mark this confirm quickly when I hear from you.  Thanks.

Sara Shackleton
1400 Smith Street, EB 3801a
Houston, Texas  77002
713-853-5620 (phone)
713-646-3490 (fax)
sara.shackleton@enron.com



<19281080.1075841524665.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"All

We had 2 service outages today, the External Internet and Email both became unavailable at about 11:00 am today, service was restored in after about 15-20 minutes.  The fact that both services went down at the same time is only coincidence.

Below are the basic causes for the outages:

The Internet outage was caused by an error in one of our Network Routers.  The device was rebooted and service was restored.

The Email outage was caused by a bug in Exchange that is remedied by rebooting the server.

Sorry for the inconvenience these outages may have caused.


Dave Steiner","[{'word': 'Dave Steiner', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Dave Steiner', 'PERSON')]"
<31635217.1075842304108.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hi Sylvia,

Re the GISB for Wisconsin,  no we would not agree to the terms of their GISB 
on the front page or their special provisions.   Are you aware we currently 
have a GISB in place with Wisconsin Public Service Company and ENA as well as 
with Wisconsin Gas Company??????

Re Master Status:  I have devoted  my afternoon to this contract  in order to 
complete the redline.  Will keep you apprised.

Do you still want a copy of our GISB.  If so, I will send you a draft 
however,  I need to fill in the name  of the counterparty etc. before it goes 
out.

Enron North America Corp.
Legal Department
Houston, Texas 77002
dperlin@enron.com
Phone 713-853-7658
Fax  713-646-3490","[{'word': 'Sylvia', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Debra Perlingiere', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Wisconsin', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Wisconsin Public Service Company', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'ENA', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Wisconsin Gas Company', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Houston, Texas', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Enron North America Corp.', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sylvia', 'PERSON'), ('Debra Perlingiere', 'PERSON'), ('Wisconsin', 'LOCATION'), ('Wisconsin Public Service Company', 'LOCATION'), ('ENA', 'LOCATION'), ('Wisconsin Gas Company', 'LOCATION'), ('Houston, Texas', 'LOCATION'), ('Enron North America Corp.', 'ORG')]"
<16989816.1075852480562.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"State Treasurer Barbara Hafer reveals that about $300,000 was fraudulently removed from the state's treasury, in what she is terming 'economic terrorism,' on Pennsylvania Newsmakers. 10 ? minutes
 
The interview can be heard by clicking on one of the links below.
 
http://www.jerrybowyer.com/audio.php?id0 for RealPlayer
http://www.jerrybowyer.com/audio.php?id1 for Windows Media Player
 
Feel free to share this information with anyone on your list, or anyone who may be interested.
 
To listen to other Jerry Bowyer interviews from The Jerry Bowyer Program, Pennsylvania Newsmakers or Focus on the Issues visit www.jerrybowyer.com/audio.php. 
 
Thanks for listening.
 
 
 
Jerry Bowyer
Pennsylvania Newsmakersseen across the state on these television stations: www.jerrybowyer.com/coveragemap.php     
The Jerry Bowyer Programon WPTT radio in Pittsburgh, 1360am: www.1360wptt.com/bowyer 
Focus on the Issueson Cornerstone Television
Audio clips from these programs can be heard at www.jerrybowyer.com/audio.php  
412.771.2282 phone
412.771.2363 faxjerrybowyer@home.com","[{'word': 'Barbara Hafer', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Jerry Bowyer', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Pennsylvania', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Pennsylvania Newsmakers', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'The Jerry Bowyer Program', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Focus on the Issues', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Cornerstone Television', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Barbara Hafer', 'PERSON'), ('Jerry Bowyer', 'PERSON'), ('Pennsylvania', 'LOCATION'), ('Pennsylvania Newsmakers', 'ORG'), ('The Jerry Bowyer Program', 'ORG'), ('Focus on the Issues', 'ORG'), ('Cornerstone Television', 'ORG')]"
<32823688.1075859051565.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Below is the file containing Flex Dollar amounts and the Benefit Rates to be used in preparing your Business Unit's 2002 Plan.  I have also included the flat rates for the Analyst and Associate Program. 

Beginning in June 2001, the Analyst and Associate Program began billing the flat fees to GL account - 52503000 Allocations Other.  A new GL account - 52502600  Analyst & Associate Allocations will be set up and should be used to plan for next year.  PLEASE NOTE:  If you have any reports, cost element groups or spreadsheets that use a listing of GL accounts, you will need to update them to include the new account.


 


Associate		$10,400
3rd Yr. Analyst		  $7,400
Analyst			  $6,400
Tax Analyst		  $2,400
Summer Analyst	  $3,300
Summer Associates	  $6,000

Please fee free to call me if you have any questions.

Dawn Derr
37775","[{'word': 'Dawn Derr', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'June 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Dawn Derr', 'PERSON'), ('June 2001', 'DATE')]"





 - OUTAGE.dbf 
<31324401.1075855096165.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Leon, the account number in the original document is actually not incorrect. This was the account to which the funds were to have been deposited to. However, SCE deposited the funds to a different account.  As a result, I agree that we should amend the document to reflect that the account where these funds where they actually ere actually sent and this will conclude our busines. 

Your file did not come over correctly but if you could hand correct the original documents by changing the banking instructions and fax to me, i will provide proper signatures on amendment and we are done.

Thanks. Barry Tycholiz
713-646-2391 (Fax )
713-853-1587 (Phone)","[{'word': 'Leon', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Barry Tycholiz', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'SCE', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Leon', 'PERSON'), ('Barry Tycholiz', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG')]"
<10342105.1075844143015.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Effective 2/2/01, please change my receipt MDQ's for contract 25841 as
follows:


Meter#   OLD  NEW
GPM Artesia 10703              22800  22800
West Pool 58646               546    5296
Central Pool 58649              8830    4080
NGPL Winkler 52862              7824    7824

TOTAL MDQ:           40000  40000


Thanks,
Jody Oberman
(301) 280-6184


PG&E National Energy Group and any other
company referenced herein that uses the PG&E name or
Electric Company, the regulated California utility.  Neither
PG&E National Energy Group nor these other
referenced companies are regulated by the California Public
Utilities Commission.  Customers of Pacific Gas and Electric Company
do not have to buy products from these companies in order
to continue to receive quality regulated services from the utility.","[{'word': 'Jody Oberman', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '2/2/01', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'PG&E National Energy Group', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Pacific Gas and Electric Company', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'California Public Utilities Commission', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Jody Oberman', 'PERSON'), ('2/2/01', 'DATE'), ('PG&E National Energy Group', 'ORG'), ('Pacific Gas and Electric Company', 'ORG'), ('California Public Utilities Commission', 'ORG')]"
<25975600.1075853162862.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"paperloop.com
BRUSSELS, July 18, 2001 (paperloop.com) - Frantschach Pulp and Paper has ordered an automatic chip storage and reclaiming system for its two pulp lines at the Steti plant in the Czech Republic. The revamp will be implemented in two stages to avoid a shutdown. The first phase of the upgrade will be completed in February 2002 and the final work will be wrapped up in July 2002. 
 A spokesman said the Steti mill produces 250,000 tonnes/yr of bleached and unbleached kraft pulp. The new system will enhance safety and product quality. 
Steti's paper mill produces 200,000 tonnes/yr of sack paper, machine-glazed (MG) wrapping paper and linerboard. A revamp of the plant's PM is also planned for next year. The unit's 12,000 tonnes/yr capacity of MG paper is set to gradually rise to 31,000 tonnes/yr following the upgrade.","[{'word': 'July 18, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'February 2002', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'July 2002', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'next year', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'BRUSSELS', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Steti', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Czech Republic', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Frantschach Pulp and Paper', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('July 18, 2001', 'DATE'), ('February 2002', 'DATE'), ('July 2002', 'DATE'), ('next year', 'DATE'), ('BRUSSELS', 'LOCATION'), ('Steti', 'LOCATION'), ('Czech Republic', 'LOCATION'), ('Frantschach Pulp and Paper', 'ORG')]"
<8735265.1075840437474.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Daren I have three meters that have flow in Feb but no deal.

1.  Meter 0416  flowed the whole month  1-28.  This our ols friends at Pawnee gas plant fuel.  Last deal used was 289396 could you extend it.
2. meter 1601 had flow on the 15 &18.  This is Southern union Lockhart.  Last deal used with them was 285350 Hpl or 259208 ENA. 
3. Meter 1598 had flow the whole month 1-28.  This is MT Enterprise C/G- Panther.  The last deal used  is 284 620

I'll get Accounting Arrangements for these when you let me know the deal status and get them cleared up. Thanks.","[{'word': 'Daren', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Feb', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': '1-28', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Pawnee gas plant fuel', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Southern union Lockhart', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'MT Enterprise C/G- Panther', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Daren', 'PERSON'), ('Feb', 'DATE'), ('1-28', 'DATE'), ('Pawnee gas plant fuel', 'ORG'), ('Southern union Lockhart', 'ORG'), ('MT Enterprise C/G- Panther', 'ORG')]"
<12519111.1075845529242.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"The party is fast approaching and the number of prizes I have received from
deputies is 16.  We would like to have 100.  Some of you have indicated that
you have collected prizes so even if you can't send me the prizes this week
please e-mail or phone me with the following information:

  your name   prize description
approximate value  name of donor


THIS INFORMATION MUST BE RECEIVED BY THIS FRIDAY TO BE PUBLISHED IN THE
BROCHURE.

Please e-mail your responses to me at maggietimmins@cdnoxy.com or call me
at 260-3441.

I look forward to hearing about your fabulous prizes!

Thanks very much.

Maggie Timmins
CXY Energy Marketing
Phone: (403) 260-3441
Fax:    (403) 237-8266
maggietimmins@cdnoxy.com


 - att1.htm","[{'word': 'Maggie Timmins', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'THIS FRIDAY', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'CXY Energy Marketing', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Maggie Timmins', 'PERSON'), ('THIS FRIDAY', 'DATE'), ('CXY Energy Marketing', 'ORG')]"
<33217125.1075845200232.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hey all,

Sunday is Shanna's 30th B-day so we are going to celebrate Saturday night.  We were planning on meeting up at my new place for drinks @ around 9:00 and then heading over to the Black Swan around 10:30.  Let me know if you care to join.

My new place is at Gables Pin Oak Park - 4848 Pin Oak Park #1503.

Directions from Downtown - take 59 south and exit Newcastle , take a left on Newcastle and follow past Westpark about a quarter mile . You will see several complexes ahead.  Take a right on Pin Oak Park.  Complex will be on the right.

Call on my cell phone if you have problems 713-628-3104.

Let me know if you can come.

-Eric","[{'word': 'Shanna', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Eric', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Gables Pin Oak Park - 4848 Pin Oak Park #1503', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Downtown', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Black Swan', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Shanna', 'PERSON'), ('Eric', 'PERSON'), ('Gables Pin Oak Park - 4848 Pin Oak Park #1503', 'LOCATION'), ('Downtown', 'LOCATION'), ('Black Swan', 'ORG')]"
<20670314.1075844704286.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hi Sara,

I have completed a preliminary legal review of the Account Agreements with 
Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley.  

I read the draft language you sent re: limitation of liability that you 
suggested we add to these and the Bear Stearns agreements for Enron Credit, 
Inc.   Because these agreements have arbitration clauses, this provision as 
drafted might be unenforceable under the NASD rules.  I am going to 
doublecheck the law on this point today or over the weekend.  If this is in 
fact correct, the firms will probably reject the provision on this ground 
especailly if including it would subject them to NASD fines.   In any case, 
we can wait to see what there response is but in the meantime we should set 
aside time to discuss the law on this point.

Cheryl Nelson
Senior Counsel
EB3880D
(713) 345-4693","[{'word': 'Sara', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Goldman Sachs', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Morgan Stanley', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Bear Stearns', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron Credit', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Cheryl Nelson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'NASD', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sara', 'PERSON'), ('Goldman Sachs', 'PERSON'), ('Morgan Stanley', 'PERSON'), ('Bear Stearns', 'PERSON'), ('Enron Credit', 'PERSON'), ('Cheryl Nelson', 'PERSON'), ('NASD', 'ORG')]"
<30515596.1075863378574.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Rick,

Attached are a clean copy of suggested modification of the body of this DASH as well as a copy of the original DASH.  This should give you some sense of the Arcos project's scale and risks.  John Sherriff and Michael Brown reportedly remain confident that this can be sold at a profit in the next three to nine months; however, if it is not, our economics on this project with a current termination cost of over $200 million is a negative NPV of approximately ($150 million).  The Enron board has not seen this, largely because the turbine cost is not specifically related to this project, but no other use of the turbines has been identified, so this project represents a huge potential loss if the sale is not successful.

Please let me know if you would like to discuss further.

Regards,

Dave","[{'word': 'Rick', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'John Sherriff', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Michael Brown', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dave', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'next three to nine months', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Rick', 'PERSON'), ('John Sherriff', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Brown', 'PERSON'), ('Dave', 'PERSON'), ('next three to nine months', 'DATE'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<4485789.1075852180957.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"The Griffith plant is currently down and will probably be down for the rest of the month.  I have put a zero capacity in CAS for the deliveries through 10/31/01.  If it should come up for allocation please analyze whether it is due to flow rate.  As long as it schedules to zero, we are fine, you can ignore the flow rate.  

The contracts which are currently scheduling there must be balanced at zero, if we allocate because of a flow rate the system generates, I may have to put on an imbalance the next morning in order to get the contracts to balance.  If you have any questions while allocating, please ask me.

Thanks for your help in this matter,
Amy","[{'word': 'Griffith', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Amy', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'through 10/31/01', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Griffith', 'PERSON'), ('Amy', 'PERSON'), ('through 10/31/01', 'DATE')]"
<30353395.1075847023823.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Attached for your approval is the form of Enron Corp. Guaranty in favor of 
Engage Energy US, L.P., now known as Coastal Merchant Energy, L.P., which 
guarantees the obligations of ENA under an  ISDA Master Agreement.  We will 
need the standard executed copy.  This guaranty will supersede and replace, 
in part, the prior guaranty with respect to ENA and Counterparty.  The 
guaranty will be fully replaced when counterparty receives the new Enron 
Corp. Guaranty with respect to the obligations of Enron Canada and Engage 
Canada (still covered under the existing guaranty, and such replacement is 
still under negotiation).

 Upon approval and execution, please call me at x33399 to pick up the 
documents.  Thank you for your assistance in this matter.","[{'word': 'Enron Corp.', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Engage Energy US, L.P.', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Coastal Merchant Energy, L.P.', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ENA', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'ISDA Master Agreement', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Enron Canada', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Engage Canada', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Enron Corp.', 'ORG'), ('Engage Energy US, L.P.', 'ORG'), ('Coastal Merchant Energy, L.P.', 'ORG'), ('ENA', 'ORG'), ('ISDA Master Agreement', 'ORG'), ('Enron Canada', 'ORG'), ('Engage Canada', 'ORG')]"
<27105313.1075862889286.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Mr. Lay,

I understand that we may not be having the holiday party.  I think this would be a huge mistake!  We have worked hard all year and recently haven't had much to celebrate.  I know alot of women (myself included) who have already bought their dresses.  I think this could be our Enron Swan Song and go out with a bang!

I think what you did about your bonus was the most unselfish thing a man in your position could do.  I have been honored to work for a man of your caliber.  I hope my next CEO can live up to your very high standards!

Regards,

Michelle
Michelle Hargrave
Global Resource Mgmt.
(713)853-6023
e-mail: michelle.hargrave@enron.com","[{'word': 'Mr. Lay', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Michelle Hargrave', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Enron', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Mr. Lay', 'PERSON'), ('Michelle Hargrave', 'PERSON'), ('Enron', 'ORG')]"
<10051222.1075856274709.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Please have your presentations to me by 10 AM Friday, October 20, 2000.   It 
takes a couple of days to get the materials back from the Copy Center. The 
presentations have to be put in new binders this time and it takes most of a 
day to put everything together in the binders.  Therefore, I  have to have 
the materials to the Copy Center by Friday afternoon in order to get them 
back by Monday afternoon or Tuesday morning.  I will need most of Tuesday to 
get everything assembled in the binders.  Thus the necessity of having your 
completed presentations by Friday morning.

Vince:  Basket Options
  Binary (Digital) Options

Krishna:  Barrier Options
  Other Complex Structures


Thanks for your help on this.

Regards,

Anita","[{'word': 'Vince', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Krishna', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Anita', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Friday, October 20, 2000', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Friday afternoon', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Monday afternoon', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Tuesday morning', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Copy Center', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Vince', 'PERSON'), ('Krishna', 'PERSON'), ('Anita', 'PERSON'), ('Friday, October 20, 2000', 'DATE'), ('Friday afternoon', 'DATE'), ('Monday afternoon', 'DATE'), ('Tuesday morning', 'DATE'), ('Copy Center', 'ORG')]"
<10471374.1075857324240.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hey!? I took your advice & attempted to  contact Karen.? I mailed a letter to 
her old address & had it forwarded  on.? She called me yesterday and we 
talked forever!
She had a boy, Nicholas Elijah Messick, on Leap Day  2/29 by C-section.? He 
weighed 9 lb. 10 oz. (I'm glad she had a  C-section!)? All is well with her.? 
She said that she & her  husband fight a lot but always work things out.? 
They live in a 15 yr. old  house in Rowlett near Hwy. 66.  So, everything 
seems to be very domestic in her  world!? She asked about you.? I said you 
were doing fine & still  in a serious relationship with a girl that's smarter 
than you! (ha!)?  Anyways, just thought I would pass on some friendly 
gossip.? Thank you for  nudging me in the right direction.? Talk to you later 
 Amy
?
?","[{'word': 'Karen', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Nicholas Elijah Messick', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Amy', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Leap Day 2/29', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Rowlett', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Hwy. 66', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}]","[('Karen', 'PERSON'), ('Nicholas Elijah Messick', 'PERSON'), ('Amy', 'PERSON'), ('Leap Day 2/29', 'DATE'), ('Rowlett', 'LOCATION'), ('Hwy. 66', 'LOCATION')]"
<18350952.1075844722787.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Thank you for submitting the following responses on the RSVP
Online Form for the 2001 Enron Law Conference. The
information you submitted is as follows:

Attendance: Y
First Name: Sara
Last Name: Shackleton
Position: Attorney
Legal Group: Enron Wholesale Services
Phone: (713) 853-5620
Fax: (713) 646-3490
Email: sara.shackleton@enron.com
Admin. Name: Kaye Ellis
Admin. Phone: (713) 853-5968
Admin. Email: kaye.ellis@ernon.com
Arrival Date: May 2, 2001
Departure Date: May 4, 2001
Hotel Accommodations: King Sized Bed
Non-Smoking: Y
Other:
Thursday Activity: None Selected - No Activity Selected
Golf Handicap:
Awards Dinner: Y
SAP Company: 0413
SAP Cost Center: 105657
State Bar Licensed: TEXAS
Bar #: 18071900
State Bar Licensed: LOUISIANA
Bar #: 11959

This message is a confirmation of the details of your RSVP
form.  If any of the information is incorrect or your plans
change, e-mail Sara Davidson with the information. Do not
make any changes on the website.","[{'word': 'Sara Shackleton', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Kaye Ellis', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Sara Davidson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'May 2, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'May 4, 2001', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Enron Wholesale Services', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Sara Shackleton', 'PERSON'), ('Kaye Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('Sara Davidson', 'PERSON'), ('May 2, 2001', 'DATE'), ('May 4, 2001', 'DATE'), ('Enron Wholesale Services', 'ORG')]"
<30422702.1075842940585.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hi Jeff,

Just a follow up to our call this morning.  If you get your guy on the phone, 
try and get the following information:

1) Route map, including both end points of the network
2) Amount of capacity they may want to lay off, (they are currently using 
some of the system, how much do they want to offer?)
3) Any contract details, (how long, terms, penalties, restrictive clauses 
like ""cannot resell"")

Once we get some details on the table lets get a call together with them and 
see if there is a deal here.  I will be out of the office from the 3rd 
through the 9th attending a trade show, so if we cannot get this together by 
tomorrow, lets do it next Thursday afternoon.

Thanks


Dan Minter
V: (503)886-0452
F: (503)886-0441","[{'word': 'Jeff', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Dan Minter', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'this morning', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'from the 3rd through the 9th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'tomorrow', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'next Thursday afternoon', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('Dan Minter', 'PERSON'), ('this morning', 'DATE'), ('from the 3rd through the 9th', 'DATE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('next Thursday afternoon', 'DATE')]"
<7999766.1075840528050.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Reliant has indicated that we must use their paper - this point is non-negotiable.

Kay, we will not wire any funds to Reliant until we have your approval of the contract.  I understand that you are also working on a gas contract with TXU.  We need one of these contracts in place so we can buy gas tomorrow morning, it doesn't matter which contract we have in place first.

Doug, Phil, Eric,
The prepayment that we were going to send to Reliant may be going to TXU instead.  We are coming dangerously close to defaulting on the Tallahassee contract.  Robin and I are going to work on a prepayment request for TXU after lunch.","[{'word': 'Kay', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Doug', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Phil', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Eric', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Robin', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Reliant', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'TXU', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'Tallahassee', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Kay', 'PERSON'), ('Doug', 'PERSON'), ('Phil', 'PERSON'), ('Eric', 'PERSON'), ('Robin', 'PERSON'), ('Reliant', 'ORG'), ('TXU', 'ORG'), ('Tallahassee', 'ORG')]"
<3423897.1075858707836.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Charles 

Thanks for the reply.  Your thoughts on the EEI draft in terms of details would be helpful.  As I read it, we still have the problems with the EEI draft that we had with the NERC draft on which it is based  deference, regional rules variances, regional reliability entities, regional advisory boards, limits on FERC authority, etc., etc.  It would also be helpful to have input on whether the plans for EISB could go forward if legislation like the EEI bill were enacted into law.  It would seem not since the ""SRO"" would focus only on ""reliability"" as defined by how the bill defines what matters are subjects for an ""organization standard.""","[{'word': 'Charles', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'EEI', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'NERC', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'EISB', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('EEI', 'ORG'), ('NERC', 'ORG'), ('EISB', 'ORG')]"
<19824952.1075841383999.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Joe,

Attached is link for Financial Trading position.  Job descriptions may not match precisely with your position as it exists today, but that is OK.  We have tried to be as broad as possible in describing the open positions to minimize the number of posting links. Your job will not change, and your offer will be made for the position and duties you are performing now.  The posting requirement is by end of day on Monday, even though this link says by Friday.  You can access the link from the internet at the office or at home.  Please let me know if you have any questions.

 


Regards,

Randy Curry
email:   randall.curry@bridgeline.net
Phone:  832- 851- 2801
Fax:       832 - 851- 2772



 Inline attachment follows","[{'word': 'Joe', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Randy Curry', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ('Randy Curry', 'PERSON')]"
<12085499.1075862333148.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Hey Steve- Since the 6th looks like it is a good day to get together, maybe I could come over to your house around 12:00.   We could go to lunch, and since I had the the last priviledge of  picking out a ""very interesting movie"", I would like you to to pick out the next one! This time I also have a lot more time flexibility in the afternoon.
     Of course, I will drop you a quick line prior to the 6th to make sure your schedule is still on target.  Otherwise, enjoy Thanksgiving with your family (don't get too fat!).  Talk with you later.  Christine
 

Get your FREE download of MSN Explorer at http://explorer.msn.com","[{'word': 'Steve', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Christine', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'the 6th', 'tag': 'DATE'}]","[('Steve', 'PERSON'), ('Christine', 'PERSON'), ('the 6th', 'DATE')]"
<5427197.1075845395123.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"POSREP HOEGH GALLEON, DATE:	10-May	12:00	9:00	(UTC)
A) Position at noon:	N	12 25	E	044 29
B) Dist. From last noon:	443	nm
C) Dist. To go to next port:	1199	nm
D) ETA next port:	Qalhat	13 0900	LT
E) 1: Average sea/wind	Sea:	SW 4	Wind:	SW 3
    2: Average speed	18.46	kn
    3: BOG consumed	0	m3
    4: BOG Total	0	m3
    5: F.O Consumed	164	m3
    6: G.O. Consumed	0	m3

Brgds Knut Bentzr?d
Master LNG/C ""Hoegh Galleon""

E-mail: master.gall@hoegh.no
Teleph: Inmarsat tel.no.+873 330853910
Fax   : Inmarsat fax no.+873 330853913
Telex : Inmarsat B telex no.+583 330853915
Telex : Inmarsat C telex no.+583 430853910 (24hrs.watch)","[{'word': 'Knut Bentzr?d', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': '10-May', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': '13 0900 LT', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'Qalhat', 'tag': 'LOCATION'}, {'word': 'Hoegh', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Knut Bentzr?d', 'PERSON'), ('10-May', 'DATE'), ('13 0900 LT', 'DATE'), ('Qalhat', 'LOCATION'), ('Hoegh', 'ORG')]"
<27236164.1075840579267.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"John,

This is the latest skew calculator file.  It has a sheet for the vol skew table, and it calculates the ENA pdf using a linear interpolation between points on the table, not a polynomial.  

The file shows yesterday's settle data for Jun, and ENA data matches very well.  (All the 2001 contracts agree closely with ENA data from yesterday, in fact.)  I've added a macro that fetches the underlying price, volatility, and interest rate from our in-house EGSPROD32 database.  Let me know if this doesn't work for you.

Feel free to contact any of us if you have any questions or requests regarding this file.  hope it is helpful.

ken","[{'word': 'John', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'ken', 'tag': 'PERSON'}]","[('John', 'PERSON'), ('ken', 'PERSON')]"
<24022347.1075855913369.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"I understand that the return e:mail that I sent to Kim Rizzi on November 27th 
was not opened by HR.  Please note on my e:mail below that I had asked for 
clarification on Brent Price.  This was the second e:mail that I had sent to 
Kim regarding Brent with no reply back.  My first message had noted for Kim 
that Brent was left out of my list, and asked whether or not Rick Causey 
planned to supply a pre-ranking for Brent or if I needed to do so.  Can you 
clarify this for me?  Brent reports to me as the head of operations for EGM 
and to Rick Causey in his role as CAO of EGM.  

Here are the appropriate pre-rankings for grouped by level:

   Superior  Excellent Strong Satisfactory    Needs Improv.  Issues

VP's      Price  Hedstrom
      Hall

Sr. Directors Solmonson Reeves Herod Scribner

Directors  Thomas  Mills  Superty Henenberg Perez   
      Wilson   Venturatos","[{'word': 'Kim Rizzi', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Brent Price', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Rick Causey', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Price Hedstrom', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Hall', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Solmonson Reeves', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Herod Scribner', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Thomas Mills', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Superty Henenberg', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Perez Wilson', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'Venturatos', 'tag': 'PERSON'}, {'word': 'November 27th', 'tag': 'DATE'}, {'word': 'EGM', 'tag': 'ORG'}, {'word': 'CAO of EGM', 'tag': 'ORG'}]","[('Kim Rizzi', 'PERSON'), ('Brent Price', 'PERSON'), ('Rick Causey', 'PERSON'), ('Price Hedstrom', 'PERSON'), ('Hall', 'PERSON'), ('Solmonson Reeves', 'PERSON'), ('Herod Scribner', 'PERSON'), ('Thomas Mills', 'PERSON'), ('Superty Henenberg', 'PERSON'), ('Perez Wilson', 'PERSON'), ('Venturatos', 'PERSON'), ('November 27th', 'DATE'), ('EGM', 'ORG'), ('CAO of EGM', 'ORG')]"
<27979298.1075861635793.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Third Set of Discovery of California Parties to Williams.  Hard copies are
being sent to the restricted service list.


Joseph H. Fagan
ATTORNEY
HellerEhrman

tel.:  202.912.2162
fax:  202.912.2020
e-mail:  jfagan@hewm.com
web:  http://www.hewm.com 
Address:  1666 K Street, N.W.
               Suite 300
               Washington, D.C. 20006-1228

error,  please e-mail the sender at JFagan@HEWM.COM 
.






 - Third Transmittal - Williams.rtf 
<33515286.1075858513006.JavaMail.evans@thyme>,"Market Participants:

Please assure that this Notification is forwarded to your respective
Operating Departments 

Notification of Operating Procedure Update

*	The following new or revised ISO Operating Procedures have been
implemented and are posted for reference on the ISO Website.

ISO Operating Procedure posted:  T-123 WSCC Path 45 ISO-CFE Operating
Transfer Capability (OTC)
Version: 4.5
Effective Date: 6-6-01
Procedure Purpose: Study results show that P-45 is limited to 408 MW
bi-directional and is a 30-minute thermal limit.  The 408 MW OTC is a subset
of the total SDGE/CFE OTC described in San Diego Area procedure T-132.
Changes / Reasons: No change from Spring

*	Please find them at
http://www1.caiso.com/thegrid/operations/opsdoc/index.html under the
appropriate Operating Procedure section heading.

If you have any questions, please e-mail the 'Procedure Control Desk'
mailbox [mailto:procctrldesk@caiso.com] and we will respond as soon as
possible.

Thank-You,
