word,label
Good,O
catch.,O
NY,B-LOCATION
law,O
should,O
apply,O
throughout,O
the,O
Americas,B-LOCATION
and,O
in,O
Japan.,O
We,O
used,O
UK,O
Europe,B-LOCATION
Singapore,B-LOCATION
on,O
theory,O
counterparties,O
there,O
would,O
be,O
more,O
comfortable,O
with,O
Uk,O
law.,O
I,O
'm,O
not,O
sure,O
which,O
Australians,O
prefer.,O
What,O
do,O
you,O
think,O
of,O
following,O
:,O
16.,O
If,O
are,O
accessing,O
this,O
website,O
from,O
North,B-LOCATION
America,I-LOCATION
",",O
South,B-LOCATION
or,O
Japan,B-LOCATION
terms,O
legal,O
Privacy,O
statement,O
shall,O
governed,O
by,O
laws,O
State,O
New,O
York,O
;,O
if,O
any,O
other,O
location,O
its,O
English,O
Leonardo,B-PERSON
Pacheco,I-PERSON
@ENRON,O
Australia,B-LOCATION
Tana,B-PERSON
",",O
Wow,O
you,O
are,O
really,O
on,O
the,O
ball.,O
Looks,O
like,O
we,O
will,O
have,O
a,O
great,O
party.,O
I,O
email,O
Matthias,B-PERSON
and,O
Karin,B-PERSON
about,O
potatoe,O
recipe,O
Stephen,B-PERSON
Long,I-PERSON
garlic,O
bread,O
recipe.,O
Judy,B-PERSON
Weller,I-PERSON
's,O
phone,O
number,O
is,O
713-524-7567.,O
And,O
Mark,B-PERSON
willing,O
to,O
bring,O
whatever,O
;,O
Ulf,B-PERSON
might,O
want,O
help,O
with,O
pork,O
chops,O
chicken.,O
How,O
plans,O
grill,O
going,O
?,O
We,O
can,O
always,O
ours,O
if,O
know,O
of,O
someone,O
truck,O
could,O
borrow.,O
Peace,O
Beth,B-PERSON
Jones,I-PERSON
wrote,O
:,O
got,O
several,O
responses,O
last,O
night,O
this,O
morning,O
by,O
so,O
am,O
attaching,O
revised,O
list.,O
(See,O
attached,O
file,O
church,O
gourmet.doc,O
),O
Name,O
Type,O
Microsoft,O
Word,O
Document,O
(application,O
/msword,O
Encoding,O
base64,O
Description,O
Mac,O
3.0,O
Download,O
Status,O
Not,O
downloaded,O
message,O
-,O
lcm.vcf,O
I,O
am,O
very,O
pleased,O
to,O
announce,O
that,O
L.D.,B-PERSON
Stephens,I-PERSON
has,O
accepted,O
the,O
position,O
of,O
Account,O
Director,O
in,O
Business,O
and,O
Power,O
Development,O
group,O
Northern,O
Natural,O
Gas,O
Marketing,O
Division.,O
been,O
with,O
Enron,B-PERSON
for,O
18,O
years,O
held,O
many,O
positions,O
from,O
Field,O
Technician,O
O,O
&M,O
Supervisor,O
Regional,O
Team,O
Advisor.,O
Most,O
recently,O
was,O
a,O
Sr.,O
Facility,O
Planner,O
had,O
primary,O
accountability,O
provide,O
planning,O
support,O
commercial,O
activities,O
team.,O
B.S.,O
Industrial,O
Technology,O
Southwest,B-LOCATION
Oklahoma,I-LOCATION
State.,O
He,O
will,O
be,O
located,O
Omaha,B-LOCATION
manage,O
number,O
projects,O
primarily,O
area,O
on,O
system,O
power,O
development,O
ethanol,O
market,O
development.,O
Please,O
join,O
me,O
welcoming,O
our,O
group.,O
Thank,O
You.,O
John,B-PERSON
Dushinske,I-PERSON
State,I-LOCATION
Chris,B-PERSON
:,O
We,O
should,O
chat.,O
Per,O
the,O
ISDA,B-ORG
",",O
ENA,B-ORG
is,O
calc,O
agent,O
and,O
we,O
have,O
already,O
agreed,O
to,O
usual,O
Market,O
Disruption,O
Events,O
fallbacks,O
in,O
ISDA.,O
If,O
you,O
want,O
change,O
agreement,O
then,O
can,O
consider,O
items,O
which,O
Merchant,B-ORG
has,O
included,O
draft.,O
As,O
create,O
a,O
draft,O
send,O
form,O
for,O
review.,O
However,O
I,O
do,O
need,O
explain,O
/verify,O
Floating,O
Price,O
B.,O
And,O
verify,O
rounding,O
convention,O
differs,O
from,O
our,O
standard.,O
Please,O
call,O
discuss.,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Shackleton,I-PERSON
Enron,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
1400,O
Smith,O
Street,O
EB,O
3801a,O
Houston,O
Texas,O
77002,O
713-853-5620,O
(phone,O
),O
713-646-3490,O
(fax,O
sara.shackleton,O
@enron.com,O
H,I-PERSON
Foster,I-PERSON
I,O
have,O
made,O
additional,O
changes,O
on,O
pages,O
11-12,O
the,O
Northwest,O
adaptations,O
to,O
make,O
LMP,O
work.,O
indicated,O
kinds,O
of,O
adjustments,O
from,O
PJM,B-ORG
platform,O
necessary,O
it,O
don,O
't,O
think,O
is,O
take,O
a,O
swing,O
at,O
Mark,B-PERSON
Mayer,I-PERSON
BPA,B-PERSON
our,O
point,O
that,O
will,O
was,O
caught,O
flat,O
footed,O
and,O
unprepared,O
for,O
Dick,O
O,O
'Niell,O
's,O
cheap,O
shot.,O
Second,O
",",O
proportion,O
hydro,O
mix,O
other,O
units,O
quite,O
different,O
in,O
NYISO,B-ORG
so,O
fact,O
they,O
fit,O
around,O
edges,O
not,O
necessarily,O
proof,O
work,O
PNW.,O
For,O
reason,O
noted,O
(hydro,O
base,O
load,O
),O
show,O
unit,O
committment,O
process,O
be,O
but,O
you,O
can,O
still,O
produce,O
hourly,O
prices.,O
Steve,B-PERSON
PNW,B-ORG
Louise,B-PERSON
:,O
You,O
requested,O
that,O
I,O
give,O
you,O
a,O
list,O
of,O
things,O
to,O
avoid,O
discussion,O
with,O
ABB.,O
We,O
've,O
maintained,O
reasonably,O
open,O
relationship,O
ABB,B-PERSON
up,O
this,O
point,O
",",O
but,O
here,O
are,O
some,O
(fairly,O
obvious,O
),O
we,O
should,O
probably,O
steer,O
clear,O
1.,O
No,O
about,O
Fronterra,B-ORG
;,O
2.,O
specifics,O
the,O
DeAcero,B-ORG
contract,O
e.g.,O
extension,O
date,O
CP,B-ORG
's,O
etc,O
and,O
3.,O
project,O
credit,O
issues,O
or,O
financing,O
alternatives,O
for,O
project.,O
When,O
contingent,O
was,O
last,O
(Feb,O
2001,I-DATE
Dave,B-PERSON
Janet,B-PERSON
essentially,O
indicated,O
an,O
important,O
Enron,B-ORG
were,O
entirely,O
committed,O
seeing,O
it,O
through,O
if,O
weren,O
't,O
damn,O
CFE,B-ORG
'd,O
already,O
be,O
done,O
etc.,O
think,O
stick,O
line,O
'll,O
fine.,O
If,O
anything,O
else,O
let,O
know,O
ASAP.,O
DTT,B-PERSON
Feb,B-DATE
Dear,O
Mr.,O
LARRY,B-PERSON
CAMPBELL,I-PERSON
:,O
Thank,O
you,O
for,O
your,O
order.,O
You,O
sold,O
120,O
shares,O
of,O
BRCD,B-ORG
(Brocade,O
Communications,I-ORG
Sys,I-ORG
I,I-ORG
Com,I-ORG
),O
at,O
169.000000.,O
ORDER,O
DETAILS,O
The,O
tracking,O
number,O
this,O
order,O
is,O
B-500-AATD-5965,O
Order,O
entered,O
14,O
:18,O
:29,O
on,O
11,O
/30,O
/00,O
processing,O
began,O
:30,O
executed,O
:37,O
ACCOUNT,O
Time,O
and,O
Date,O
Your,O
position,O
in,O
0,O
real,O
cash,O
total,O
$5,O
",685.43",O
will,O
receive,O
a,O
printed,O
Datek,B-ORG
Online,I-ORG
confirmation,O
by,O
postal,O
mail,O
",",O
or,O
electronic,O
delivery,O
if,O
are,O
subscribed,O
to,O
that,O
service.,O
Questions,O
regarding,O
transaction,O
?,O
Contact,O
our,O
Customer,O
Support,O
department,O
e-mailing,O
support,O
@datek.com.,O
Please,O
reference,O
the,O
number.,O
Brocade,B-ORG
DON,B-PERSON
BAUGHMAN,I-PERSON
JR,I-PERSON
",",O
The,O
PEP,O
system,O
closes,O
on,O
Friday,O
May,O
25,O
2001.,O
Our,O
records,O
indicate,O
that,O
you,O
have,O
not,O
selected,O
reviewers.,O
Please,O
suggest,O
a,O
list,O
of,O
reviewers,O
as,O
quickly,O
possible,O
-,O
the,O
feedback,O
process,O
cannot,O
begin,O
until,O
your,O
has,O
been,O
reviewed,O
and,O
approved,O
by,O
supervisor.,O
To,O
access,O
at,O
http,O
:,O
/,O
/pep.enron.com,O
select,O
'Suggest,O
Reviewers,O
',O
from,O
Main,O
Menu.,O
If,O
any,O
questions,O
regarding,O
PRC,O
or,O
please,O
contact,O
Help,O
Desk,O
Houston,O
1.713.853.4777,O
Option,O
4,O
email,O
perfmgmt,O
@enron.com,O
London,O
44.207.783.4040,O
pep.enquiries,O
Ken,B-PERSON
-,O
I,O
thought,O
would,O
give,O
you,O
a,O
quick,O
update,O
on,O
our,O
conversations,O
regarding,O
Atlantic,B-PERSON
Copper.,O
Our,O
team,O
met,O
with,O
the,O
senior,O
management,O
from,O
Copper,I-PERSON
last,B-DATE
week,I-DATE
in,O
concert,O
London,B-ORG
Metal,I-ORG
Exchange,I-ORG
Week.,O
There,O
are,O
several,O
hurdles,O
to,O
overcome,O
structuring,O
deal,O
acquire,O
and,O
long,O
term,O
copper,O
concentrates,O
supply,O
FM,B-PERSON
's,O
Indonesian,O
mine,O
complex.,O
Current,O
contract,O
prices,O
for,O
smelting,O
refining,O
capacity,O
low,O
they,O
might,O
be,O
bit,O
unrealistic,O
price.,O
We,O
suggested,O
conceptual,O
structure,O
that,O
may,O
work,O
but,O
is,O
probably,O
shot,O
at,O
this,B-DATE
time.,O
They,O
were,O
interested,O
requested,O
more,O
definitive,O
proposal,O
",",O
which,O
we,O
will,O
develop,O
week.,O
keep,O
posted.,O
John,B-PERSON
Phyllis,B-PERSON
:,O
Here,O
is,O
where,O
I,O
understand,O
we,O
are,O
with,O
the,O
LOC,O
provisions,O
and,O
LC,O
for.,O
1.,O
No,O
changes,O
will,O
be,O
made,O
to,O
provisions.,O
2.,O
In,O
form,O
of,O
",",O
i,O
delete,O
language,O
in,O
drawing,O
condition,O
1,O
"""the",O
entire,O
undrawn,O
amount,O
"LOC""",O
put,O
"""",O
"$.""",O
alos,O
automatic,O
renewal,O
third,O
paragraph,O
such,O
that,O
it,O
read,O
"""This",O
shall,O
expire,O
days,O
from,O
date,O
"issuance.""",O
Are,O
ready,O
finalize,O
?,O
If,O
so,O
e-mail,O
you,O
final,O
forms,O
docs.,O
Carol,B-PERSON
St.,I-PERSON
Clair,I-PERSON
EB,O
3889,O
713-853-3989,O
(Phone,O
),O
713-646-3393,O
(Fax,O
carol.st.clair,O
@enron.com,O
James,B-PERSON
",",O
please,O
find,O
the,O
file,O
attached,O
with,O
SoCal,B-ORG
amounts,O
in,O
dispute,O
as,O
we,O
discussed.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
need,O
any,O
further,O
assistance.,O
Richard,B-PERSON
We,O
are,O
meeting,O
tomorrow,B-DATE
afternoon,I-DATE
(internally,O
),O
to,O
discuss,O
a,B-DATE
possible,O
settlement,O
position.,O
Could,O
verify,O
from,O
March,O
2001,O
through,O
September,O
by,O
lunch,O
time,O
?,O
(I,O
was,O
using,O
combination,O
of,O
spreadsheet,O
Linda,B-PERSON
Ward,I-PERSON
had,O
provided,O
couple,I-DATE
months,I-DATE
ago,I-DATE
and,O
inquiring,O
CBS,B-ORG
invoice,O
system.,O
I,O
want,O
make,O
sure,O
have,O
most,O
current,O
information.,O
If,O
not,O
let,O
your,O
timing.,O
Also,O
been,O
billing,O
interest,O
on,O
disputed,O
don,O
't,O
see,O
anything,O
Please,O
know.,O
Thanks,O
Lindy,B-PERSON
Dear,O
General,O
Counsels,O
:,O
The,O
attachments,O
are,O
Westlaw,B-ORG
October,O
allocations,O
and,O
Lexis-Nexis,B-ORG
September,O
Usage,O
(Actuals,O
),O
reports.,O
Please,O
feel,O
free,O
to,O
call,O
me,O
if,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions.,O
We,O
had,O
an,O
amendment,O
contract,O
include,O
Public,O
Records,O
Dow,O
Jones,O
/Company,O
News,O
with,O
current,O
$14,O
",000",O
monthly,O
rate,O
in,O
August.,O
As,O
of,O
today,B-DATE
",",O
I,O
am,O
still,O
working,O
get,O
Aug.,O
Sept.,O
charges,O
reflect,O
the,O
changes,O
(total,O
about,O
$5,O
credit,O
).,O
apologize,O
for,O
not,O
having,O
corrected,O
invoices,O
do,O
allocation,O
reports,O
you.,O
Lexis,O
Nexis,O
report,O
has,O
coming,O
yet.,O
August,B-DATE
one,O
according,O
Julie,B-PERSON
Pechersky,I-PERSON
was,O
sent,O
but,O
got,O
lost,O
mail.,O
process,O
send,O
us,O
another,O
copy.,O
Again,O
long,O
wait,O
even,O
it,O
's,O
under,O
my,O
control.,O
Thanks,O
Sylvia,B-PERSON
Hu,I-PERSON
Corporate,O
Law,O
Information,O
Services,O
x36775,O
Mike,B-PERSON
",",O
We,O
will,O
be,O
setting,O
up,O
both,O
physical,O
and,O
financial,O
books,O
for,O
everyone.,O
I,O
know,O
not,O
everyone,O
have,O
but,O
to,O
keep,O
it,O
consistent,O
just,O
in,O
case.,O
the,O
10,O
names,O
you,O
sent,O
Jeff,B-PERSON
earlier,O
please,O
let,O
me,O
if,O
that,O
changes.,O
Do,O
what,O
structure,O
going,O
look,O
like,O
?,O
ie.,O
each,O
trader,O
assigned,O
specific,O
curves,O
/locations,O
cash,O
vs.,O
term,O
how,O
many,O
different,O
people,O
curves.,O
starting,O
over,O
with,O
our,O
curve,O
files,O
also.,O
want,O
only,O
start,O
true,O
published,O
derived,O
/internal,O
aren,O
't,O
necessary,O
we,O
need,O
create,O
more,O
into,O
later.,O
Since,O
number,O
of,O
greatly,O
reduced,O
probably,O
one,O
file.,O
Thanks,O
Kam,B-PERSON
Pat,B-PERSON
For,O
your,O
information,O
",",O
I,O
have,O
attached,O
the,O
current,O
proformas,O
(UBS,O
and,O
standard,O
).,O
know,O
John,B-PERSON
Mike,B-PERSON
had,O
a,O
lot,O
of,O
conversations,O
on,O
this,O
-,O
essentially,O
where,O
we,O
stand,O
is,O
that,O
work,O
has,O
been,O
done,O
to,O
complete,O
commercial,O
reductions,O
(by,O
name,O
),O
but,O
non-commercial,O
groups,O
just,O
reduced,O
across,O
board,O
intend,O
start,O
process,O
today,O
how,O
cut,O
numbers,O
side.,O
The,O
theory,O
was,O
communicating,O
Netcolite,O
concept,O
something,O
would,O
not,O
do,O
until,O
bit,O
more,O
clarity.,O
Webb,B-PERSON
knows,O
's,O
about,O
it,O
Hope,O
helps.,O
Louise,B-PERSON
Kitchen,O
Chief,O
Operating,O
Officer,O
Enron,B-ORG
Americas,I-ORG
Tel,O
:,O
713,O
853,O
3488,O
Fax,O
646,O
2308,O
UBS,B-ORG
This,O
is,O
a,O
friendly,O
reminder,O
for,O
your,O
support,O
the,O
American,O
Heart,O
Walk,O
on,O
Nov,B-DATE
3.,O
I,O
thank,O
you,O
all.,O
Several,O
of,O
have,O
pledged,O
support.,O
Please,O
submit,O
to,O
me,O
tax,O
deductible,O
contribution,O
by,O
22,B-DATE
October,I-DATE
",",O
Monday,O
so,O
can,O
turn,O
our,O
team,O
's,O
collection,O
in,O
before,O
deadline,O
30,B-DATE
Tuesday.,O
In,O
order,O
obtain,O
Enron,B-ORG
matching,O
gift,O
behalf,O
donation,O
also,O
would,O
like,O
GIS,O
number,O
(900...,O
),O
since,O
program,O
now,O
has,O
gone,O
paperless.,O
My,O
inter-office,O
address,O
Mail,O
stop,O
ECS,O
03-455.,O
Tushar,B-PERSON
Dhruv,I-PERSON
03524,O
713-853-5336,O
(Office,O
713-503-6798,O
(Cell,O
713-646-3653,O
(Fax,O
3,I-DATE
Geynille,B-PERSON
and,O
team,O
",",O
I,O
'll,O
be,O
at,O
Harvard,B-LOCATION
on,B-DATE
the,I-DATE
3rd,I-DATE
morning,I-DATE
of,I-DATE
4thI,O
'm,O
happy,O
to,O
take,O
short,O
drive,O
participate,O
in,O
reception,O
evening,I-DATE
4th.,O
If,O
needed,O
can,O
interviews,O
5th.,O
Also,O
Carol,B-PERSON
/Cindy,O
'd,O
like,O
see,O
if,O
we,O
follow,O
up,O
Jean,O
Baker,O
Miller,O
Training,O
Institute,O
research,O
relationship,O
possibilities,O
sometime,O
care,O
my,O
own,O
arrangements,O
expenses,O
but,O
would,O
you,O
please,O
reserve,O
a,O
room,O
for,O
me,O
(for,O
4th,I-DATE
),O
same,O
location,O
as,O
rest,O
group,O
will,O
staying,O
?,O
Thanks,O
!,O
Christie.,O
Cindy,B-PERSON
Christie,B-PERSON
5th,I-DATE
Dear,O
ROD,O
",",O
You,O
have,O
received,O
this,O
email,O
because,O
you,O
are,O
a,O
valued,O
customer,O
of,O
Platts,B-ORG
-,O
the,O
energy,O
information,O
division,O
The,B-ORG
McGraw,I-ORG
Hill,I-ORG
Companies.,O
It,O
's,O
easy,O
to,O
subscribe,O
GLOBAL,O
ENERGY,O
BUSINESS.,O
Click,O
here,O
answer,O
few,O
short,O
questions,O
and,O
be,O
on,O
your,O
way,O
FREE,O
subscription,O
BUSINESS,O
!,O
is,O
magazine,O
choice,O
for,O
executives,O
senior,O
managers,O
worldwide.,O
In,O
each,O
issue,O
will,O
receive,O
comprehensive,O
analysis,O
perspective,O
host,O
subjects,O
essential,O
firm,O
operation,O
including,O
:,O
Energy,O
Trading,O
Risk,O
Management,O
Information,O
Technologies,O
Power,O
Generation,O
Delivery,O
*,O
Finance,O
Retail,O
Business,O
Legal,O
/Regulatory,O
Strategies,O
Corporate,O
/Executive,O
Profiles,O
link,O
below,O
If,O
feel,O
message,O
in,O
error,O
or,O
would,O
like,O
removed,O
from,O
list,O
please,O
click,O
below.,O
Companies,I-ORG
Pinnacle,B-DATE
2001,I-DATE
is,O
quickly,O
approaching,O
!,O
Remember,O
",",O
all,O
EES,B-ORG
employees,O
are,O
eligible,O
to,O
be,O
nominated,O
but,O
only,O
those,O
who,O
stand,O
out,O
as,O
top,O
performers,O
in,O
their,O
field,O
will,O
selected,O
for,O
participation.,O
held,O
at,O
a,O
five-star,O
resort,O
on,O
the,O
island,O
of,O
Nevis,B-LOCATION
West,B-LOCATION
Indies.,O
This,O
years,O
event,O
an,O
exciting,O
and,O
great,O
experience,O
selected.,O
Click,O
attachment,O
below,O
get,O
feel,O
what,O
's,O
come,O
2001.,O
After,O
launching,O
file,O
website,O
can,O
accessed,O
by,O
clicking,O
link,O
bottom,O
page.,O
Indies,I-LOCATION
It,O
's,O
time,O
to,O
update,O
the,O
McAfee,B-ORG
virus,O
files....,O
Please,O
Note,O
:,O
This,O
is,O
for,O
Windows95,O
customers,O
only,O
",",O
if,O
you,O
have,O
questions,O
call,O
Helpdesk.,O
But,O
before,O
run,O
winstall,O
please,O
verify,O
that,O
version,O
4.0,O
or,O
greater,O
To,O
check,O
VShield,O
Right,O
click,O
on,O
Virus,O
shield,O
in,O
lower,O
right,O
corner,O
Select,O
About,O
The,O
should,O
be,O
not,O
contact,O
Helpdesk,I-ORG
Update,O
files,O
Click,O
Start,O
Winstall,O
Auto,O
take,O
about,O
20,O
seconds,O
-,O
If,O
don,O
't,O
When,O
completed,O
may,O
prompt,O
reboot,O
your,O
PC,O
any,O
concerns,O
running,O
Thanks,O
Omaha,B-ORG
ETS,I-ORG
x7454,O
87,O
",7454",O
I,O
am,O
writing,O
to,O
you,O
as,O
Co-chair,O
of,O
the,O
2001,B-DATE
Enron,B-ORG
Kids,I-ORG
program.,O
A,O
lot,O
ex-Enron,O
folks,O
who,O
use,O
your,O
website,O
were,O
involved,O
in,O
this,O
year,O
's,O
Gordon,O
Elementary,O
School,O
adoption,O
Many,O
these,O
people,O
sacrificed,O
some,O
their,O
own,O
Christmas,O
so,O
that,O
kids,O
at,O
would,O
not,O
be,O
let,O
down.,O
like,O
them,O
know,O
efforts,O
truly,O
appreciated,O
by,O
students,O
",",O
faculty,O
and,O
especially,O
those,O
us,O
on,O
Committee.,O
Would,O
please,O
consider,O
posting,O
site,O
attached,O
thank-you,O
letter,O
from,O
school,O
?,O
thank,O
Kevin,B-PERSON
Hyatt,I-PERSON
Co-Chair,O
Committee,I-ORG
It,O
is,O
unbelievable,O
how,O
the,O
management,O
(both,O
past,O
and,O
present,O
),O
think,O
they,O
can,O
run,O
a,O
business,O
with,O
no,O
regard,O
for,O
customer.,O
They,O
have,O
to,O
be,O
one,O
of,O
worst,O
marketing,O
organizations,O
in,O
world.,O
great,O
product,O
",",O
but,O
don,O
't,O
clue,O
on,O
promote,O
it.,O
Another,O
big,O
news,O
item,O
:,O
PPI,B-ORG
used,O
headline,O
sponser.,O
left,O
few,O
years,O
ago,O
FedEx,B-ORG
came,O
board.,O
Rumors,O
are,O
rampant,O
that,O
will,O
leaving,O
soon.,O
You,O
wonder,O
what,O
it,O
takes,O
make,O
light,O
go,O
some,O
people.,O
extremely,O
frustrating,O
try,O
continue,O
fan.,O
?,O
On,O
Friday,O
",",O
Socalgas,B-PERSON
?filed,O
a,O
protest,O
to,O
the,O
emergency,O
application,O
we,O
filed,O
on,O
Thursday,O
which,O
asked,O
CPUC,B-PERSON
exercise,O
its,O
authority,O
under,O
Public,O
Utility,O
Code,O
section,O
2774,O
and,O
order,O
provide,O
use,O
with,O
assistance,O
avert,O
core,O
gas,O
supply,O
shortages.,O
asserts,O
(1,O
),O
does,O
not,O
apply,O
shortages,O
arising,O
from,O
financial,O
difficulties,O
;,O
(2,O
requested,O
would,O
jeopardize,O
viability,O
ability,O
service,O
own,O
customers,O
(3,O
relief,O
be,O
an,O
unconstitutional,O
taking,O
of,O
property,O
(4,O
PG,O
&E,O
has,O
exhausted,O
remedies,O
in,O
particular,O
complains,O
that,O
wants,O
act,O
before,O
diverts,O
noncore,O
supplies.,O
states,O
it,O
plans,O
ask,O
federal,O
court,O
for,O
injunctive,O
prevent,O
issuance,O
order.,O
-,O
Protest,O
&E-cover.doc,O
Opposition-PG,O
&E.doc,O
CERTIFICATE,O
OF,O
SERVICE.doc,O
BROADCAST,O
MESSAGE,O
TO,O
ALL,O
PILOTS,O
:,O
PLEASE,O
REMEMBER,O
CONTACT,O
YOUR,O
PATIENT,O
AS,O
SOON,O
YOU,O
RECEIVE,O
THE,O
PAPERWORK,O
",",O
AND,O
AT,O
LEAST,O
24,O
HOURS,O
BEFORE,O
FLIGHT,O
CONFIRM,O
TIME,O
PLACE.,O
WE,O
HAVE,O
HAD,O
PATIENTS,O
CALLING,O
IN,O
BECAUSE,O
THEY,O
HAVEN,O
'T,O
HEARD,O
FROM,O
THEIR,O
PILOT,O
YET.,O
ALSO,O
SOME,O
ARE,O
WORRIED,O
WHEN,O
DON,O
HEAR,O
MISSION,O
DATE,O
GETS,O
CLOSE,O
FINDING,O
OTHER,O
WAYS,O
GET,O
THERE,O
CANCELING.,O
I,O
currently,O
have,O
13,O
pending,O
missions.,O
If,O
you,O
can,O
fly,O
please,O
call,O
or,O
email,O
the,O
office,O
as,O
soon,O
possible.,O
1,O
for,O
SAT,O
1.,O
New,B-LOCATION
Orleans,I-LOCATION
to,O
Huntsville,O
AL,O
(leg,O
of,O
3,O
leg,O
mission,O
),O
THURS,O
Houston,B-LOCATION
Jackson,O
MS,O
(LEG,O
2,O
CHECK,O
WEBSITE,O
FOR,O
OTHERS,O
thank,O
Beth,B-PERSON
972,O
458,O
0700,O
afsc,O
@angelflightsc.org,O
http,O
/,O
/www.angelflightsc.org,O
/afpage2a.htm,O
I,O
am,O
writing,O
to,I-DATE
make,O
a,O
correction,O
yesterday,B-DATE
's,O
table.,O
Joel,B-PERSON
and,O
were,O
looking,O
over,O
Connecticut,B-LOCATION
SIP,O
rule,O
because,O
he,O
noticed,O
that,O
1990,I-DATE
seemed,O
too,O
early.,O
defines,O
baseline,O
EGUs,O
as,O
those,O
operating,O
prior,I-DATE
units,O
are,O
allocated,O
from,O
the,I-DATE
main,O
trading,O
budget.,O
The,O
change,O
would,O
like,O
note,O
is,O
state,O
also,O
distinguishes,O
between,O
"""new",O
"units""",O
"EGUs.""",O
New,O
anything,O
2001,O
season,I-DATE
they,O
separately,O
",",O
but,O
point,O
will,O
receive,O
allowances,O
pool,O
just,O
be,O
differently.,O
This,O
won,O
't,O
affect,O
our,O
current,O
tasks,O
does,O
not,O
allocate,O
until,O
three,B-DATE
months,I-DATE
start,I-DATE
of,I-DATE
season.,O
attaching,O
corrected,O
Thanks,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Here,O
is,O
the,O
final,O
draft,O
of,O
my,O
rebuttal,O
testimony.,O
?,O
I,O
will,O
be,O
spending,O
rest,O
morning,O
cleaning,O
up,O
few,O
remaining,O
holes,O
for,O
numbers,O
",",O
etc.,O
Please,O
note,O
have,O
added,O
extensive,O
to,O
SCGC,B-ORG
/,O
TURN,B-ORG
study,O
showning,O
that,O
demand,O
charges,O
could,O
increase,O
EG,O
fixed,O
costs,O
by,O
20,O
%.,O
The,O
which,O
Edison,B-ORG
received,O
in,O
a,O
data,O
response,O
late,B-DATE
Wednesday,I-DATE
very,O
weak.,O
call,O
with,O
any,O
comments,O
1,O
p.m.,O
today.,O
Also,O
this,O
has,O
revised,O
language,O
indicating,O
testimony,O
not,O
meant,O
express,O
CCC,B-ORG
's,O
or,O
Dynegy,B-ORG
opposition,O
element,O
Interim,B-ORG
Settlement.,O
would,O
appreciate,O
feedback,O
on,O
whether,O
consistent,O
how,O
other,O
signatories,O
Settlement,I-ORG
are,O
dealing,O
issue.,O
Tom,B-PERSON
Beach,I-PERSON
You,O
are,O
invited,O
to,O
a,O
MEETING,O
OF,O
THE,O
MINDS,O
!,O
On,O
Thursday,B-DATE
August,I-DATE
30,I-DATE
@,O
4,O
:30,O
please,O
",",O
plan,O
on,O
attending,O
the,O
monthly,O
24,O
hour,O
group,O
meeting.,O
Agenda,O
:,O
will,O
have,O
opportunity,O
meet,O
Introductions,O
of,O
new,O
staff.,O
Discuss,O
current,O
events.,O
be,O
able,O
make,O
suggestions,O
for,O
group.,O
Be,O
advised,O
desk,O
happenings.,O
Open,O
forum,O
discussion.,O
There,O
happy,O
immediately,O
following,O
meeting,O
held,O
in,O
or,O
near,O
Downtown.,O
Sling,O
me,O
some,O
where,O
you,O
might,O
want,O
go.,O
If,O
any,O
questions,O
give,O
call.,O
See,O
y,O
'all,O
there.,O
Don,B-PERSON
Cell,O
No.,O
281-787-0029,O
Downtown,B-LOCATION
What,O
does,O
this,O
all,O
mean,O
for,O
you,O
after,O
July,O
1,O
",",O
2000,O
?,O
New,O
SAP,O
Coding,O
everyone,O
This,O
includes,O
new,O
General,O
Ledger,O
Accounts,O
Workorder,O
numbers,O
and,O
Cost,O
Centers.,O
Company,O
have,O
now,O
been,O
expanded,O
to,O
four,O
positions.,O
All,O
departments,O
assigned,O
a,O
Center,O
number,O
A,O
/Cost,O
must,O
be,O
used,O
request,O
Houston,B-LOCATION
Office,I-LOCATION
internal,O
services,O
such,O
as,O
:,O
Forms,O
&,O
Stationary,O
Overnight,O
Deliveries,O
(Fed,O
Ex,O
UPS,O
etc.,O
),O
Audio,O
/Visual,O
Services,O
TAP,O
-,O
Travel,O
Agency,O
in,O
the,O
Park,O
/C,O
Lighting,O
hours,O
Catering,O
Contract,O
Staff,O
forms,O
developed,O
Invoice,O
Expense,O
Reports,O
will,O
accommodate,O
codes.,O
Where,O
do,O
find,O
information,O
Documentation,O
cost,O
center,O
codes,O
are,O
on,O
intranet,O
"""Quick",O
"Reference""",O
site,O
at,O
http,O
/,O
/sap.enron.com,O
/quickref,O
Call,O
your,O
Project,O
Manager,O
Here,O
are,O
two,O
documents,O
per,O
your,O
request,O
",",O
Maureen,B-PERSON
-,O
I,O
was,O
not,O
sure,O
which,O
one,O
you,O
wanted,O
:,O
(See,O
attached,O
file,O
5,O
Part,O
Leadership,O
ModelFall,O
2000.doc,O
),O
Evaluations1.ppt,O
++,O
|,O
This,O
message,O
may,O
contain,O
confidential,O
and,O
/or,O
privileged,O
information.,O
If,O
the,O
addressee,O
or,O
authorized,O
to,O
receive,O
this,O
for,O
must,O
use,O
copy,O
disclose,O
take,O
any,O
action,O
based,O
on,O
information,O
herein.,O
have,O
received,O
in,O
error,O
please,O
advise,O
sender,O
immediately,O
by,O
reply,O
e-mail,O
delete,O
message.,O
Thank,O
cooperation.,O
Mr.,B-PERSON
Lay,I-PERSON
",",O
We,O
have,O
not,O
met,O
but,O
I,O
want,O
to,O
thank,O
you,O
for,O
the,O
letter,O
sent,O
all,O
employees,O
re,O
:,O
Sept.,B-DATE
11.,O
am,O
a,O
still-new,O
employee,O
(1+,O
years,O
),O
of,O
Portland,B-ORG
General,I-ORG
Electric,I-ORG
(a,O
wholly,O
owned,O
electric,O
utility,O
subsidiary,O
:-,O
tell,O
how,O
proud,O
being,O
member,O
team,O
so,O
dedicated,O
doing,O
its,O
best,O
at,O
times,O
even,O
in,O
absolute,O
worst,O
as,O
we,O
've,O
experienced,O
last,B-DATE
month.,O
only,O
hope,O
that,O
if,O
PGE,O
must,O
leave,O
Enron,B-ORG
family,O
will,O
be,O
able,O
maintain,O
same,O
high,O
level,O
respect,O
and,O
integrity,O
achieved,O
date.,O
an,O
/PGE,O
employee.,O
Regards,O
Jeana,B-PERSON
McClure,I-PERSON
e42625,O
Web,O
Specialist,O
III,O
503.464.2843,O
http,O
/,O
/www.portlandgeneral.com,O
Do,O
You,O
Yahoo,O
!,O
?,O
Make,O
great,O
connection,O
Personals.,O
/personals.yahoo.com,O
11,I-DATE
month,I-DATE
Ernie,B-PERSON
and,O
Gerald,B-PERSON
",",O
well,O
dudes,O
we,O
're,O
doing,O
just,O
what,O
said,O
were,O
not,O
going,O
to,O
do.,O
Fall,O
out,O
of,O
touch,O
again.,O
Here,O
is,O
the,O
latest.,O
I,O
am,O
on,O
my,O
ship,O
for,O
six,O
months,O
now.,O
We,O
left,O
June,B-DATE
4th,I-DATE
get,O
back,O
in,O
November.,O
It,O
's,O
a,O
bitch,O
be,O
gone,O
from,O
family,O
that,O
long,O
but,O
it,O
very,O
busy,O
so,O
goes,O
fast,O
me.,O
had,O
our,O
fourth,O
(and,O
probably,O
last,O
),O
kid,O
May,B-DATE
13th.,O
Her,O
name,O
Chloe,B-PERSON
Elizabeth.,O
She,O
perfect.,O
My,O
two,O
year,O
old,O
(Kate,O
was,O
surprised,O
when,O
brought,O
her,O
home.,O
Carson,B-PERSON
he,O
wanted,O
brother,O
Kelly,B-PERSON
wants,O
hold,O
all,O
time.,O
You,O
can,O
check,O
some,O
pictures,O
at,O
www.geocities.com,O
/pbieraugel.,O
Take,O
easy,O
you,O
guys,O
stay,O
touch.,O
Paul.,O
Elizabeth,I-PERSON
Kate,B-PERSON
Paul,B-PERSON
November,B-DATE
13th,I-DATE
Dear,O
Vince,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
was,O
wondering,O
whether,O
in,O
addition,O
to,O
your,O
talk,O
on,O
market,O
and,O
credit,O
risk,O
at,O
EPRM,B-LOCATION
you,O
would,O
be,O
interested,O
participating,O
the,O
panel,O
debate,O
beginning,O
of,O
day,O
two,O
?,O
The,O
will,O
a,O
senior-level,O
future,O
US,B-LOCATION
power,O
markets,O
thought,O
this,O
might,O
something,O
speaking,O
on.,O
have,O
reattached,O
an,O
up-to-date,O
version,O
agenda.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
what,O
think.,O
Best,O
wishes,O
Victoria,B-PERSON
P.S.,O
other,O
people,O
invited,O
so,O
far,O
take,O
part,O
are,O
Eddie,O
Meche,O
Reliant,B-ORG
Bill,B-PERSON
Schivley,I-PERSON
Select,B-ORG
Energy.,O
Kerridge,I-PERSON
Manager,O
Risk,B-ORG
&,O
Conferences,O
Waters,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
T,O
:,O
+44,O
(0,O
)20,O
7484,O
9875,O
F,O
9800,O
E,O
vkerridge,O
@riskwaters.com,O
http,O
/,O
/www.riskwaters.com,O
Haymarket,O
House,O
28-29,O
London,O
SW1Y,O
4RX,O
-,O
2002,O
draft.doc,O
Energy,I-ORG
Oh,O
no.,O
In,O
the,O
meanwhile,O
",",O
Ella,B-PERSON
learned,O
to,O
tie,O
her,O
shoes.,O
Unbelievalbe,O
but,O
she,O
just,O
did,O
it,O
like,O
that.,O
I,O
talked,O
about,O
having,O
Ms,B-PERSON
Jane,I-PERSON
help,O
learn,O
and,O
put,O
me,O
shame.,O
Sam,B-PERSON
misses,O
you.,O
want,O
book,O
Broadmoor,B-LOCATION
-,O
looks,O
great,O
3,O
days,O
tennis,O
1,O
/2,O
day,O
Friday,B-DATE
Sat,O
Sun,O
August,O
10,O
11,O
12.,O
Dede,B-PERSON
is,O
booked,O
have,O
a,O
call,O
in,O
for,O
you,O
me.,O
You,O
'll,O
come,O
right,O
?,O
miss,O
signed,O
up,O
little,O
mixed,O
doubles,O
on,O
night,I-DATE
630,O
-830.,O
Do,O
sign,O
Everybody,O
fine.,O
This,O
is,O
how,O
the,O
logic,O
now,O
within,O
UBSWenergy.com,B-ORG
:,O
All,O
counterparties,O
with,O
Master,O
Agreements,O
ECC,B-PERSON
that,O
hit,O
a,O
US,O
product,O
must,O
be,O
booked,O
as,O
two,O
legs,O
leg,O
one,O
between,O
and,O
counterparty,O
risk,O
assignment,O
of,O
FT-US,O
/CAND-ERMS,O
;,O
flipping,O
position,O
out,O
to,O
appropriate,O
book,O
(the,O
on,O
online,O
).,O
applies,O
only,O
finanical,O
swaps,O
not,O
physical,O
deals.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
there,O
going,O
change,O
so,O
what,O
deals,O
should,O
look,O
like,O
in,O
Tagg.,O
The,O
programmers,O
need,O
time,O
modify,O
I,O
test,O
!,O
Thanks,O
for,O
your,O
help.,O
Dawn,B-PERSON
3-9353,O
I,O
have,O
been,O
working,O
with,O
Gerald,B-PERSON
Nemec,I-PERSON
on,O
precedent,O
agreements,O
to,O
gas,O
transportation,O
Transcontinental,B-ORG
Gas,I-ORG
Pipeline.,O
The,O
provide,O
pipeline,O
capacity,O
in,O
support,O
of,O
two,O
electric,O
generation,O
plant,O
projects,O
that,O
Enron,B-ORG
is,O
developing,O
Georgia.,O
project,O
companies,O
are,O
the,O
Hartwell,B-ORG
Land,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
",",O
L.L.C.,O
and,O
Athens,B-ORG
Transco,O
has,O
requested,O
a,O
corporate,O
guaranty,O
from,O
cover,O
obligations,O
Athens.,O
At,O
first,O
provided,O
their,O
form,O
but,O
we,O
rejected,O
it.,O
Later,O
our,O
preferred,O
guaranty.,O
reviewed,O
this,O
proposed,O
revisions.,O
believe,O
forwarded,O
these,O
comments,O
you.,O
Could,O
you,O
please,O
give,O
or,O
myself,O
an,O
update,O
your,O
review,O
's,O
comments.,O
Georgia,B-LOCATION
Pipeline,I-ORG
John,B-PERSON
I,O
am,O
surprised,O
that,O
you,O
interpret,O
this,O
is,O
a,O
new,O
request.,O
From,O
day,O
1,O
",",O
ETS,B-ORG
has,O
been,O
responsible,O
for,O
preparing,O
Level,O
B,O
estimate,O
the,O
Sun,O
Devil,O
project.,O
What,O
would,O
like,O
your,O
group,O
to,O
do,O
come,O
up,O
with,O
cost,O
all,O
work,O
related,O
environmentsl,O
aspect,O
of,O
project,O
from,O
today,O
through,O
completion,O
i.e,O
Jan,O
2004,O
in,O
service,O
date,O
Timewise,O
lime,O
first,O
pass,O
by,O
Sept,B-DATE
21,I-DATE
second,O
26,I-DATE
and,O
final,O
complete,O
28,I-DATE
Please,O
call,O
me,O
if,O
unclear,O
so,O
we,O
can,O
discuss.,O
Thanks,O
Dave,B-PERSON
:,O
Below,O
please,O
find,O
the,O
language,O
that,O
Mark,B-PERSON
&,O
I,O
propose,O
for,O
EnronOnline,O
Markets,O
page,O
as,O
well,O
each,O
commodity,O
"""home""",O
web,O
site.,O
Please,O
let,O
us,O
know,O
if,O
it,O
looks,O
like,O
such,O
is,O
going,O
to,O
be,O
limited,O
in,O
length,O
so,O
not,O
necessary,O
scroll,O
down,O
see,O
entire,O
page.,O
Your,O
company,O
should,O
enter,O
into,O
any,O
transaction,O
unless,O
fully,O
understands,O
potential,O
risks,O
and,O
rewards,O
of,O
has,O
independently,O
determined,O
appropriate,O
light,O
your,O
's,O
objectives,O
",",O
experience,O
financial,O
operational,O
resources,O
other,O
relevant,O
circumstances.,O
bear,O
mind,O
providing,O
this,O
site,O
Enron,B-ORG
acting,O
a,O
arm,O
counterparty,O
adviser.,O
For,O
further,O
information,O
Legal,O
Privacy,O
Information,O
[link,O
],O
Let,O
disclaimer,O
will,O
work.,O
Leslie,B-PERSON
Hi,O
Sara,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
need,O
to,O
reschedule,O
on,O
of,O
the,O
three,O
brokerage,O
account,O
meetings,O
that,O
are,O
my,O
calendar,O
for,O
tomorrow.,O
My,O
indicates,O
have,O
a,O
9,O
a.m.,O
one,O
hour,O
meeting,O
with,O
you,O
10,O
swaps,O
1,O
:30,O
2,O
credit,O
support,O
and,O
4,O
p.m.,O
someone,O
from,O
yet,O
another,O
Enron,B-ORG
entity,O
seeking,O
open,O
an,O
urgent,O
basis.,O
Keegan,B-PERSON
now,O
developed,O
strategy,O
ensure,O
we,O
do,O
not,O
so,O
many,O
day.,O
Most,O
other,O
group,O
therefore,O
possible,O
reschedule.,O
Cheryl,B-PERSON
Nelson,I-PERSON
Senior,O
Counsel,O
EB3816,O
(713,O
),O
345-4693,O
Type,O
of,O
Contract,O
:,O
ISDA,O
Master,O
Agreement,O
(Multicurrency-Cross,O
Border,O
),O
Effective,O
Date,O
September,O
1,O
",",O
2000,O
Enron,B-ORG
Entity,O
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
Counterparty,O
H.Q.,O
Energy,O
Services,O
(U.S.,O
Inc.,O
Transactions,O
Covered,O
Approved,O
for,O
all,O
products,O
with,O
the,O
exception,O
Foreign,O
Exchange,O
Confirming,O
Governing,O
Law,O
New,O
York,O
Special,O
Provisions,O
The,O
Confirmation,O
section,O
prescribes,O
using,O
form,O
confirmation,O
contained,O
in,O
Definitions,O
or,O
1993,O
Commodity,O
Definitions.,O
timing,O
dispute,O
confirmations,O
has,O
been,O
amended,O
from,O
standard,O
2,O
days,O
to,O
3,O
days.,O
Desk,O
note,O
p.28,O
Schedule,O
rounding,O
conventions.,O
On,O
Friday,B-DATE
we,O
will,O
be,O
receiving,O
the,O
remaining,O
customer,O
list,O
from,O
credit,O
",",O
due,O
to,O
timescales,O
I,O
am,O
asking,O
for,O
turnaround,O
on,O
matrix,O
and,O
master,O
agreement,O
review,O
by,O
end,O
of,O
play,O
Tuesday,B-DATE
12th,I-DATE
October.,O
Any,O
problems,O
with,O
this,O
please,O
notify,O
me,O
immediately,O
as,O
are,O
now,O
running,O
up,O
against,O
very,O
tight,O
deadlines,O
in,O
terms,O
getting,O
all,O
information,O
system,O
launch,O
schedule.,O
Thanks,O
Louise,B-PERSON
Mark,B-PERSON
another,O
note,O
requesting,O
a,O
blanket,O
decision,O
which,O
has,O
been,O
made,O
prevent,O
any,O
regulated,O
utility,O
completing,O
financial,O
transactions,O
if,O
not,O
prepared,O
do,O
diligence,O
ones,O
can,O
transact,O
-,O
is,O
our,O
responsibility,O
or,O
theirs,O
?,O
ie,O
their,O
whether,O
trade,O
not.,O
October,I-DATE
SB,O
1741,O
;,O
Telecommunications,O
:,O
technology,O
specific,O
area,O
codes,O
",",O
Author,O
Bowen,B-PERSON
Introduced,O
2,O
/23,O
/00,O
Sponsor,O
Summary,O
Currently,O
in,O
California,B-LOCATION
cannot,O
be,O
approved,O
based,O
on,O
technology.,O
This,O
bill,O
would,O
require,O
the,O
Public,B-ORG
Utilities,I-ORG
Commission,I-ORG
to,O
request,O
authority,O
from,O
Federal,B-ORG
Communications,I-ORG
telephone,O
corporations,O
establish,O
wireless,O
and,O
data,O
communications.,O
also,O
prohibit,O
approving,O
new,O
code,O
splits,O
or,O
overlays,O
unless,O
a,O
had,O
been,O
established,O
affected,O
further,O
relief,O
is,O
warranted.,O
Position,O
What,O
our,O
position,O
this,O
issue,O
?,O
Should,O
we,O
watch,O
Attached,O
bill.,O
"""Each",O
party,O
consents,O
to,O
the,O
recording,O
",",O
at,O
any,O
time,O
and,O
from,O
by,O
other,O
of,O
all,O
communications,O
between,O
officers,O
or,O
employees,O
parties,O
waives,O
further,O
notice,O
such,O
recording.,O
Additionally,O
in,O
absence,O
a,O
Confirmation,O
executed,O
both,O
may,O
be,O
submitted,O
evidence,O
court,O
proceedings,O
for,O
purpose,O
establishing,O
matters,O
pertinent,O
terms,O
"Transaction.""",O
Marty,B-PERSON
:,O
This,O
would,O
appear,O
Part,O
5,O
(f,O
),O
Schedule.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
this,O
is,O
acceptable.,O
I,O
'll,O
follow,O
up,O
with,O
Tanya,B-PERSON
on,O
Monday.,O
Per,O
the,O
attached,O
document,O
",",O
Angela,B-PERSON
Lewis,I-PERSON
a,O
representative,O
from,O
The,O
Japan,O
Partnership,O
an,O
international,O
executive,O
search,O
firm,O
will,O
be,O
in,O
area,O
at,O
5pm,O
on,O
Sunday,O
October,O
7th,O
and,O
is,O
interested,O
meeting,O
with,O
native,O
Japanese,O
graduating,O
Haas,B-ORG
students,O
to,O
discuss,O
career,O
opportunities,O
Japan.,O
If,O
you,O
are,O
attending,O
this,O
presentation,O
please,O
respond,O
back,O
me,O
right,O
away.,O
volume,O
of,I-ORG
responses,O
determine,O
whether,O
event,O
take,O
place,O
or,O
not.,O
It,O
scheduled,O
Faculty,O
Club.,O
Regards,O
Rich,B-PERSON
Wong,I-PERSON
Account,O
Manager,O
Technology,O
&,O
Entertainment,O
MBA,O
Recruiting,O
School,I-ORG
Business,I-ORG
Career,I-ORG
Center,I-ORG
545,O
Student,O
Services,O
Building,O
#1900,O
Berkeley,O
CA,O
94720-1900,O
ph,O
:,O
510-643-4211,O
fax,O
510-643-5257,O
email,O
:rwong,O
@haas.berkeley.edu,O
Message,O
sent,O
from,O
the,O
pjm-customer-info,O
mailing,O
list,O
at,O
@majordomo.pjm.com,O
:,O
In,O
response,O
to,O
customer,O
feedback,O
and,O
in,O
order,O
make,O
our,O
website,O
more,O
user,O
friendly,O
",",O
PJM,B-ORG
will,O
add,O
buttons,O
for,O
widely,O
used,O
eTools,O
home,O
page.,O
The,O
button,O
be,O
located,O
just,O
under,O
weather,O
maps,O
eliminate,O
's,O
need,O
scroll,O
or,O
multiple,O
clicks,O
reach,O
suite,O
of,O
eTools.,O
entire,O
continue,O
accessible,O
via,O
"""Business",O
"eTools""",O
link,O
on,O
navigational,O
bar.,O
new,O
should,O
available,O
Thursday,O
12,O
/14,O
/00,O
approximately,O
3,O
:00PM.,O
Please,O
DO,O
NOT,O
REPLY,O
this,O
message.,O
If,O
you,O
have,O
a,O
question,O
Customer,O
Relations,O
Training,O
please,O
complete,O
submit,O
form,O
http,O
/,O
/www.pjm.com,O
/contact,O
/questions.html,O
To,O
unsubscribe,O
send,O
an,O
e-mail,O
majordomo,O
containing,O
only,O
following,O
line,O
body,O
Dear,O
Mr.,O
LARRY,B-PERSON
CAMPBELL,I-PERSON
:,O
Thank,O
you,O
for,O
your,O
order.,O
You,O
bought,O
70,O
shares,O
of,O
CIEN,B-ORG
(Ciena,O
Corp,I-ORG
Com,I-ORG
),O
at,O
113.430000.,O
ORDER,O
DETAILS,O
The,O
tracking,O
number,O
this,O
order,O
is,O
B-600-AASF-8733,O
Order,O
entered,O
10,O
:33,O
:00,O
on,O
11,O
/03,O
/00,O
processing,O
began,O
:01,O
executed,O
ACCOUNT,O
Time,O
and,O
Date,O
Your,O
position,O
in,O
real,O
cash,O
total,O
$-28,O
",527.00",O
will,O
receive,O
a,O
printed,O
Datek,B-ORG
Online,I-ORG
confirmation,O
by,O
postal,O
mail,O
",",O
or,O
electronic,O
delivery,O
if,O
are,O
subscribed,O
to,O
that,O
service.,O
Questions,O
regarding,O
transaction,O
?,O
Contact,O
our,O
Customer,O
Support,O
department,O
e-mailing,O
support,O
@datek.com.,O
Please,O
reference,O
the,O
number.,O
Ciena,B-ORG
Jerald,B-PERSON
Surface,I-PERSON
will,O
be,O
in,O
Portland,B-LOCATION
(from,O
Houston,B-LOCATION
),O
to,O
interview,O
for,O
a,O
position,O
Real,O
Time.,O
I,O
provide,O
copy,O
of,O
his,O
resume,O
interviews,O
review.,O
See,O
below,O
schedule,O
and,O
location,O
:,O
",",O
Cascade,B-LOCATION
Conference,I-LOCATION
Room,I-LOCATION
Thursday,O
July,O
5th,O
2001,O
11,O
:30am,O
-,O
Chris,B-PERSON
Mallory,I-PERSON
12,O
:15pm,O
Greg,B-PERSON
Wolfe,I-PERSON
1,O
:00pm,O
Stewart,B-PERSON
Rosman,I-PERSON
:45pm,O
Amy,B-PERSON
FitzPatrick,I-PERSON
Mt.,B-LOCATION
Rainier,I-LOCATION
Friday,O
6th,O
9,O
:15am,O
Bill,B-PERSON
Williams,I-PERSON
III,I-PERSON
10,O
:00am,O
Ryan,B-PERSON
Slinger,I-PERSON
Each,O
has,O
been,O
45,O
minutes.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions.,O
Thanks,O
Grace,B-PERSON
x8321,O
Sara-,O
I,O
am,O
sorry,O
to,O
hear,O
Frank,B-PERSON
has,O
left..,O
have,O
you,O
spoken,O
him,O
",",O
is,O
he,O
OK,O
?,O
How,O
are,O
doing,O
Can,O
please,O
tell,O
me,O
how,O
dealing,O
with,O
counterparties,O
who,O
still,O
exposure,O
Enron,B-ORG
know,O
all,O
contracts,O
null,O
and,O
void..,O
what,O
the,O
process,O
for,O
them,O
take,O
off,O
deals.,O
The,O
only,O
any,O
:,O
tudor,B-ORG
wexford,B-ORG
asking,O
specifically.,O
Also,O
on,O
monies,O
we,O
owe,O
counterparties..,O
like,O
catequil,B-ORG
they,O
must,O
go,O
through,O
Thanks,O
very,O
much,O
Caroline,B-PERSON
cell-,O
917,O
324,O
1999,O
home-,O
212,O
737,O
2082,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Per,O
our,O
discussions,O
yesterday,O
",",O
the,O
following,O
should,O
hopefully,O
be,O
completed,O
before,O
2,O
:30,O
(CST,O
),O
conference,O
call,O
on,O
Recoupment,O
and,O
4,O
:00,O
PX,O
Credit,O
&,O
1c,O
/kwh,O
Surcharge.,O
1.,O
Bob,B-PERSON
Williams,I-PERSON
-,O
Synopsis,O
of,O
Surcharge,O
2.,O
Sue,B-PERSON
Mara,I-PERSON
Background,O
CPUC,B-ORG
Activity,O
(to,O
included,O
in,O
',O
write-up,O
3.,O
Dian,B-PERSON
Huddleson,I-PERSON
Plan,O
for,O
Requesting,O
Net,O
Bill,O
Reinstatement,O
4.,O
URM,B-PERSON
Analysis,O
Methodology,O
5.,O
Mary,B-PERSON
Lynne,I-PERSON
Ruffer,I-PERSON
Amounts,O
6.,O
Jim,B-PERSON
Steffes,I-PERSON
Legal,O
The,O
goal,O
today,O
is,O
to,O
have,O
all,O
necessary,O
data,O
develop,O
recommendations,O
how,O
proceed,O
these,O
matters,O
so,O
that,O
we,O
can,O
meet,O
with,O
business,O
heads,O
tomorrow.,O
Call,O
In,O
Information,O
1-800-998-2462,O
#,O
5462908,O
To,O
Be,O
Provided,O
By,O
Linda,B-PERSON
Noske,I-PERSON
Kay,B-PERSON
please,O
forward,O
to,O
Max,B-PERSON
Yzaguirre.,O
",",O
congrats,O
on,O
the,O
Decero,B-ORG
PPA,O
-,O
we,O
need,O
wrestle,O
up,O
another,O
100,O
200,O
MW.,O
This,O
should,O
be,O
a,O
priority,O
given,O
profit,O
potential,O
of,O
this,O
deal,O
as,O
per,O
Oz,B-PERSON
and,O
Doug,B-PERSON
(+50M,O
in,B-DATE
2000,I-DATE
).,O
Is,O
there,O
an,O
ability,O
let,O
Sabine,B-PERSON
or,O
Irvin,B-PERSON
run,O
with,O
Vitro,B-ORG
get,O
your,O
attention,O
item,O
asap.,O
I,O
know,O
that,O
Monterrey,B-LOCATION
project,O
is,O
eating,O
into,O
time.,O
Do,O
augment,O
resources,O
?,O
On,O
different,O
note,O
current,O
control,O
budget,O
showing,O
$5.3M,O
negative,O
variance,O
from,O
original,O
budget.,O
accurate,O
Does,O
reduce,O
profitability,O
it,O
absorbed,O
by,O
's,O
Regards,O
Delainey,B-PERSON
Yzaguirre,I-PERSON
FYI.,O
?,O
SoCalGas,B-ORG
',O
response,O
to,O
protests,O
AL2966.,O
Received,O
:,O
from,O
dymwsm06.mailwatch.com,B-ORG
by,O
ArterHadden.com,B-ORG
;,O
Tue,O
",",O
07,O
Nov,O
2000,O
10,O
:54,O
:19,O
-0500,O
dymw0125.mailwatch.com,B-ORG
(dymw0125.allegro.net,O
[204.253.83.81,O
],O
),O
(8.11.0,O
/8.11.0,O
with,O
SMTP,O
id,O
eA7FsbW02410,O
for,O
7,O
:37,O
204.253.83.72,O
(,O
WorldSecure,O
Server,O
Relay,O
(WSS,O
v4.3,O
00,O
:51,O
:53,O
X-Server-Uuid,O
8014d96c-8cb5-11d4-814d-00508bd934cf,O
mail1.sempra.com,B-ORG
(mail1.sempra.com,O
[4.21.3.129,O
dymwsm10.mailwatch.com,B-ORG
ESMTP,O
eA7Fpph12200,O
(localhost,O
[127.0.0.1,O
(Microsoft,O
Exchange,O
Internet,O
Mail,O
Service,O
Version,O
5.5.2650.21,O
WGWCN70F,O
:50,O
:43,O
-0800,O
4.21.3.3,O
(InterScan,O
E-Mail,I-ORG
VirusWall,I-ORG
NT,I-ORG
:34,O
(Pacific,O
Standard,O
Time,O
ex-socal-c01.pacent.com,B-ORG
:47,O
Message-ID,O
AL2966,B-ORG
InterScan,B-ORG
To,O
member,O
:,O
dvdexpress,B-PERSON
From,O
shig4413,B-PERSON
There,O
's,O
a,O
dutch,O
auction,O
going,O
on,O
for,O
these,O
items.,O
Find,O
by,O
using,O
Enron,O
Cube.,O
Auction,O
is,O
at,O
$23,O
right,O
now.,O
This,O
email,O
was,O
sent,O
an,O
eBay,B-ORG
via,O
forwarding,O
system.,O
If,O
you,O
reply,O
to,O
the,O
",",O
your,O
response,O
will,O
go,O
directly,O
and,O
not,O
through,O
eBay.,O
does,O
tolerate,O
spam,O
(i.e.,O
unsolicited,O
commercial,O
),O
taking,O
steps,O
protect,O
members,O
from,O
this,O
abuse.,O
In,O
addition,O
solicitations,O
buy,O
or,O
sell,O
items,O
outside,O
of,O
violate,O
rules,O
are,O
covered,O
services,O
that,O
such,O
as,O
feedback,O
insurance,O
escrow,O
dispute,O
resolution.,O
offer,O
/sell,O
please,O
do,O
participate.,O
Enter,O
following,O
link,O
into,O
browser,O
learn,O
more.,O
Link,O
http,O
/,O
/pages.digitalcity.ebay.com,O
/help,O
/emailinfo.html,O
Bill-,O
Two,O
files,O
are,O
attached.,O
The,O
first,O
file,O
is,O
the,O
text,O
and,O
figures,O
of,O
a,O
plan,O
for,O
characterizing,O
impacted,O
soil,O
in,O
former,O
surface,O
impoundment,O
areas.,O
second,O
contains,O
attachments,O
to,O
characterization,O
plan.,O
include,O
copies,O
boring,O
logs,O
summary,O
some,O
previous,O
sample,O
results.,O
I,O
will,O
also,O
send,O
two,O
hard,O
you,O
via,O
FedEx.,O
Transwestern,O
ready,O
proceed,O
upon,O
approval,O
from,O
NMOCD,O
NMED,O
HRMB.,O
Please,O
call,O
me,O
if,O
have,O
any,O
questions,O
or,O
comments.,O
Thanks,O
",",O
George,B-PERSON
C.,I-PERSON
Robinson,I-PERSON
PE,O
Contract,O
Environmental,O
Engineer,O
Cypress,B-ORG
Engineering,I-ORG
ENRON,B-ORG
Office,O
:,O
(713,O
),O
646-7327,O
email,O
george.robinson,O
@enron.com,O
Bill,B-PERSON
Hi,O
",",O
Dana,B-PERSON
:,O
We,O
have,O
received,O
the,O
original,O
copy,O
of,O
ISDA,O
Master,O
Agreement.,O
In,O
looking,O
through,O
supporting,O
documents,O
we,O
noted,O
two,O
outstanding,O
items,O
1.,O
did,O
not,O
receive,O
an,O
signed,O
IRS,O
Tax,O
Form,O
W-9,O
as,O
required,O
pursuant,O
to,O
Part,O
3,O
(a,O
),O
;,O
and,O
2.,O
The,O
Certificate,O
Incumbency,O
was,O
dated,O
November,O
14,O
2000.,O
would,O
like,O
certificate,O
a,O
current,O
date.,O
If,O
you,O
any,O
questions,O
please,O
do,O
hesitate,O
contact,O
either,O
Frank,B-PERSON
or,O
me.,O
look,O
forward,O
receiving,O
this,O
documentation.,O
Marie,B-PERSON
Heard,I-PERSON
Senior,O
Legal,O
Specialist,O
Enron,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
Phone,O
(713,O
853-3907,O
Fax,O
646-3490,O
marie.heard,O
@enron.com,O
Richter,B-PERSON
reserved,O
that,O
last,O
year.,O
He,O
made,O
the,O
money.,O
It,O
's,O
his.,O
goes,O
against,O
refund,O
risk,O
in,O
California.,O
If,O
we,O
take,O
a,O
hit,O
CA,O
due,O
to,O
refunds,O
",",O
should,O
eat,O
good,O
chunk,O
of,O
if,O
there,O
is,O
extra,O
money,O
then,O
he,O
keep,O
it.,O
John,B-PERSON
has,O
asked,O
me,O
do,O
thorough,O
review,O
our,O
Schedule,O
C,O
reserves,O
light,O
northwest,O
decision,O
BPA,B-ORG
new,O
contracts,O
started,O
October,O
and,O
overall,O
lower,O
price,O
environment.,O
will,O
be,O
part,O
this,O
bigger,O
effort,O
I,O
get,O
done,O
week.,O
Let,O
know,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions.,O
My,O
dear,O
compadres,O
",",O
We,O
are,O
a,O
month,O
away,O
from,B-DATE
our,O
trip,O
to,I-DATE
the,I-DATE
beautiful,O
Lake,B-LOCATION
Tahoe.,O
Here,O
is,O
link,O
house,O
we,O
have,O
reserved.,O
As,O
repeat,O
offender,O
get,O
price,O
break,O
and,O
it,O
going,O
be,O
$198.00,O
for,O
March,I-DATE
8th,I-DATE
13th,I-DATE
ten,O
people.,O
http,O
:,O
/,O
/www.tahoevacationguide.com,O
/LTRB,O
/Homes,O
/2240E.html,O
So,O
I,O
currently,O
Michael,B-PERSON
W.,I-PERSON
Mark,B-PERSON
M.,I-PERSON
Virginia,B-PERSON
H.,I-PERSON
Friend.,O
Patricia,B-PERSON
David,B-PERSON
?,O
Gerald,B-PERSON
Let,O
me,O
know,O
!,O
Have,O
great,O
weekend,O
Thanks,O
Cuero,I-PERSON
Bus,O
Ops,O
Program,O
Manager,O
(512,O
),O
723-6977,O
(800,O
289-3355,O
ext.,O
36977,O
728-3653,O
fax,O
"""The",O
only,O
limits,O
on,O
what,O
you,O
can,O
accomplish,O
place,O
your,O
own,O
"imagination.""",O
Tahoe,I-LOCATION
Hello,O
All-,O
I,O
wanted,O
to,O
let,O
you,O
know,O
that,O
",",O
as,O
of,O
July,B-DATE
1,I-DATE
Jan,B-PERSON
Haizmann,I-PERSON
's,O
responsibilities,O
will,O
expand,O
include,O
competition,O
issues,O
in,O
European,O
energy,O
markets.,O
As,O
addition,O
his,O
work,O
for,O
EBS,B-ORG
Europe,B-LOCATION
has,O
been,O
spending,O
considerable,O
time,O
directing,O
',O
government,O
affairs,O
Asia.,O
Due,O
large,O
part,O
the,O
progress,O
he,O
made,O
we,O
are,O
now,O
able,O
shift,O
effort,O
an,O
individual,O
region,O
until,O
a,O
new,O
hire,O
is,O
on,O
board,O
Singapore.,O
continue,O
spend,O
approximately,O
half,O
Europe.,O
The,O
remainder,O
which,O
previously,O
was,O
spent,O
Asia,B-LOCATION
be,O
Please,O
feel,O
free,O
call,O
me,O
if,O
have,O
any,O
questions.,O
Regards,O
Sue,B-PERSON
Nord,I-PERSON
Sr.,O
Director,O
Government,O
Affairs,O
713,O
345-4196,O
Singapore,B-LOCATION
Melissa,B-PERSON
:,O
Before,O
I,O
can,O
respond,O
",",O
need,O
to,O
know,O
the,O
following,O
answers,O
(1,O
),O
What,O
is,O
Exercise,O
Period,O
(Commencement,O
/Expiration,O
Dates,O
for,O
swaption,O
and,O
during,O
what,O
hours,O
we,O
exercise,O
?,O
Is,O
it,O
from,O
Jan.,O
2,O
-,O
Feb,O
28,O
2001,O
9,O
am,O
11,O
New,B-LOCATION
York,I-LOCATION
time,O
(2,O
Commencement,O
Date,O
also,O
Premium,O
Payment,O
(3,O
For,O
early,O
termination,O
purposes,O
there,O
just,O
a,O
single,O
Optional,O
Early,O
Termination,O
or,O
period,O
of,O
(4,O
Did,O
want,O
specify,O
any,O
Cash,O
Settlement,O
Reference,O
Banks,O
mark,O
this,O
confirm,O
quickly,O
when,O
hear,O
you.,O
Thanks.,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Shackleton,I-PERSON
Enron,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
1400,O
Smith,O
Street,O
EB,O
3801a,O
Houston,O
Texas,O
77002,O
713-853-5620,O
(phone,O
713-646-3490,O
(fax,O
sara.shackleton,O
@enron.com,O
Rodriguez,O
All,O
We,O
had,O
2,O
service,O
outages,O
today,O
",",O
the,O
External,O
Internet,O
and,O
Email,O
both,O
became,O
unavailable,O
at,O
about,O
11,O
:00,O
am,O
was,O
restored,O
in,O
after,O
15-20,O
minutes.,O
The,O
fact,O
that,O
services,O
went,O
down,O
same,O
time,O
is,O
only,O
coincidence.,O
Below,O
are,O
basic,O
causes,O
for,O
:,O
outage,O
caused,O
by,O
an,O
error,O
one,O
of,O
our,O
Network,O
Routers.,O
device,O
rebooted,O
restored.,O
a,O
bug,O
Exchange,O
remedied,O
rebooting,O
server.,O
Sorry,O
inconvenience,O
these,O
may,O
have,O
caused.,O
Dave,B-PERSON
Steiner,I-PERSON
Hi,O
Sylvia,B-PERSON
",",O
Re,O
the,O
GISB,O
for,O
Wisconsin,B-LOCATION
no,O
we,O
would,O
not,O
agree,O
to,O
terms,O
of,O
their,O
on,O
front,O
page,O
or,O
special,O
provisions.,O
Are,O
you,O
aware,O
currently,O
have,O
a,O
in,O
place,O
with,O
Public,I-LOCATION
Service,I-LOCATION
Company,I-LOCATION
and,O
ENA,B-LOCATION
as,O
well,O
Gas,I-LOCATION
?,O
Master,O
Status,O
:,O
I,O
devoted,O
my,O
afternoon,O
this,O
contract,O
order,O
complete,O
redline.,O
Will,O
keep,O
apprised.,O
Do,O
still,O
want,O
copy,O
our,O
GISB.,O
If,O
so,O
will,O
send,O
draft,O
however,O
need,O
fill,O
name,O
counterparty,O
etc.,O
before,O
it,O
goes,O
out.,O
Debra,B-PERSON
Perlingiere,I-PERSON
Enron,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
Legal,O
Department,O
1400,O
Smith,O
Street,O
EB,O
3885,O
Houston,O
Texas,O
77002,O
dperlin,O
@enron.com,O
Phone,O
713-853-7658,O
Fax,O
713-646-3490,O
State,O
Treasurer,O
Barbara,B-PERSON
Hafer,I-PERSON
reveals,O
that,O
about,O
$300,O
",000",O
was,O
fraudulently,O
removed,O
from,O
the,I-ORG
state,O
's,O
treasury,O
",",O
in,O
what,O
she,O
is,O
terming,O
'economic,O
terrorism,O
',O
on,I-ORG
Pennsylvania,B-ORG
Newsmakers.,O
10,O
?,O
minutes,O
The,B-ORG
interview,O
can,O
be,O
heard,O
by,O
clicking,O
one,O
of,O
links,O
below.,O
http,O
:,O
/,O
/www.jerrybowyer.com,O
/audio.php,O
?id0,O
for,O
RealPlayer,O
?id1,O
Windows,O
Media,O
Player,O
Feel,O
free,O
to,O
share,O
this,O
information,O
with,O
anyone,O
your,O
list,O
or,O
who,O
may,O
interested.,O
To,O
listen,O
other,O
Jerry,I-ORG
Bowyer,I-ORG
interviews,O
Program,I-ORG
Newsmakers,I-ORG
Focus,B-ORG
Issues,I-ORG
visit,O
www.jerrybowyer.com,O
/audio.php.,O
Thanks,O
listening.,O
Newsmakersseen,O
across,O
these,O
television,O
stations,O
/coveragemap.php,O
Programon,O
WPTT,O
radio,O
Pittsburgh,O
1360am,O
www.1360wptt.com,O
/bowyer,O
Issueson,O
Cornerstone,B-ORG
Television,I-ORG
Audio,O
clips,O
programs,O
at,O
412.771.2282,O
phone,O
412.771.2363,O
faxjerrybowyer,O
@home.com,O
Below,O
is,O
the,O
file,O
containing,O
Flex,O
Dollar,O
amounts,O
and,O
Benefit,O
Rates,O
to,O
be,O
used,O
in,O
preparing,O
your,O
Business,O
Unit,O
's,O
2002,O
Plan.,O
I,O
have,O
also,O
included,O
flat,O
rates,O
for,O
Analyst,O
Associate,O
Program.,O
Beginning,O
June,B-DATE
2001,I-DATE
",",O
Program,O
began,O
billing,O
fees,O
GL,O
account,O
-,O
52503000,O
Allocations,O
Other.,O
A,O
new,O
52502600,O
&,O
will,O
set,O
up,O
should,O
plan,O
next,O
year.,O
PLEASE,O
NOTE,O
:,O
If,O
you,O
any,O
reports,O
cost,O
element,O
groups,O
or,O
spreadsheets,O
that,O
use,O
a,O
listing,O
of,O
accounts,O
need,O
update,O
them,O
include,O
account.,O
$10,O
",400",O
3rd,O
Yr.,O
$7,O
$6,O
Tax,O
$2,O
Summer,O
$3,O
",300",O
Associates,O
",000",O
Please,O
fee,O
free,O
call,O
me,O
if,O
questions.,O
Dawn,B-PERSON
Derr,I-PERSON
37775,O
Dear,O
Power,O
Outage,O
Database,O
Customer,O
",",O
Attached,O
you,O
will,O
find,O
an,O
excel,O
document.,O
The,O
outage,O
contained,O
within,O
is,O
a,O
rescheduled,O
outage.,O
Your,O
daily,O
delivery,O
still,O
contain,O
this,O
In,O
addition,O
to,O
the,O
document,O
there,O
dbf,O
file,O
that,O
formatted,O
like,O
your,O
receive,O
nightly.,O
This,O
enable,O
load,O
data,O
into,O
regular,O
database.,O
Any,O
questions,O
please,O
let,O
me,O
know.,O
Thanks.,O
Greg,B-PERSON
Elliott,I-PERSON
IIR,O
Inc.,O
713-783-5147,O
x,O
3481,O
outages,O
@industrialinfo.com,O
THE,O
INFORMATION,O
CONTAINED,O
IN,O
THIS,O
E-MAIL,O
IS,O
LEGALLY,O
PRIVILEGED,O
AND,O
CONFIDENTIAL,O
INTENDED,O
ONLY,O
FOR,O
USE,O
OF,O
INDIVIDUAL,O
OR,O
ENTITY,O
NAMED,O
ABOVE.,O
YOU,O
ARE,O
HEREBY,O
NOTIFIED,O
THAT,O
ANY,O
DISSEMINATION,O
DISTRIBUTION,O
COPY,O
TO,O
UNAUTHORIZED,O
ENTITIES,O
STRICTLY,O
PROHIBITED.,O
IF,O
HAVE,O
RECEIVED,O
ERROR,O
PLEASE,O
DELETE,O
IT.,O
-,O
OUTAGE.dbf,O
112001R.xls,O
Leon,B-PERSON
",",O
the,O
account,O
number,O
in,O
original,O
document,O
is,O
actually,O
not,O
incorrect.,O
This,O
was,O
to,O
which,O
funds,O
were,O
have,O
been,O
deposited,O
to.,O
However,O
SCE,B-ORG
a,O
different,O
account.,O
As,O
result,O
I,O
agree,O
that,O
we,O
should,O
amend,O
reflect,O
where,O
these,O
they,O
ere,O
sent,O
and,O
this,O
will,O
conclude,O
our,O
busines.,O
Your,O
file,O
did,O
come,O
over,O
correctly,O
but,O
if,O
you,O
could,O
hand,O
correct,O
documents,O
by,O
changing,O
banking,O
instructions,O
fax,O
me,O
i,O
provide,O
proper,O
signatures,O
on,O
amendment,O
are,O
done.,O
Thanks.,O
Barry,B-PERSON
Tycholiz,I-PERSON
713-646-2391,O
(Fax,O
),O
713-853-1587,O
(Phone,O
Effective,O
2,O
/2,O
/01,O
",",O
please,O
change,O
my,O
receipt,O
MDQ,O
's,O
for,O
contract,O
25841,O
as,O
follows,O
:,O
Meter,O
#,O
OLD,O
NEW,O
GPM,O
Artesia,O
10703,O
22800,O
West,O
Pool,O
58646,O
546,O
5296,O
Central,O
58649,O
8830,O
4080,O
NGPL,O
Winkler,O
52862,O
7824,O
TOTAL,O
40000,O
Thanks,O
Jody,B-PERSON
Oberman,I-PERSON
(301,O
),O
280-6184,O
PG,O
&E,O
National,O
Energy,O
Group,O
and,I-ORG
any,O
other,O
company,O
referenced,O
herein,O
that,O
uses,O
the,O
name,O
or,O
logo,O
are,O
not,O
same,O
Pacific,B-ORG
Gas,I-ORG
Electric,I-ORG
Company,I-ORG
regulated,O
California,O
utility.,O
Neither,O
nor,O
these,O
companies,O
by,O
Public,O
Utilities,O
Commission.,O
Customers,O
of,O
do,O
have,O
to,O
buy,O
products,O
from,O
in,O
order,O
continue,O
receive,O
quality,O
services,O
paperloop.com,O
BRUSSELS,B-LOCATION
",",O
July,B-DATE
18,O
2001,O
(paperloop.com,O
),O
-,O
Frantschach,B-ORG
Pulp,I-ORG
and,I-ORG
Paper,I-ORG
has,O
ordered,O
an,O
automatic,O
chip,O
storage,O
reclaiming,O
system,O
for,O
its,O
two,O
pulp,O
lines,O
at,O
the,O
Steti,B-LOCATION
plant,O
in,O
Czech,B-LOCATION
Republic.,O
The,O
revamp,O
will,O
be,O
implemented,O
stages,O
to,O
avoid,O
a,O
shutdown.,O
first,O
phase,O
of,O
upgrade,O
completed,O
February,B-DATE
2002,I-DATE
final,O
work,O
wrapped,O
up,O
2002.,O
A,O
spokesman,O
said,O
mill,O
produces,O
250,O
",000",O
tonnes,O
/yr,O
bleached,O
unbleached,O
kraft,O
pulp.,O
new,O
enhance,O
safety,O
product,O
quality.,O
's,O
paper,O
200,O
sack,O
machine-glazed,O
(MG,O
wrapping,O
linerboard.,O
PM,O
is,O
also,O
planned,O
next,B-DATE
year.,O
unit,O
12,O
capacity,O
MG,O
set,O
gradually,O
rise,O
31,O
following,O
upgrade.,O
year,I-DATE
Republic,I-LOCATION
Daren,B-PERSON
I,O
have,O
three,O
meters,O
that,O
flow,O
in,O
Feb,B-DATE
but,O
no,O
deal.,O
1.,O
Meter,O
0416,O
flowed,O
the,O
whole,O
month,O
1-28.,O
This,O
our,O
ols,O
friends,O
at,O
Pawnee,B-ORG
gas,I-ORG
plant,I-ORG
fuel.,O
Last,O
deal,O
used,O
was,O
289396,O
could,O
you,O
extend,O
it.,O
2.,O
meter,O
1601,O
had,O
on,O
15,O
&18.,O
is,O
Southern,B-ORG
union,I-ORG
Lockhart.,O
with,O
them,O
285350,O
Hpl,O
or,O
259208,O
ENA.,O
3.,O
1598,O
MT,O
Enterprise,O
C,O
/G-,O
Panther.,O
The,O
last,O
284,O
620,O
'll,O
get,O
Accounting,O
Arrangements,O
for,O
these,O
when,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
status,O
and,O
cleared,O
up.,O
Thanks.,O
1-28,B-DATE
fuel,I-ORG
Lockhart,I-ORG
The,O
party,O
is,O
fast,O
approaching,O
and,O
the,O
number,O
of,O
prizes,O
I,O
have,O
received,O
from,O
deputies,O
16.,O
We,O
would,O
like,O
to,O
100.,O
Some,O
you,O
indicated,O
that,O
collected,O
so,O
even,O
if,O
can,O
't,O
send,O
me,O
this,O
week,O
please,O
e-mail,O
or,O
phone,O
with,O
following,O
information,O
:,O
your,O
name,O
prize,O
description,O
approximate,O
value,O
donor,O
THIS,B-DATE
INFORMATION,O
MUST,O
BE,O
RECEIVED,O
BY,O
FRIDAY,I-DATE
TO,O
PUBLISHED,O
IN,O
THE,O
BROCHURE.,O
Please,O
responses,O
at,O
maggietimmins,O
@cdnoxy.com,O
call,O
260-3441.,O
look,O
forward,O
hearing,O
about,O
fabulous,O
!,O
Thanks,O
very,O
much.,O
Maggie,B-PERSON
Timmins,I-PERSON
CXY,B-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
Marketing,I-ORG
Phone,O
(403,O
),O
260-3441,O
Fax,O
237-8266,O
-,O
att1.htm,O
Hey,O
all,O
",",O
Sunday,O
is,O
Shanna,B-PERSON
's,O
30th,O
B-day,O
so,O
we,O
are,O
going,O
to,O
celebrate,O
Saturday,O
night.,O
We,O
were,O
planning,O
on,O
meeting,O
up,O
at,O
my,O
new,O
place,O
for,O
drinks,O
@,O
around,O
9,O
:00,O
and,O
then,O
heading,O
over,O
the,O
Black,B-ORG
Swan,I-ORG
10,O
:30.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
care,O
join.,O
My,O
Gables,O
Pin,O
Oak,O
Park,O
-,O
4848,O
#1503.,O
Directions,O
from,O
Downtown,B-LOCATION
take,O
59,O
south,O
exit,O
Newcastle,O
a,O
left,O
follow,O
past,O
Westpark,O
about,O
quarter,O
mile,O
.,O
You,O
will,O
see,O
several,O
complexes,O
ahead.,O
Take,O
right,O
Park.,O
Complex,O
be,O
right.,O
Call,O
cell,O
phone,O
have,O
problems,O
713-628-3104.,O
can,O
come.,O
-Eric,O
Eric,B-PERSON
Hi,O
Sara,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
have,O
completed,O
a,O
preliminary,O
legal,O
review,O
of,O
the,O
Account,O
Agreements,O
with,O
Goldman,B-PERSON
Sachs,I-PERSON
and,O
Morgan,B-PERSON
Stanley.,O
read,O
draft,O
language,O
you,O
sent,O
re,O
:,O
limitation,O
liability,O
that,O
suggested,O
we,O
add,O
to,O
these,O
Bear,B-PERSON
Stearns,I-PERSON
agreements,O
for,O
Enron,B-PERSON
Credit,I-PERSON
Inc.,O
Because,O
arbitration,O
clauses,O
this,O
provision,O
as,O
drafted,O
might,O
be,O
unenforceable,O
under,O
NASD,B-ORG
rules.,O
am,O
going,O
doublecheck,O
law,O
on,O
point,O
today,O
or,O
over,O
weekend.,O
If,O
is,O
in,O
fact,O
correct,O
firms,O
will,O
probably,O
reject,O
ground,O
especailly,O
if,O
including,O
it,O
would,O
subject,O
them,O
fines.,O
In,O
any,O
case,O
can,O
wait,O
see,O
what,O
there,O
response,O
but,O
meantime,O
should,O
set,O
aside,O
time,O
discuss,O
point.,O
Cheryl,B-PERSON
Nelson,I-PERSON
Senior,O
Counsel,O
EB3880D,O
(713,O
),O
345-4693,O
Stanley,I-PERSON
Rick,B-PERSON
",",O
Attached,O
are,O
a,O
clean,O
copy,O
of,O
suggested,O
modification,O
the,O
body,O
this,O
DASH,O
as,O
well,O
original,O
DASH.,O
This,O
should,O
give,O
you,O
some,O
sense,O
Arcos,O
project,O
's,O
scale,O
and,O
risks.,O
John,B-PERSON
Sherriff,I-PERSON
Michael,B-PERSON
Brown,I-PERSON
reportedly,O
remain,O
confident,O
that,O
can,O
be,O
sold,O
at,O
profit,O
in,O
next,B-DATE
three,I-DATE
to,I-DATE
nine,I-DATE
months,I-DATE
;,O
however,O
if,O
it,O
is,O
not,O
our,O
economics,O
on,O
with,O
current,O
termination,O
cost,O
over,O
$200,O
million,O
negative,O
NPV,O
approximately,O
(,O
$150,O
).,O
The,O
Enron,B-ORG
board,O
has,O
seen,O
largely,O
because,O
turbine,O
specifically,O
related,O
but,O
no,O
other,O
use,O
turbines,O
been,O
identified,O
so,O
represents,O
huge,O
potential,O
loss,O
sale,O
successful.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
would,O
like,O
discuss,O
further.,O
Regards,O
Dave,B-PERSON
The,O
Griffith,B-PERSON
plant,O
is,O
currently,O
down,O
and,O
will,O
probably,O
be,O
for,O
the,O
rest,O
of,O
month.,O
I,O
have,O
put,O
a,O
zero,O
capacity,O
in,O
CAS,O
deliveries,O
through,O
10,O
/31,O
/01.,O
If,O
it,O
should,O
come,O
up,O
allocation,O
please,O
analyze,O
whether,O
due,O
to,O
flow,O
rate.,O
As,O
long,O
as,O
schedules,O
",",O
we,O
are,O
fine,O
you,O
can,O
ignore,O
contracts,O
which,O
scheduling,O
there,O
must,O
balanced,O
at,O
if,O
allocate,O
because,O
rate,O
system,O
generates,O
may,O
on,O
an,O
imbalance,O
next,O
morning,O
order,O
get,O
balance.,O
any,O
questions,O
while,O
allocating,O
ask,O
me.,O
Thanks,O
your,O
help,O
this,O
matter,O
Amy,B-PERSON
Attached,O
for,O
your,O
approval,O
is,O
the,O
form,O
of,O
Enron,B-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
Guaranty,O
in,O
favor,O
Engage,O
Energy,O
US,O
",",O
L.P.,O
now,O
known,O
as,O
Coastal,O
Merchant,O
which,O
guarantees,O
obligations,O
ENA,B-ORG
under,O
an,O
ISDA,B-ORG
Master,I-ORG
Agreement.,O
We,O
will,O
need,O
standard,O
executed,O
copy.,O
This,O
guaranty,O
supersede,O
and,O
replace,O
part,O
prior,O
with,O
respect,O
to,O
Counterparty.,O
The,O
be,O
fully,O
replaced,O
when,O
counterparty,O
receives,O
new,O
Canada,I-ORG
(still,O
covered,O
existing,O
such,O
replacement,O
still,O
negotiation,O
).,O
Upon,O
execution,O
please,O
call,O
me,O
at,O
x33399,O
pick,O
up,O
documents.,O
Thank,O
you,O
assistance,O
this,O
matter.,O
Agreement,I-ORG
Mr.,B-PERSON
Lay,I-PERSON
",",O
I,O
understand,O
that,O
we,O
may,O
not,O
be,O
having,O
the,O
holiday,O
party.,O
think,O
this,O
would,O
a,O
huge,O
mistake,O
!,O
We,O
have,O
worked,O
hard,O
all,O
year,O
and,O
recently,O
haven,O
't,O
had,O
much,O
to,O
celebrate.,O
know,O
alot,O
of,O
women,O
(myself,O
included,O
),O
who,O
already,O
bought,O
their,O
dresses.,O
could,O
our,O
Enron,B-ORG
Swan,O
Song,O
go,O
out,O
with,O
bang,O
what,O
you,O
did,O
about,O
your,O
bonus,O
was,O
most,O
unselfish,O
thing,O
man,O
in,O
position,O
do.,O
been,O
honored,O
work,O
for,O
caliber.,O
hope,O
my,O
next,O
CEO,O
can,O
live,O
up,O
very,O
high,O
standards,O
Regards,O
Michelle,B-PERSON
Hargrave,I-PERSON
Global,O
Resource,O
Mgmt.,O
(713,O
)853-6023,O
e-mail,O
:,O
michelle.hargrave,O
@enron.com,O
Please,O
have,O
your,O
presentations,O
to,O
me,O
by,O
10,O
AM,O
Friday,B-DATE
",",O
October,O
20,O
2000.,O
It,O
takes,O
a,O
couple,O
of,O
days,O
get,O
the,O
materials,O
back,O
from,O
Copy,B-ORG
Center.,O
The,O
be,O
put,O
in,O
new,O
binders,O
this,O
time,O
and,O
it,O
most,O
day,O
everything,O
together,O
binders.,O
Therefore,O
I,O
Center,I-ORG
afternoon,I-DATE
order,O
them,O
Monday,B-DATE
or,O
Tuesday,B-DATE
morning.,O
will,O
need,O
assembled,O
Thus,O
necessity,O
having,O
completed,O
Vince,B-PERSON
:,O
Basket,O
Options,O
Binary,O
(Digital,O
),O
Krishna,B-PERSON
Barrier,O
Other,O
Complex,O
Structures,O
Thanks,O
for,O
help,O
on,O
this.,O
Regards,O
Anita,B-PERSON
morning,I-DATE
Hey,O
!,O
?,O
I,O
took,O
your,O
advice,O
&,O
attempted,O
to,O
contact,O
Karen.,O
mailed,O
a,O
letter,O
her,O
old,O
address,O
had,O
it,O
forwarded,O
on.,O
She,O
called,O
me,O
yesterday,O
and,O
we,O
talked,O
forever,O
boy,O
",",O
Nicholas,B-PERSON
Elijah,I-PERSON
Messick,I-PERSON
on,O
Leap,O
Day,O
2,O
/29,O
by,O
C-section.,O
He,O
weighed,O
9,O
lb.,O
10,O
oz.,O
(I,O
'm,O
glad,O
she,O
C-section,O
),O
All,O
is,O
well,O
with,O
her.,O
said,O
that,O
husband,O
fight,O
lot,O
but,O
always,O
work,O
things,O
out.,O
They,O
live,O
in,O
15,O
yr.,O
house,O
Rowlett,B-LOCATION
near,O
Hwy.,B-LOCATION
66.,O
So,O
everything,O
seems,O
be,O
very,O
domestic,O
world,O
asked,O
about,O
you.,O
you,O
were,O
doing,O
fine,O
still,O
serious,O
relationship,O
girl,O
's,O
smarter,O
than,O
(ha,O
Anyways,O
just,O
thought,O
would,O
pass,O
some,O
friendly,O
gossip.,O
Thank,O
for,O
nudging,O
the,O
right,O
direction.,O
Talk,O
later,O
Amy,B-PERSON
Karen,B-PERSON
66,I-LOCATION
Thank,O
you,O
for,O
submitting,O
the,O
following,O
responses,O
on,O
RSVP,O
Online,O
Form,O
2001,O
Enron,B-ORG
Law,O
Conference.,O
The,O
information,O
submitted,O
is,O
as,O
follows,O
:,O
Attendance,O
Y,O
First,O
Name,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Last,O
Shackleton,O
Position,O
Attorney,O
Legal,O
Group,O
Wholesale,I-ORG
Services,I-ORG
Phone,O
(713,O
),O
853-5620,O
Fax,O
646-3490,O
Email,O
sara.shackleton,O
@enron.com,O
Admin.,O
Kaye,B-PERSON
Ellis,I-PERSON
853-5968,O
kaye.ellis,O
@ernon.com,O
Arrival,O
Date,O
May,O
2,O
",",O
Departure,O
4,O
Hotel,O
Accommodations,O
King,O
Sized,O
Bed,O
Non-Smoking,O
Other,O
Thursday,O
Activity,O
None,O
Selected,O
-,O
No,O
Golf,O
Handicap,O
Awards,O
Dinner,O
SAP,O
Company,O
0413,O
Cost,O
Center,O
105657,O
State,O
Bar,O
Licensed,O
TEXAS,O
#,O
18071900,O
LOUISIANA,O
11959,O
This,O
message,O
a,O
confirmation,O
of,O
details,O
your,O
form.,O
If,O
any,O
incorrect,O
or,O
plans,O
change,O
e-mail,O
Davidson,I-PERSON
with,O
information.,O
Do,O
not,O
make,O
changes,O
website.,O
Hi,O
Jeff,B-PERSON
",",O
Just,O
a,O
follow,O
up,O
to,O
our,O
call,O
this,B-DATE
morning.,O
If,O
you,O
get,O
your,O
guy,O
on,O
the,O
phone,O
try,O
and,O
following,O
information,O
:,O
1,O
),O
Route,O
map,O
including,O
both,O
end,O
points,O
of,O
network,O
2,O
Amount,O
capacity,O
they,O
may,O
want,O
lay,O
off,O
(they,O
are,O
currently,O
using,O
some,O
system,O
how,O
much,O
do,O
offer,O
?,O
3,O
Any,O
contract,O
details,O
(how,O
long,O
terms,O
penalties,O
restrictive,O
clauses,O
like,O
"""cannot",O
"resell""",O
Once,O
we,O
table,O
lets,O
together,O
with,O
them,O
see,O
if,O
there,O
is,O
deal,O
here.,O
I,O
will,O
be,O
out,O
office,O
from,O
3rd,O
through,O
9th,O
attending,O
trade,O
show,O
so,O
cannot,O
by,O
tomorrow,B-DATE
it,O
next,B-DATE
Thursday,I-DATE
afternoon.,O
Thanks,O
Dan,B-PERSON
Minter,I-PERSON
V,O
(503,O
)886-0452,O
F,O
)886-0441,O
morning,I-DATE
afternoon,I-DATE
Reliant,B-ORG
has,O
indicated,O
that,O
we,O
must,O
use,O
their,O
paper,O
-,O
this,O
point,O
is,O
non-negotiable.,O
Kay,B-PERSON
",",O
will,O
not,O
wire,O
any,O
funds,O
to,O
until,O
have,O
your,O
approval,O
of,O
the,O
contract.,O
I,O
understand,O
you,O
are,O
also,O
working,O
on,O
a,O
gas,O
contract,O
with,O
TXU.,O
We,O
need,O
one,O
these,O
contracts,O
in,O
place,O
so,O
can,O
buy,O
tomorrow,O
morning,O
it,O
doesn,O
't,O
matter,O
which,O
first.,O
Doug,B-PERSON
Phil,B-PERSON
Eric,B-PERSON
The,O
prepayment,O
were,O
going,O
send,O
may,O
be,O
TXU,B-ORG
instead.,O
coming,O
dangerously,O
close,O
defaulting,O
Tallahassee,B-ORG
Robin,B-PERSON
and,O
work,O
request,O
for,O
after,O
lunch.,O
Charles,B-PERSON
Thanks,O
for,O
the,O
reply.,O
Your,O
thoughts,O
on,O
EEI,B-ORG
draft,O
in,O
terms,O
of,O
details,O
would,O
be,O
helpful.,O
As,O
I,O
read,O
it,O
",",O
we,O
still,O
have,O
problems,O
with,O
that,O
had,O
NERC,B-ORG
which,O
is,O
based,O
deference,O
regional,O
rules,O
variances,O
reliability,O
entities,O
advisory,O
boards,O
limits,O
FERC,O
authority,O
etc.,O
It,O
also,O
helpful,O
to,O
input,O
whether,O
plans,O
EISB,B-ORG
could,O
go,O
forward,O
if,O
legislation,O
like,O
bill,O
were,O
enacted,O
into,O
law.,O
seem,O
not,O
since,O
"""SRO""",O
focus,O
only,O
"""reliability""",O
as,O
defined,O
by,O
how,O
defines,O
what,O
matters,O
are,O
subjects,O
an,O
"""organization",O
"standard.""",O
Joe,B-PERSON
",",O
Attached,O
is,O
link,O
for,O
Financial,O
Trading,O
position.,O
Job,O
descriptions,O
may,O
not,O
match,O
precisely,O
with,O
your,O
position,O
as,O
it,O
exists,O
today,O
but,O
that,O
OK.,O
We,O
have,O
tried,O
to,O
be,O
broad,O
possible,O
in,O
describing,O
the,O
open,O
positions,O
minimize,O
number,O
of,O
posting,O
links.,O
Your,O
job,O
will,O
change,O
and,O
offer,O
made,O
duties,O
you,O
are,O
performing,O
now.,O
The,O
requirement,O
by,O
end,O
day,O
on,O
Monday,O
even,O
though,O
this,O
says,O
Friday.,O
You,O
can,O
access,O
from,O
internet,O
at,O
office,O
or,O
home.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
any,O
questions.,O
Regards,O
Randy,B-PERSON
Curry,I-PERSON
email,O
:,O
randall.curry,O
@bridgeline.net,O
Phone,O
832-,O
851-,O
2801,O
Fax,O
832,O
-,O
2772,O
Inline,O
attachment,O
follows,O
Hey,O
Steve-,O
Since,O
the,B-DATE
6th,I-DATE
looks,O
like,O
it,O
is,O
a,O
good,O
day,O
to,O
get,O
together,O
",",O
maybe,O
I,O
could,O
come,O
over,O
your,O
house,O
around,O
12,O
:00.,O
We,O
go,O
lunch,O
and,O
since,O
had,O
last,O
priviledge,O
of,O
picking,O
out,O
"""very",O
interesting,O
"movie""",O
would,O
you,O
pick,O
next,O
one,O
!,O
This,O
time,O
also,O
have,O
lot,O
more,O
flexibility,O
in,O
afternoon.,O
Of,O
course,O
will,O
drop,O
quick,O
line,O
prior,O
make,O
sure,O
schedule,O
still,O
on,O
target.,O
Otherwise,O
enjoy,O
Thanksgiving,O
with,O
family,O
(don,O
't,O
too,O
fat,O
).,O
Talk,O
later.,O
Christine,B-PERSON
Get,O
FREE,O
download,O
MSN,O
Explorer,O
at,O
http,O
:,O
/,O
/explorer.msn.com,O
Steve,B-PERSON
POSREP,O
HOEGH,O
GALLEON,O
",",O
DATE,O
:,O
10-May,B-DATE
12,O
:00,O
9,O
(UTC,O
),O
A,O
Position,O
at,O
noon,O
N,O
25,O
E,O
044,O
29,O
B,O
Dist.,O
From,O
last,O
443,O
nm,O
C,O
To,O
go,O
to,O
next,O
port,O
1199,O
D,O
ETA,O
Qalhat,B-LOCATION
13,O
0900,O
LT,O
1,O
Average,O
sea,O
/wind,O
Sea,O
SW,O
4,O
Wind,O
3,O
2,O
speed,O
18.46,O
kn,O
BOG,O
consumed,O
0,O
m3,O
Total,O
5,O
F.O,O
Consumed,O
164,O
6,O
G.O.,O
Brgds,O
Knut,O
Bentzr,O
?d,O
Master,O
LNG,O
/C,O
"""Hoegh",O
"Galleon""",O
E-mail,O
master.gall,O
@hoegh.no,O
Teleph,O
Inmarsat,O
tel.no.+873,O
330853910,O
Fax,O
fax,O
no.+873,O
330853913,O
Telex,O
telex,O
no.+583,O
330853915,O
430853910,O
(24hrs.watch,O
Hoegh,B-ORG
John,B-PERSON
",",O
This,O
is,O
the,O
latest,O
skew,O
calculator,O
file.,O
It,O
has,O
a,O
sheet,O
for,O
vol,O
table,O
and,O
it,O
calculates,O
ENA,O
pdf,O
using,O
linear,O
interpolation,O
between,O
points,O
on,O
not,O
polynomial.,O
The,O
file,O
shows,O
yesterday,O
's,O
settle,O
data,O
Jun,O
matches,O
very,O
well.,O
(All,O
2001,O
contracts,O
agree,O
closely,O
with,O
from,O
in,O
fact.,O
),O
I,O
've,O
added,O
macro,O
that,O
fetches,O
underlying,O
price,O
volatility,O
interest,O
rate,O
our,O
in-house,O
EGSPROD32,O
database.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
this,O
doesn,O
't,O
work,O
you.,O
Feel,O
free,O
to,O
contact,O
any,O
of,O
us,O
you,O
have,O
questions,O
or,O
requests,O
regarding,O
hope,O
helpful.,O
ken,B-PERSON
I,O
understand,O
that,O
the,O
return,O
e,O
:mail,O
sent,O
to,O
Kim,B-PERSON
Rizzi,I-PERSON
on,O
November,B-DATE
27th,I-DATE
was,O
not,O
opened,O
by,O
HR.,O
Please,O
note,O
my,O
below,O
had,O
asked,O
for,O
clarification,O
Brent,B-PERSON
Price.,O
This,O
second,O
regarding,O
with,O
no,O
reply,O
back.,O
My,O
first,O
message,O
noted,O
left,O
out,O
of,I-ORG
list,O
",",O
and,O
whether,O
or,O
Rick,B-PERSON
Causey,I-PERSON
planned,O
supply,O
a,O
pre-ranking,O
if,O
needed,O
do,O
so.,O
Can,O
you,O
clarify,O
this,O
me,O
?,O
reports,O
as,O
head,O
operations,O
EGM,I-ORG
in,O
his,O
role,O
CAO,B-ORG
EGM.,O
Here,O
are,O
appropriate,O
pre-rankings,O
grouped,O
level,O
:,O
Superior,O
Excellent,O
Strong,O
Satisfactory,O
Needs,O
Improv.,O
Issues,O
VP,O
's,O
Price,I-PERSON
Hedstrom,O
Hall,B-PERSON
Sr.,O
Directors,O
Solmonson,B-PERSON
Reeves,I-PERSON
Herod,B-PERSON
Scribner,I-PERSON
Thomas,O
Mills,O
Superty,B-PERSON
Henenberg,I-PERSON
Perez,O
Wilson,O
Venturatos,B-PERSON
Third,O
Set,O
of,O
Discovery,O
California,O
Parties,O
to,O
Williams.,O
Hard,O
copies,O
are,O
being,O
sent,O
the,O
restricted,O
service,O
list.,O
Joseph,B-PERSON
H.,I-PERSON
Fagan,I-PERSON
ATTORNEY,O
HellerEhrman,B-ORG
tel.,O
:,O
202.912.2162,O
fax,O
202.912.2020,O
e-mail,O
jfagan,O
@hewm.com,O
web,O
http,O
/,O
/www.hewm.com,O
Address,O
1666,O
K,O
Street,O
",",O
N.W.,O
Suite,O
300,O
Washington,O
D.C.,O
20006-1228,O
The,O
information,O
contained,O
in,O
this,O
message,O
may,O
be,O
privileged,O
confidential,O
and,O
protected,O
from,O
disclosure.,O
If,O
you,O
not,O
intended,O
recipient,O
any,O
dissemination,O
distribution,O
or,O
copying,O
is,O
strictly,O
prohibited.,O
think,O
that,O
have,O
received,O
error,O
please,O
sender,O
at,O
JFagan,O
@HEWM.COM,O
.,O
-,O
Transmittal,O
Williams.rtf,O
Willi.rtf,O
Market,O
Participants,O
:,O
Please,O
assure,O
that,O
this,O
Notification,O
is,O
forwarded,O
to,O
your,O
respective,O
Operating,O
Departments,O
of,O
Procedure,O
Update,O
*,O
The,O
following,O
new,O
or,O
revised,O
ISO,B-ORG
Procedures,O
have,O
been,O
implemented,O
and,O
are,O
posted,O
for,O
reference,O
on,O
the,O
Website.,O
T-123,O
WSCC,O
Path,O
45,O
ISO-CFE,O
Transfer,O
Capability,O
(OTC,O
),O
Version,O
4.5,O
Effective,O
Date,O
6-6-01,B-DATE
Purpose,O
Study,O
results,O
show,O
P-45,O
limited,O
408,O
MW,O
bi-directional,O
a,O
30-minute,O
thermal,O
limit.,O
OTC,O
subset,O
total,O
SDGE,O
/CFE,O
described,O
in,O
San,B-LOCATION
Diego,I-LOCATION
Area,O
procedure,O
T-132.,O
Changes,O
/,O
Reasons,O
No,O
change,O
from,O
Spring,O
find,O
them,O
at,O
http,O
/www1.caiso.com,O
/thegrid,O
/operations,O
/opsdoc,O
/index.html,O
under,O
appropriate,O
section,O
heading.,O
If,O
you,O
any,O
questions,O
",",O
please,O
e-mail,O
'Procedure,O
Control,O
Desk,O
',O
mailbox,O
[mailto,O
:procctrldesk,O
@caiso.com,O
],O
we,O
will,O
respond,O
as,O
soon,O
possible.,O
Thank-You,O
Operations,O
Support,O
Training,O
Glad,O
you,O
got,O
some,O
rain.,O
We,O
are,O
still,O
doing,O
lots,O
of,O
watering,O
on,B-DATE
the,I-DATE
yard.,O
No,O
water,O
rationing,O
in,O
our,O
area,O
yet,O
",",O
but,O
it,O
has,O
been,O
put,O
place,O
many,O
areas,O
and,O
around,O
Houston.,O
I,O
have,O
to,O
be,O
Austin,B-LOCATION
for,O
a,O
presentation,O
reception,O
late,O
afternoon,O
September,O
5,O
so,O
thought,O
that,O
would,O
fun,O
try,O
come,O
earlier,O
lunch,O
your,O
birthday.,O
haven,O
't,O
made,O
flight,O
reservations,O
am,O
sure,O
can,O
work,O
at,O
University,B-LOCATION
Club,I-LOCATION
by,O
12,O
:15.,O
Looks,O
as,O
if,O
whole,O
family,O
will,O
go,O
Hallettsville,B-LOCATION
9th.,O
David,O
enjoy,O
drive,O
girls,O
sleep,O
way,O
over,O
!,O
9th,I-DATE
Houston,B-LOCATION
Hey,O
Scott,O
;,O
Attached,O
are,O
some,O
representative,O
bonds,O
as,O
discussed.,O
Give,O
Pat,B-PERSON
or,O
I,O
a,O
call,O
to,O
discuss.,O
Best,O
regards,O
",",O
Vincent,B-PERSON
M.,I-PERSON
Weir,I-PERSON
Investment,O
Associate,O
UBSPaineWebber,O
Inc,O
713-957-7088,O
Notice,O
Regarding,O
Entry,O
of,O
Orders,O
and,O
Instructions,O
:,O
Please,O
do,O
not,O
transmit,O
orders,O
/or,O
instructions,O
regarding,O
your,O
UBS,O
PaineWebber,O
account,O
(s,O
),O
by,O
e-mail.,O
transmitted,O
e-mail,O
will,O
be,O
accepted,O
responsible,O
for,O
carrying,O
out,O
such,O
instructions.,O
Privacy,O
Confidentiality,O
reserves,O
the,O
right,O
monitor,O
review,O
content,O
all,O
communications,O
sent,O
received,O
its,O
employees.,O
-,O
HM-ES,O
SCOTT,O
NEAL,O
BOND,O
06072001.xls,O
06072001,B-DATE
Mark,B-PERSON
:,O
I,O
had,O
a,O
chat,O
with,O
our,O
people,O
in,O
Mexico,B-LOCATION
and,O
",",O
as,O
Haedicke,I-PERSON
warned,O
me,O
they,O
are,O
very,O
eager,O
for,O
to,O
go,O
there.,O
They,O
asked,O
whether,O
could,O
there,O
next,B-DATE
week.,O
think,O
the,O
purpose,O
of,O
trip,O
is,O
meet,O
them,O
kind,O
let,O
know,O
what,O
have.,O
have,O
no,O
idea,O
if,O
any,O
policy,O
you,O
travelling.,O
All,O
things,O
being,O
equal,O
less,O
travel,O
better,O
but,O
by,O
same,O
token,O
absolutely,O
problem,O
about,O
going,O
where,O
need,O
go.,O
these,O
just,O
little,O
"""hand",O
"holding""",O
while.,O
How,O
do,O
want,O
deal,O
respect,O
my,O
travelling,O
?,O
Do,O
approve,O
(or,O
not,O
),O
whenever,O
or,O
advance,O
Thanks,O
FPL,B-PERSON
week,I-DATE
Jeff,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
have,O
been,O
receiving,O
and,O
forwarding,O
mail,O
from,O
you,O
a,O
lot,O
lately,O
decided,O
that,O
since,O
it,O
doesn,O
't,O
seem,O
to,O
be,O
ending,O
anytime,O
soon,O
should,O
contact,O
you.,O
You,O
send,O
out,O
multiple,O
mailings,O
daily,O
regarding,O
all,O
things,O
California,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
people,O
on,O
list,O
is,O
Mike,B-PERSON
Smith,I-PERSON
in,O
legal.,O
His,O
address,O
D,I-PERSON
Smith.,O
am,O
EEIS,O
my,O
M,O
would,O
contacted,O
sooner,O
but,O
other,O
's,O
messages,O
happens,O
quite,O
frequently,O
usually,O
works,O
as,O
stop,O
gap,O
method.,O
appreciate,O
if,O
changed,O
your,O
mailing,O
look,O
forward,O
not,O
hearing,O
near,O
future.,O
Thank,O
Please,O
see,O
Professor,B-PERSON
Littlechild,I-PERSON
's,O
note,O
to,O
our,O
former,O
Deputy,O
Chairman,O
for,O
Enron,B-ORG
Europe,I-ORG
",",O
Ralph,B-PERSON
Hodge.,O
is,O
no,O
longer,O
with,O
us.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
would,O
like,O
support,O
(,O
$,O
),O
coming,O
California.,O
He,O
was,O
a,O
somewhat,O
passive,O
regulator,O
(too,O
academic,O
but,O
credible,O
authority,O
having,O
written,O
what,O
regarded,O
as,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
seminal,O
works,O
on,O
incentive,O
regulation,O
which,O
model,O
in,O
use,O
UK.,O
likes,O
and,O
has,O
been,O
trying,O
get,O
us,O
pay,O
him,O
some,O
work,O
time.,O
No,O
need,O
it,O
here,O
UK,B-LOCATION
I,O
emerging,O
markets,O
given,O
opportunity.,O
have,O
your,O
thoughts,O
at,O
earliest,O
convenience.,O
thanks,O
mcs,O
Hodge,I-PERSON
California,B-LOCATION
Attached,O
is,O
PIRA,B-ORG
's,O
latest,O
"""Monthly",O
Gas,O
"Forecast.""",O
If,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions,O
regarding,O
the,O
report,O
content,O
",",O
please,O
contact,O
:,O
Greg,B-PERSON
Shuttlesworth,I-PERSON
(email,O
greg,O
@pira.com,O
),O
Tom,B-PERSON
Howard,I-PERSON
tazh,O
Richard,B-PERSON
Redash,I-PERSON
Rich,O
Nobu,B-PERSON
Tarui,I-PERSON
nobuo,O
or,O
Jane,B-PERSON
Hsu,I-PERSON
jane,O
at,O
(212,O
686-6808.,O
Contact,O
Client,O
Services,O
distribution,O
and,O
address,O
changes,O
686-6808,O
email,O
support,O
@pira.com.,O
NOTE,O
Circulation,O
of,O
"Forecast""",O
outside,O
a,O
licensed,O
area,O
strictly,O
prohibited.,O
Clients,O
that,O
are,O
unsure,O
their,O
require,O
an,O
extension,O
current,O
license,O
should,O
sales,O
representative,O
to,O
Energy,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
-,O
gasnov01.pdf,O
Kalen,B-PERSON
",.",O
per,O
your,O
discussion,O
about,O
getting,O
these,O
issues,O
to,I-DATE
management,O
committee,O
",",O
below,O
are,O
some,O
of,O
the,O
HR,O
Policy,O
changes,O
consider,O
implementing,O
prior,B-DATE
year,I-DATE
end.,O
Clarification,O
-,O
what,O
revisions,O
if,O
any,O
should,O
apply,O
non-filed,O
entities,O
?,O
Vacation,O
change,O
accrual,O
rate,O
as,O
planned,O
FMLA,O
/,O
Sick,O
Leave,O
leave,O
run,O
concurrent,O
with,O
Enron,B-ORG
's,O
sick,O
program,O
when,O
appropriate.,O
Educational,O
Assistance,O
:,O
suspend,O
tuition,O
reimbursements.,O
absence,O
reduce,O
or,O
amend,O
paid,O
leave.,O
Leaves,O
include,O
Personal,O
(eliminate,O
Mgmt.,O
discretion,O
),O
Funeral,O
/bereavement,O
(should,O
we,O
establish,O
a,O
policy,O
cap,O
3,O
days,O
Paternity,O
adoption,O
pay,O
parent,O
father,O
(40,O
hours,O
outside,O
Jury,O
Witness,O
duty,O
(pay,O
extent,O
required,O
by,O
law,O
Military,O
(reduce,O
eliminate,O
salary,O
bridge,O
paid-,O
difference,O
between,O
base,O
and,O
military,O
end,I-DATE
BROADCAST,O
MESSAGE,O
TO,O
ALL,O
PILOTS,O
:,O
Happy,O
Halloween,O
on,O
Wednesday,B-DATE
!,O
2001,B-DATE
charts,O
now,O
most,O
recent,O
version,O
Adobe,O
Acrobat,O
4.0,O
and,O
print,O
clearly,O
Reader,O
3.0,O
higher.,O
downloaded,O
for,O
FREE,O
www.adobe.com.,O
(See,O
attached,O
file,O
:,O
qoq-60-min.pdf,O
),O
-,O
Thanks,O
for,O
forwarding,O
all,O
of,O
this,O
stuff,O
-,O
so,O
far,O
it,O
has,O
been,O
mine.,O
I,O
think,O
your,O
name,O
must,O
come,O
up,O
automatically,O
some,O
these,O
folks,O
when,O
they,O
just,O
type,O
in,O
Mark,B-PERSON
Taylor.,O
It,O
's,O
not,O
nearly,O
as,O
bad,O
there,O
was,O
another,O
E,I-PERSON
Taylor,I-PERSON
and,O
he,O
wasn,O
't,O
nice,O
about,O
either,O
(instead,O
them,O
to,O
me,O
",",O
would,O
send,O
back,O
the,O
senders,O
with,O
sometimes,O
nasty,O
notes,O
like,O
'try,O
get,O
right,O
next,O
time,O
',O
).,O
Luckily,O
both,O
you,O
is,O
no,O
longer,O
Enron,B-ORG
can,O
imagine,O
how,O
be,O
if,O
were,O
three,O
us,O
?,O
When,O
usually,O
a,O
note,O
sender,O
letting,O
know,O
that,O
are,O
two,O
need,O
pay,O
attention,O
addressing,O
things,O
one,O
or,O
other.,O
A,O
@EES,O
Hi,O
Jon,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
spoke,O
with,O
Russel,B-PERSON
and,O
this,O
is,O
what,O
he,O
said,O
:,O
-Enron,O
Canada,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
will,O
be,O
posting,O
the,O
letter,O
of,O
credit,O
-the,O
cost,O
75-100bp,O
's,O
per,O
amount,O
LC,O
ie.,O
$1,O
",000",O
=,O
$7,O
",500-",O
associated,O
particular,O
business,O
group-most,O
likely,O
Enron,B-ORG
-NGX,O
provide,O
updates,O
so,O
regarding,O
$30,O
MM,O
-We,O
have,O
to,O
actively,O
requesting,O
our,O
position,O
-Russel,O
able,O
run,O
real,O
time,O
data,O
in,O
a,O
crunch,O
situation,O
but,O
typically,O
we,O
can,O
expect,O
one,O
day,O
lag,O
also,O
mentioned,O
that,O
going,O
contact,O
NGX,B-ORG
group,O
they,O
attempt,O
tp,O
mimic,O
format,O
best,O
can.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
need,O
anything,O
else.,O
Ian,B-PERSON
Hi,O
All,O
",",O
The,O
full,O
requirement,O
dispatch,O
application,O
version,O
0.9,O
is,O
now,O
available.,O
To,O
install,O
copy,O
all,O
three,O
files,O
in,O
O,O
:,O
\Research,O
\Common,O
\fromcs,O
\fullReqDispatch,O
\installation,O
into,O
a,O
directory,O
and,O
click,O
setup,O
follow,O
onscreen,O
instructions.,O
document,O
will,O
shortly.,O
A,O
stochastic,O
programming,O
that,O
optimally,O
trades,O
power,O
operates,O
portfolio,O
of,O
generators,O
to,O
satisfy,O
load,O
commitment,O
contracts,O
with,O
uncertainties,O
prices,O
fuel,O
loads.,O
Under,O
transmission,O
constraints,O
we,O
can,O
trade,O
some,O
amount,O
the,O
market,O
at,O
bid-ask,O
prices.,O
In,O
this,O
model,O
also,O
take,O
account,O
minimum,O
up,O
time,O
downtime,O
as,O
well,O
startup,O
costs.,O
-Chonawee,O
Below,O
are,O
screen,O
shots,O
Chonawee,B-PERSON
Hi,O
Guys-,O
Just,O
wanted,O
to,O
let,O
you,O
know,O
that,O
my,O
hotmail,O
account,O
will,O
be,O
the,O
best,O
way,O
reach,O
me,O
for,O
now.,O
Our,O
company,O
shut,O
down,O
last,B-DATE
Thursday-,O
so,O
now,O
I,O
am,O
out,O
of,O
a,O
job.,O
Great,O
time,O
looking.,O
Anyways-,O
it,O
was,O
total,O
shock,O
and,O
we,O
were,O
quite,O
upset.,O
My,O
parent,O
is,O
trying,O
find,O
something,O
there-,O
but,O
its,O
not,O
looking,O
too,O
good.,O
If,O
hear,O
any,O
leads-please,O
know.,O
Also-,O
anyones,O
addresss,O
missed-,O
can,O
send,O
them,O
this,O
way.,O
don,O
't,O
have,O
Amanda,B-PERSON
's,O
",",O
Lisa,B-PERSON
or,O
Courtney,B-PERSON
(work,O
).,O
sure,O
if,O
right,O
address,O
Courtnie.,O
So-,O
'll,O
keep,O
updated.,O
Thanks-,O
Laura,B-PERSON
home,O
#,O
281.583.7820,O
cell,O
832.452.3247,O
ps-,O
Hey,O
Em-,O
busy,O
?,O
Send,O
receive,O
Hotmail,O
on,O
your,O
mobile,O
device,O
:,O
Click,O
Here,O
Courtnie,B-PERSON
Em,B-PERSON
Thursday,I-DATE
Attached,O
is,O
a,O
PIRA,B-ORG
Special,O
Release,O
entitled,O
"""Gas",O
Flash,O
:,O
Strong,O
Supply,O
Growth,O
"Indicated.""",O
If,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions,O
regarding,O
the,O
report,O
's,O
content,O
",",O
please,O
contact,O
Greg,B-PERSON
Shuttlesworth,I-PERSON
(email,O
greg,O
@pira.com,O
),O
Tom,B-PERSON
Howard,I-PERSON
tazh,O
Richard,B-PERSON
Redash,I-PERSON
Rich,O
Nobu,B-PERSON
Tarui,I-PERSON
nobuo,O
or,O
Jane,B-PERSON
Hsu,I-PERSON
jane,O
at,O
(212,O
686-6808.,O
Contact,O
John,B-PERSON
Graziano,I-PERSON
distribution,O
and,O
address,O
changes,O
686-6808,O
email,O
support,O
@pira.com.,O
NOTE,O
Circulation,O
of,O
"Weekly""",O
outside,O
Client,O
licensed,O
area,O
strictly,O
prohibited.,O
Clients,O
that,O
are,O
unsure,O
their,O
require,O
an,O
extension,O
current,O
license,O
should,O
sales,O
representative,O
to,O
Energy,I-ORG
Group,I-ORG
-,O
agaspec043001.pdf,O
We,O
have,O
decided,O
to,O
postpone,O
the,O
All-Employee,O
Meeting,O
",",O
which,O
was,O
scheduled,O
at,O
10,O
a.m.,O
Wednesday,O
August,O
9,O
and,O
concentrate,O
our,O
efforts,O
on,O
a,O
successful,O
kick,O
off,O
of,O
2000,O
Houston,B-LOCATION
United,B-ORG
Way,I-ORG
campaign.,O
This,O
year,O
's,O
gameshow,O
event,O
"""Who",O
Wants,O
Help,O
Millions,O
"?""",O
will,O
run,O
as,O
previously,O
announced,O
from,O
11,O
:15,O
noon,O
in,O
Hyatt,B-LOCATION
Regency,I-LOCATION
Imperial,O
Ballroom,O
followed,O
by,O
lunch,O
Antioch,B-LOCATION
Park,I-LOCATION
1,O
:30,O
p.m.,O
encourage,O
all,O
employees,O
attend,O
this,O
fun,O
cheer,O
your,O
business,O
unit,O
representatives,O
victory,O
helping,O
others,O
community.,O
communicate,O
new,O
date,O
soon,O
it,O
has,O
been,O
determined.,O
Your,O
passwords,O
are,O
extended,O
",",O
or,O
if,O
you,O
did,O
not,O
have,O
one,O
before,O
(Rogers,O
and,O
Russell,B-PERSON
),O
now,O
do.,O
Normally,O
Jeff,B-PERSON
Maack,I-PERSON
handles,O
this,O
but,O
he,O
's,O
in,O
our,O
home,O
office,O
Philadelphia,B-LOCATION
today.,O
?,O
Rogers,B-PERSON
we,O
launching,O
TVA,B-ORG
ComEd,B-ORG
ERCOT,B-ORG
hourly,O
daily,O
term,O
indexes,O
March,B-DATE
19,I-DATE
will,O
begin,O
beta,O
testing,O
on,O
Feb.,B-DATE
19.,O
Feel,O
free,O
to,O
let,O
your,O
colleagues,O
know.,O
Thanks,O
for,O
interest.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
I,O
can,O
assist,O
any,O
way.,O
Bobette,O
Riner,O
Senior,O
Power,O
Markets,O
Analyst,O
TradersNews,B-ORG
Energy,I-ORG
713,O
/647-8690,O
FAX,O
:,O
/647-7552,O
cell,O
832,O
/428-7008,O
bobette.riner,O
@ipgdirect.com,O
http,O
/,O
/www.tradersnewspower.com,O
Hi,O
Ken,B-PERSON
",",O
You,O
have,O
always,O
told,O
us,O
that,O
we,O
can,O
email,O
at,O
any,O
time,O
with,O
comments,O
or,O
questions.,O
Employees,O
are,O
really,O
getting,O
worried,O
about,O
what,O
's,O
happened,O
our,O
stock,O
price.,O
It,O
not,O
looking,O
too,O
good.,O
I,O
know,O
you,O
and,O
upper,O
management,O
working,O
hard,O
to,O
sort,O
this,O
out.,O
Please,O
let,O
is,O
going,O
on.,O
Rumors,O
flying,O
layoffs,O
bankruptcy,O
takeovers.,O
All,O
of,O
lives,O
affected.,O
People,O
trying,O
hang,O
in,O
here,O
but,O
the,O
future,O
uncertain.,O
We,O
wondering,O
whether,O
stay,O
bail,O
need,O
more,O
answers.,O
Another,O
comment,O
which,O
constantly,O
being,O
made,O
"""It",O
encouraging,O
when,O
don,O
't,O
see,O
buying,O
shares,O
these,O
historically,O
low,O
"prices"".",O
Any,O
?,O
Thanks,O
Clara,B-PERSON
Carrington,I-PERSON
Financial,O
Trading,O
Manager,O
-,O
Rate,O
Currency,O
Risk,O
Mgmt,O
Direct,O
Tel,O
:,O
(713,O
),O
853-9224,O
Email,O
Clara.Carrington,O
@enron.com,O
I,O
am,O
taking,O
Good,B-DATE
Friday,I-DATE
as,O
my,O
discretionary,O
holiday,O
for,O
the,O
year.,O
will,O
be,O
in,O
Austin,B-LOCATION
with,O
daughter,O
her,O
official,O
tour,O
and,O
info,O
session,O
at,O
UT,B-LOCATION
",",O
plus,O
a,O
look,O
dorms.,O
Patti,B-PERSON
have,O
numbers,O
where,O
can,O
reached,O
Austin.,O
We,O
are,O
making,O
final,O
changes,O
to,O
orig,O
presentation,O
today,O
-,O
reviewing,O
those,O
tomorrow,B-DATE
e,O
:mailing,O
you,O
current,O
draft,O
version,O
although,O
it,O
does,O
not,O
yet,O
reflect,O
all,O
of,O
needed.,O
still,O
trying,O
eliminate,O
some,O
pages,O
make,O
more,O
manageable,O
size.,O
taken,O
work,O
that,O
Rahil,B-PERSON
Fred,B-PERSON
done,O
on,O
services,O
made,O
into,O
an,O
appendix,O
nice,O
but,O
way,O
too,O
much,O
detail,O
presentation.,O
Thank,O
you,O
for,O
the,O
response.,O
Would,O
it,O
be,O
fair,O
to,O
say,O
that,O
all,O
capacity,O
California,B-LOCATION
and,O
Arizona,B-LOCATION
is,O
fully,O
subscribed,O
?,O
Thanks.,O
jrm,O
Elizabeth.Brown,O
@enron.com,O
wrote,O
:,O
John,B-PERSON
",",O
With,O
regard,O
your,O
first,O
question,O
yes,O
there,O
are,O
additional,O
design,O
capacities,O
considered.,O
The,O
Topock,O
lateral,O
which,O
consists,O
of,O
three,O
points,O
listed,O
has,O
a,O
400,O
MDth,O
/d.,O
Additionally,O
mainline,O
going,O
west,O
serves,O
ALL,O
our,O
markets,O
in,O
as,O
well,O
at,O
1090,O
As,O
second,O
data,O
fields,O
were,O
highlighted,O
red,O
more,O
my,O
reference,O
since,O
these,O
required,O
some,O
manual,O
review,O
/correction,O
on,O
part.,O
If,O
need,O
further,O
information,O
or,O
explanation,O
please,O
feel,O
free,O
contact,O
me.,O
Thanks,O
Elizabeth,B-PERSON
Corry,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
would,O
love,O
to,O
start,O
the,O
process,O
of,O
cleaning,O
up,O
scheduling,O
system.,O
We,O
will,O
need,O
help,O
from,O
schedulers,O
as,O
well,O
so,O
can,O
you,O
send,O
Duong,B-PERSON
Luu,I-PERSON
their,O
logins,O
and,O
request,O
'Zero,O
Volumes,O
',O
application,O
in,O
EnPower.,O
There,O
are,O
many,O
people,O
asking,O
about,O
what,O
is,O
flowing,O
month,O
creeping,O
by,O
if,O
could,O
get,O
with,O
me,O
tomorrow,O
make,O
a,O
game,O
plan,O
that,O
be,O
great.,O
think,O
we,O
should,O
have,O
us,O
spreadsheets,O
an,O
explanatory,O
then,O
along,O
Unify,O
users,O
come,O
plan.,O
hope,O
use,O
this,O
let,O
know,O
your,O
thoughts.,O
Thanks,O
Stacey,B-PERSON
Paul,B-PERSON
:,O
John,B-PERSON
Fortunato,I-PERSON
has,O
advised,O
me,O
that,O
CP,B-ORG
only,O
three,O
(3,O
),O
issues,O
with,O
the,O
draft,O
which,O
we,O
delivered,O
in,O
November,O
",",O
2000.,O
The,O
credit,O
are,O
(1,O
financials,O
available,O
online,O
-,O
'll,O
need,O
their,O
website,O
address,O
(2,O
Threshold,O
for,O
cross,O
default,O
is,O
too,O
low,O
and,O
wish,O
a,O
"""higher",O
"number""",O
but,O
have,O
not,O
given,O
any,O
indication,O
of,O
what,O
they,O
want,O
Please,O
let,O
Stephanie,B-PERSON
know,O
outcome,O
so,O
can,O
prepare,O
executable,O
docs.,O
Thanks.,O
P.S.,O
legal,O
issue,O
was,O
governing,O
law,O
Texas,O
or,O
NY.,O
doesn,O
't,O
care,O
needs,O
confirmation,O
possibly,O
explanation.,O
Sara,B-PERSON
Shackleton,I-PERSON
Enron,B-ORG
North,I-ORG
America,I-ORG
Corp.,I-ORG
1400,O
Smith,O
Street,O
EB,O
3801a,O
Houston,O
77002,O
713-853-5620,O
(phone,O
713-646-3490,O
(fax,O
sara.shackleton,O
@enron.com,O
I,O
thought,O
'd,O
communicate,O
to,O
the,O
group,O
some,O
recent,O
developments.,O
1.,O
Gordon,B-PERSON
and,O
Ryan,B-PERSON
advise,O
that,O
swaps,O
for,O
assets,O
in,O
JEDI,B-ORG
1,O
2,O
will,O
cover,O
our,O
proportionate,O
economic,O
interest,O
asset,O
within,O
JEDI.,O
believes,O
spreadsheet,O
of,O
proposed,O
reflects,O
this.,O
The,O
swap,O
be,O
between,O
Harrier,B-ORG
Talon,B-ORG
there,O
no,O
back-to-back,O
with,O
There,O
should,O
required,O
disclosures,O
CalPERS,B-ORG
resulting,O
from,O
these,O
hedges.,O
2.,O
currently,O
on,O
balance,O
sheet,O
are,O
hedged,O
Raptor,B-ORG
then,O
sold,O
Condor,B-ORG
",",O
reduction,O
hedge,O
or,O
any,O
when,O
it,O
moves,O
into,O
Condor.,O
Talon.,O
3.,O
Mark,B-PERSON
Taylor,I-PERSON
Bob,B-PERSON
Baird,I-PERSON
have,O
concluded,O
can,O
terminable,O
by,O
if,O
underlying,O
security,O
is,O
sold.,O
Here,O
is,O
the,I-DATE
electronic,O
version,O
of,I-DATE
PGE,O
/Sierra,O
answer,O
to,O
TANC,O
/SMUD,O
protest,O
which,O
was,O
filed,O
on,B-DATE
Monday.,O
Unfortunately,O
",",O
everyone,O
not,O
included,O
Skadden,B-PERSON
circulation,O
list,O
review,O
drafts,O
so,O
rectify,O
this,O
problem,O
I,O
will,O
forward,O
all,O
future,O
merger,O
related,O
emails,O
email,O
as,O
receive,O
them.,O
We,O
are,O
trying,O
set,O
up,O
a,O
conference,O
call,O
with,O
LeBoeuf,B-PERSON
attorneys,O
(FERC,O
and,O
SEC,B-ORG
),O
for,O
timing,O
update,O
we,O
around,O
check,O
's,O
availability,O
within,B-DATE
next,I-DATE
couple,I-DATE
days.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know,O
if,O
you,O
have,O
any,O
questions,O
or,O
comments.,O
Sarah,B-PERSON
Monday,I-DATE
days,I-DATE
FERC,B-ORG
I,O
notice,O
that,O
there,O
is,O
another,O
message,O
from,O
you.,O
Just,O
to,O
let,O
you,O
know,O
have,O
chosen,O
not,O
read,O
it.,O
Though,O
hopefully,O
did,O
mean,O
",",O
my,O
feeling,O
were,O
very,O
hurt,O
by,O
your,O
last,O
one,O
and,O
just,O
cannot,O
deal,O
with,O
again,O
right,O
now.,O
We,O
had,O
a,O
great,O
time,O
at,O
the,O
museum,O
as,O
usual.,O
Christopher,B-PERSON
knows,O
it,O
heart,O
could,O
be,O
tour,O
guide.,O
bought,O
him,O
an,O
arrowhead,O
goede,O
called,O
ocos,O
?,O
Carley,B-PERSON
only,O
wanted,O
butterfly,O
pin,O
(,O
$,O
.92,O
),O
do,O
can,O
imagine,O
beauty,O
of,O
As,O
usual,O
they,O
good,O
gold.,O
stopped,O
see,O
Kirk,B-PERSON
Sue,B-PERSON
them,O
give,O
Jerry,B-PERSON
call,O
on,O
phone.,O
All,O
",",O
Each,O
of,O
you,O
have,O
received,O
your,O
interview,O
schedule,O
and,O
resumes,O
for,O
tomorrow,O
's,O
interviews,O
taking,O
place,O
at,O
3,O
Allen,O
Center,O
17th,O
Floor,O
from,O
2.00,O
-,O
4.30,O
/5.00.,O
You,O
been,O
broken,O
down,O
into,O
four,O
teams,O
(as,O
per,O
).,O
Please,O
note,O
that,O
the,O
candidate,O
will,O
be,O
stationed,O
in,O
office,O
rotate,O
to,O
(all,O
which,O
are,O
adjacent,O
ensure,O
arrive,O
promptly,O
first,O
pm,O
keep,O
30,O
min,O
time,O
limt,O
interview.,O
team,O
assigned,O
a,O
coordinator,O
assist,O
through,O
event.,O
Red,O
Team,O
:,O
Interviewing,O
5,O
Candidates,O
Karen,B-PERSON
Buckley,I-PERSON
Green,O
Todd,B-PERSON
Peikert,I-PERSON
Purple,O
6,O
Courtnie,B-PERSON
Parker,I-PERSON
Blue,O
Adrianne,B-PERSON
Engler,I-PERSON
We,O
look,O
forward,O
seeing,O
tomorrow.,O
Rgds,O
Karen.,O
Henry,B-PERSON
is,O
a,O
code,O
name.,O
It,O
happen,O
to,O
both,O
of,O
us,O
this,O
pass,O
week,O
/weekend.,O
11,O
/26,O
:19,O
AM,O
You,O
are,O
so,O
nasty,O
!,O
Who,O
(that,O
get,O
's,O
on,O
your,O
nerves,O
),O
?,O
I,O
can,O
take,O
breather,O
anytime,O
now.,O
have,O
an,O
:45,O
meeting,O
today,O
and,O
then,O
after,O
that,O
",",O
it,O
just,O
wait,O
see.,O
am,O
thrilled,O
for,O
you,O
deserve,O
everything,O
're,O
receiving,O
now,O
much,O
more,O
too,O
very,O
glad,O
be,O
friend...I,O
only,O
wished,O
we,O
lived,O
in,O
the,O
same,O
city,O
could,O
visit,O
often.,O
When,O
God,O
put,O
together,O
he,O
knew,O
what,O
was,O
doing,O
AS,O
ALWAYS,O
love,O
my,O
sister.,O
Also,O
need,O
careful,O
e-mail,O
use,O
words,O
if,O
know,O
mean.,O
how,O
READ,O
Love,O
ya,O
Dale,B-PERSON
:,O
Looks,O
okay,O
I,O
just,O
made,O
a,O
few,O
changes,O
updated,O
the,O
reference,O
NYISO,B-LOCATION
as,O
site,O
publisher,O
and,O
also,O
location,O
reference.,O
ISO,O
NY,O
Zone,O
A,O
(West,O
),O
Peak,O
The,O
Floating,O
Price,O
during,O
Determination,O
Period,O
shall,O
be,O
average,O
of,O
hourly,O
day-ahead,O
prices,O
listed,O
in,O
Index,O
(in,O
final,O
",",O
not,O
estimate,O
form,O
for,O
electricity,O
delivered,O
hours,O
on,O
each,O
Delivery,O
Day,O
applicable,O
Period.,O
calculated,O
utilizing,O
clearing,O
published,O
by,O
New,O
York,O
Independent,O
System,O
Operator,O
its,O
official,O
web,O
currently,O
located,O
at,O
http,O
/,O
/www.nyiso.com,O
/oasis,O
/index.html,O
or,O
any,O
successor,O
thereto,O
under,O
headings,O
"""Day",O
Ahead,O
Market,O
LBMP,O
-,O
Zonal,O
;,O
Prices,O
West,O
(61752,O
")""",O
(the,O
"""Index""",O
).,O
Leslie,B-PERSON
This,O
is,O
to,O
confirm,O
our,O
conversation,O
relating,O
the,O
Option,O
Agreement.,O
If,O
EFI,B-PERSON
sign,O
",",O
I,O
believe,O
that,O
following,O
changes,O
need,O
be,O
made.,O
1.,O
The,O
last,O
sentence,O
of,O
paragraph,O
No.,O
2,O
should,O
deleted.,O
agreements,O
provide,O
has,O
right,O
assign,O
an,O
affiliate,O
without,O
EI,O
's,O
consent.,O
needs,O
maintain,O
its,O
so,O
during,O
term,O
agreements.,O
Paragraph,O
3,O
modified,O
by,O
adding,O
words,O
"""as",O
"reasonably""",O
before,O
requested,O
in,O
third,O
line,O
thereof,O
;,O
and,O
deleting,O
word,O
"""not""",O
fifth,O
thereof.,O
Additionally,O
deleted,O
because,O
indemnity,O
agreement,O
remain,O
effect,O
for,O
long,O
as,O
perform,O
any,O
services,O
under,O
those,O
Please,O
call,O
if,O
these,O
present,O
problems.,O
Tim,B-PERSON
:,O
Attached,O
is,O
a,O
proposed,O
nondisclosure,O
agreement,O
for,O
use,O
in,O
connection,O
with,O
the,O
upcoming,O
Enron,B-ORG
meeting.,O
It,O
based,O
on,O
form,O
recently,O
used,O
another,O
matter,O
",",O
so,O
should,O
be,O
acceptable,O
to,O
Enron.,O
Please,O
review,O
and,O
comment.,O
This,O
message,O
contains,O
information,O
which,O
may,O
confidential,O
privileged.,O
Unless,O
you,O
are,O
addressee,O
(or,O
authorized,O
receive,O
),O
not,O
copy,O
or,O
disclose,O
anyone,O
any,O
contained,O
message.,O
If,O
have,O
received,O
error,O
please,O
advise,O
sender,O
by,O
reply,O
e-mail,O
@mofo.com,O
delete,O
Thank,O
very,O
much.,O
-,O
Enron-Global,O
Photon,O
NDA.DOC,O
Hi,O
Jeff,B-PERSON
",",O
It,O
was,O
a,O
pleasure,O
to,O
meet,O
you.,O
As,O
we,O
discussed,O
attached,O
please,O
find,O
our,O
company,O
presentation.,O
I,O
really,O
appreciate,O
your,O
support,O
and,O
consideration,O
an,O
as,O
you,O
know,O
goal,O
is,O
get,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
data,O
center,O
people-infrastructure,O
application,O
folks.,O
Again,O
nutshell,O
Cambira,B-ORG
Content,O
Delivery,O
Networking,O
company.,O
Our,O
products,O
allow,O
significantly,O
increase,O
performance,O
reliability,O
scalability,O
while,O
reducing,O
overall,O
cost,O
ownership.,O
We,O
would,O
be,O
happy,O
give,O
technical,O
presentation,O
anyone,O
anyplace,O
at,O
any,O
time.,O
Thanks,O
again,O
for,O
efforts,O
look,O
forward,O
hearing,O
from,O
Best,O
regards,O
John,B-PERSON
Protzel,I-PERSON
Corporation,I-ORG
john,O
@cambira.com,O
Tel,O
:,O
408-748-6407,O
-,O
Presentation,O
Enron.ppt,O
Wilson,B-PERSON
",",O
We,O
are,O
running,O
short,O
on,O
time.,O
planning,O
to,O
sign,O
Tuesday,O
and,O
I,O
hesitate,O
put,O
a,O
new,O
document,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
them,O
at,O
this,O
late,O
date.,O
Would,O
it,O
be,O
easier,O
work,O
with,O
reps,O
/warranties,O
?,O
definitely,O
need,O
an,O
answer,O
from,O
your,O
firm,O
confirming,O
(1,O
),O
enforceability,O
(2,O
obligation,O
the,O
Cities,O
financially,O
support,O
agreement.,O
Also,O
could,O
you,O
provide,O
me,O
Mississippi,B-LOCATION
law,O
defn,O
consequential,O
damages,O
couple,O
examples,O
where,O
Enron,B-ORG
responsible,O
for,O
same,O
under,O
agreement,O
can,O
MDEA,B-ORG
liableto,O
consequentials,O
(absent,O
waiver,O
Your,O
comments,O
previously,O
forwarded,O
draft,O
would,O
greatly,O
appreciated.,O
Kay,B-PERSON
Cynthia,B-PERSON
asked,O
me,O
to,O
forward,O
Chairman,B-PERSON
Ewing,I-PERSON
's,O
substitute,O
bill,O
which,O
is,O
attached.,O
There,O
are,O
two,O
changes,O
that,O
present,O
a,O
problem,O
for,O
us,O
:,O
1.,O
metals,O
have,O
been,O
taken,O
out,O
and,O
2.,O
rulemaking,O
authority,O
manipulation,O
has,O
put,O
in.,O
Please,O
pay,O
close,O
attention,O
pages,O
38,O
39,O
",",O
specifically,O
(2,O
),O
(c,O
).,O
(The,O
good,O
news,O
we,O
told,O
by,O
staff,O
it,O
could,O
worse,O
!,O
also,O
note,O
the,O
House,O
subcommittee,O
mark-up,O
tomorrow,B-DATE
followed,O
full,O
committee,O
on,O
Tuesday.,O
The,O
Senate,O
will,O
then,O
act,O
more,O
quickly,O
than,O
anticipated,O
scheduled,O
next,B-DATE
Thursday.,O
We,O
in,O
process,O
of,O
securing,O
meetings,O
with,O
key,O
tomorrow.,O
-,O
explanation,O
amendment.doc,O
EWING027.PDF,O
Tuesday,B-DATE
Thursday,I-DATE
Thanks,O
for,O
the,O
info,O
additional,O
load.,O
As,O
I,O
understand,O
it,O
",",O
we,O
now,O
have,O
approximately,O
20,O
mw,O
's,O
in,O
South.,O
This,O
is,O
great,O
!,O
Each,O
day,O
review,O
balancing,O
energy,O
prices,O
vs.,O
daily,O
and,O
choice,O
extremely,O
simple,O
:,O
We,O
allow,O
pool,O
to,O
fill,O
this,O
would,O
recommend,O
against,O
buying,O
any,O
hedges,O
power,O
until,O
further.,O
There,O
a,O
good,O
chance,O
that,O
occasionally,O
go,O
negative,O
offpeak,O
/weekends,O
want,O
take,O
full,O
advantage.,O
Do,O
need,O
discuss,O
further,O
?,O
just,O
be,O
on,O
same,O
page.,O
Let,O
me,O
know,O
what,O
you,O
think.,O
JMF,B-PERSON
Mark,B-PERSON
Duffey,I-PERSON
has,O
invited,O
you,O
to,O
"""YPO",O
Houston,B-LOCATION
Chapter,O
-,O
Executive,O
"Breakfast"".",O
Note,O
from,O
:,O
This,O
invitation,O
also,O
been,O
sent,O
via,O
hard,O
copy,O
and,O
blast,O
e-mail,O
(to,O
your,O
assistant,O
),O
",",O
as,O
we,O
want,O
rsvp,O
options,O
be,O
wide,O
open,O
!,O
Perhaps,O
email,O
program,O
doesn,O
't,O
recognize,O
Web,O
address,O
an,O
active,O
link.,O
entire,O
URL,O
paste,O
it,O
into,O
browser.,O
If,O
would,O
like,O
further,O
assistance,O
send,O
Updated,O
03,O
/15,O
/01.,O
YPO,B-ORG
Hey,O
Russell,B-PERSON
",",O
We,O
talked,O
about,O
this,O
point,O
earlier,O
(see,O
an,O
e-mail,O
to,O
you,O
dated,O
September,O
22,O
2000,O
),O
and,O
we,O
agreed,O
that,O
the,O
guarantees,O
would,O
not,O
reference,O
both,O
Enron,B-ORG
North,O
America,O
Canada,I-ORG
Corp.,O
There,O
were,O
a,O
number,O
of,O
reasons,O
for,O
(ie.,O
complexity,O
regarding,O
future,O
amendments,O
differences,O
/peculiarities,O
between,O
Canadian,O
American,O
law,O
possible,O
"""permanent",O
"establishment""",O
issues,O
had,O
discussed,O
etc.,O
).,O
You,O
may,O
also,O
want,O
look,O
at,O
I,O
sent,O
on,O
26,O
(re,O
:,O
East,B-ORG
desk,I-ORG
deals,I-ORG
with,I-ORG
ENA,I-ORG
Is,O
case,O
anymore,O
?,O
think,O
it,O
is,O
better,O
have,O
separate,O
all,O
mentioned,O
in,O
e-mail.,O
Please,O
let,O
me,O
know.,O
Mark,B-PERSON
Powell,I-PERSON
Corp,I-ORG
Attached,O
is,O
a,O
revised,O
Master,O
Setoff.,O
I,O
have,O
made,O
changes,O
&,O
asked,O
for,O
some,O
help,O
on,O
couple,O
of,O
points.,O
Please,O
review,O
the,O
list,O
entities,O
",",O
and,O
we,O
are,O
finalizing,O
our,O
as,O
well.,O
We,O
also,O
obviously,O
need,O
clean,O
up,O
cosmetic,O
things,O
Finally,O
if,O
can,O
get,O
this,O
done,O
lined,O
CFO,O
to,O
sign,O
today,O
would,O
expect,O
you,O
be,O
working,O
identifying,O
your,O
signatory,O
(ies,O
),O
Call,O
me,O
after,O
reviewed,O
this.,O
Thanks.,O
(See,O
attached,O
file,O
:,O
86452.DOC,O
This,O
e-mail,O
message,O
from,O
Legal,O
Department,O
American,O
Electric,O
Power,O
sole,O
use,O
intended,O
recipient,O
(s,O
may,O
contain,O
confidential,O
privileged,O
information.,O
Any,O
unauthorized,O
disclosure,O
or,O
distribution,O
prohibited.,O
If,O
not,O
please,O
contact,O
sender,O
by,O
reply,O
destroy,O
all,O
copies,O
original,O
message.,O
-,O
Steve,B-PERSON
-,O
Thanks,O
for,O
the,O
comments.,O
Here,O
are,O
my,O
responses,O
:,O
1.,O
Introductory,O
Paragraph,O
Section,O
(a,O
),O
is,O
unacceptable,O
as,O
this,O
places,O
an,O
administrative,O
burden,O
on,O
Enron,B-ORG
that,O
currently,O
does,O
not,O
exist.,O
(b,O
acceptable.,O
2.,O
3,O
Changes,O
3.,O
4,O
in,O
section,O
acceptable,O
",",O
however,O
it,O
's,O
strong,O
preference,O
no,O
indemnity,O
language,O
be,O
included.,O
4.,O
5,O
Deletion,O
of,O
provision,O
unacceptable.,O
5.,O
6,O
This,O
deletion,O
fine.,O
6.,O
7,O
change,O
7.,O
9,O
If,O
we,O
still,O
need,O
to,O
discuss,O
above,O
items,O
please,O
call,O
me.,O
Otherwise,O
confirm,O
can,O
move,O
forward,O
based,O
upon,O
your,O
changes,O
and,O
responses.,O
Thanks.,O
Mark,O
Senior,O
Counsel,O
EWS,O
Phone,O
713-345-8897,O
Facsimile,O
713-646-3490,O
E-Mail,O
Mark.Greenberg,O
@enron.com,O
Howarth,O
NYMEX,B-ORG
Membership,I-ORG
Services,I-ORG
March,O
19,O
",",O
2001,O
Notice,O
#,O
MS-18,O
SWITCH,O
OF,O
LESSOR,O
Please,O
be,O
advised,O
that,O
effective,O
with,O
the,O
close,O
of,O
business,O
14,O
following,O
member,O
(s,O
),O
will,O
switch,O
their,O
lessor,O
within,O
Exchange,B-ORG
:,O
John,B-PERSON
D.,I-PERSON
Leahy,I-PERSON
(LAHY-4596,O
Members,O
and,O
Member,O
Firms,O
have,O
(10,O
days,O
from,O
date,O
this,O
notice,O
to,O
advise,O
Corporate,O
Secretary,O
",s",O
Office,O
any,O
claims,O
in,O
accordance,O
withRule,O
2.51.,O
Inquiries,O
regarding,O
above,O
should,O
addressed,O
Department,O
(212,O
299-2379.,O
click,O
on,O
link,O
below,O
indicate,O
you,O
received,O
email.,O
"""http",O
/,O
/208.206.41.61,O
/email,O
/emaillog.cfm,O
?useremailtana.jones,O
@enron.com,O
&refdo,O
c,O
(MS-18,O
")""",O
Note,O
If,O
line,O
nothing,O
happens,O
please,O
copy,O
text,O
between,O
quotes,O
open,O
your,O
internet,O
browser,O
paste,O
it,O
into,O
web,O
site,O
address,O
press,O
Return.,O
Louise,B-PERSON
",",O
I,O
think,O
the,O
following,O
is,O
appropriate,O
and,O
can,O
get,O
done,O
:,O
Dyer,B-PERSON
Base,O
-,O
Same,O
Cash,O
$50,O
Equity,O
$150,O
Mcdonald,B-PERSON
$75,O
$200,O
Parquet,B-PERSON
$100,O
$250,O
know,O
these,O
are,O
at,O
top,O
end.,O
For,O
what,O
it,O
worth,O
other,O
guys,O
got,O
this,O
year,O
were,O
not,O
end,O
because,O
did,O
believe,O
was,O
necessary,O
(Gilbert,O
Page,B-PERSON
Etringer,B-PERSON
Thome,B-PERSON
Wehn,B-PERSON
).,O
If,O
we,O
say,O
actual,O
contract,O
process,O
be,O
slowed,O
so,O
that,O
equity,O
set,O
till,O
November,O
meeting.,O
Also,O
if,O
wont,O
bug,O
you,O
anymore,O
!,O
Chris,B-PERSON
